Chapter 1226: Battle to the Death 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Slayer appeared in the air above Garen quickly, his sharp fingers attempting to gauge out Garen’s eyes.

“It’s over.”

His expression was emotionless.

His fingers stabbed downward like knives.

The strength and speed behind that attack were enough to instantly make Garen’s eyeballs explode, and he could even shatter Garen’s brain at the same time too.

Smack!

All of a sudden, Garen grabbed his palm tightly. Slayer’s finger was suspended just a hair away from his face, but it could not move even a millimeter more.

The immense impact brought both of them crashing down, making them sink into the bottomless ocean.

Blood spread slowly from Garen’s chest, the blood-red water accompanied by hints of pain. As a result, Garen’s previously calm expression finally turned serious.

“How many years has it been… since I got hurt?”

His murmur penetrated Slayer’s eardrums.

In that instant, he abruptly felt a chilling wave of immense threat.

He did not think twice. Even though his average physical fitness levels had doubled, he still retreated instantly, without an ounce of hesitation.

Smack!

But even so, his arms still fell prey to Garen’s tight grip. He looked down to see an eerie smile on Garen’s heart. An ominous premonition crossed his heart.

“Goodbye,” Garen spoke softly.

In that instant, an extremely vast wave of Soul Energy Forces abruptly burst forth from Garen’s body, the invisible Soul Energy instantly forming an enormous sphere that surrounded them both.

This was purely a clashing of Soul Rings, but they could only truly collide when their limbs came into contact, so that their bodies acted as a medium. Garen’s two Soul Rings rushed madly at Slayer’s single Soul Ring.

The clash between the three was like a collision of three spheres. Large torrents of blood gushed out of Slayer’s eyes, ears, nose, mouth, and nose, dying all the seawater around him red.

“You…!!” He stared at Garen disbelievingly. It had never occurred to him that Garen would have two Soul Rings. One of them even had a lingering wisp of Mind Reader’s aura.

At that moment, he finally understood why Garen would choose to take him on, one-on-one, and even why he chose to conduct the battle in these uncharted and unclaimed waters. He offered the condition that the loser would have to obey the victor as bait, but everything, all of it was just a trick to hide the truth from the others. His real aim was to absorb Slayer’s Soul Ring!

In terms of simply excavating Soul Rings, he had already reached the highest pinnacle. Even those who had reached the peak of the Demon Lord One-Ringed Level could not do much better once they got this far. The only way to know that would be to fight them yourself.

But right now, Garen grabbed the opportunity and used their bodily contact to start a battle of Soul Rings. It was no longer a test of power utilization. It was the same as in a regular fight, once the two fighters become embroiled in a close-quarters wrestling match, fighting skills such as throwing punches or evading hits become pointless. It would come down directly to a test of stamina and strength.

“This is truly the end.” There was an eerie smile on Garen’s face.

“No!!!” Slayer’s eyes shone brightly with red light. “Nobody can defeat me! Nobody!!!”

It was the first time he lost his cool. He howled loudly, the muscles all over his body twisting and rippling madly. Many mysterious symbols and words appeared on the surface of his body, spreading from the black hole in his chest and moving all over his body like countless black tadpoles.

“This is?!!!” Garen instantly felt something was wrong, so he quickly released his grip and attempted to retreat.

“Above the Clouds! Thunder Field! Wind Jade!!!” Slayer roared, ferociously and madly.

A large number of high-pressure white electric arches appeared all around him suddenly, and most of these electric arches wove into a white net of electricity that trapped Garen within it.

A torrent of seawater gathered in Slayer’s hands, compressing and condensing, becoming a giant white bow and arrow that was as tall as two people and more than a meter thick.

An enormous ice-crystal arrow, crackling with white electricity, aimed straight at Garen who was retreating backward rapidly.

Boom-boom…

There was the sound of real thunder in the distant sky.

Barroom!!!

A pillar of electricity, several dozen meters thick, descended from the sky and shrunk instantly. It landed on the tip of Slayer’s nocked arrow, turning into a blinding ball of white light.

“Are you trying to pull me down with you!?” Garen’s scalp had gone numb. Even he could not take this amount of power in this Universe, and the same went without saying for Slayer, whose body type was the same as his! Did he have a death wish?!

“Pull you down with me?” The red light in Slayer’s eyes grew brighter and brighter. His voice sounded androgynous, eerily high-pitched, as though the mutation had changed his voice as well. “No, I will reincarnate. You, on the other hand, will fall to the depths of this bottomless oceanic abyss, and become fertilizer for this entire World…”

Garen could already feel his body temperature start to rise rapidly, white smoke was rising from his skin even though it was underwater.

But Garen was no weakling either, he had experienced countless life-or-death battles. The panic from before was instantly suppressed. If he did not fight for his life now, he would surely never have a chance again.

Right now, his Soul Energy Sphere had completely sealed Slayer within it, and Slayer was directly invoking an explosion of lightning. Although he could not break out of the Soul Energy seal, he could still drag Garen into the afterlife with him before the Soul Energy Sphere finished him off!

“Well, I’d like to see who dies first, you or me!!” Brutality rose in Garen’s heart, and he used his palms like knives, abruptly carving out a circle beside him.

“Sky Sword, Four Directional Stars!!!” All the strength in his body surged into his palm blades, and he jumped up fiercely, pouncing downward as he fell. All of the immense Soul Energy was resonating at the same time.

The infinite seawater before him was slashed apart as though cut by a gigantic knife, creating a huge vacuum and isolating the two of them completely. Garen’s twin sabers beckoned forth a huge torrent of seawater and waves, forming the image of a peacock that screeched piercingly. It pounced downward madly, like a gigantic bird on the hunt.

Slayer raised his bow and gathered his Soul Energy together with the lightning, the red light in his eyes sparkling like the sun. The tip of the arrow was absorbing the white water currents around it madly, as though they were countless white strings gathering at the tip of his arrow.

Bloody cracks were forming on the muscles all over his body. His muscle sinews began to snap one after the other, like steel cables that could not take the pressure.

All of a sudden, he relaxed his arm, and the giant white bow and arrow vanished abruptly. The bow fell apart and shattered, whereas the arrow just disappeared from the spot, rushing instead at Garen with unimaginably terrifying speed and strength.

Barroom!!!!!

The entire blue ocean gave a jolt, and then a round blue image made of lightning actually began to appear on the surface of the water. After a mere two seconds, all the seawater had vanished from the several hundred meters taken up by the electric image, and a giant black abyss had appeared on the surface of the ocean.

Strangely, the water around it did not cascade into the black hole. Instead, it just turned straight to ice.

The storm of lightning and the layer of ice spread across the walls of water, engaged in a tug-of-war battle. One half had turned to ice, and the other half was lightning.

The white and the blue fought evenly against each other, dividing and splitting.

Boom!!!

Endless white vapor surged out of the black hole and shot into the air. The white steam became a white pillar of air, shooting straight into the sky.

The infinite pillar of air currents rushed madly into the sky, turning into many white clouds. The white clouds grew thicker as time passed, and the sky grew dimmer. The endlessly clear and sunny sky above the ocean slowly began to darken.

Ker-chak!

A bolt of lightning flashed by, illuminating the gradually darkening ocean.

Whoosh…

There was a sudden and heavy downpour of rain.

The white air current pillar also gradually shrank, becoming thinner and longer. The original white hue slowly turned grey, until it finally became a sea tornado. The giant tornado was connected to the sky and the earth, like a grey-black funnel.

As the hurricane blew at the heavy downpour, rather than falling straight down, the rain formed many disorderly slanted lines in the air.

On an abandoned island nearby.

On a yellow beach, Garen and Slayer both lay face-up at the line where the sand met the sea, all the strength drained from their bodies.

The two of them were covered in pale wounds. Both of Garen’s arms were broken, his chest had sunk in, and one of his ears had been ripped off.

And Slayer had returned to his original form, having broken both legs and lost one arm completely. He had also gone blind in one eye.

It was a draw with injuries on both sides. Neither of them expected that outcome.

Lying on their backs on the beach, both of them had no extra strength left.

“Hah… Haha… I won in the end, after all…” Garen forced a smile. He had lost a lot of blood together with his grievous injuries, and other than his external injuries, he had also sustained massive internal damage. He had a concussion too, which was why his senses were a bit blurry even now.

“You… won?” Slayer smiled with great difficulty. “Or do you think you won?”

“All of your Soul Energy will be mine eventually.” Garen panted heavily and began to turn over, crawling toward Slayer’s direction slowly.

He could no longer remember how long it had been since he got injured like this. But that just showed how high the quality of Slayer’s Soul Ring was, it was far better than the other three Cornerstones.

Slayer’s physical fitness had only been temporarily increased, unlike Garen, who was already usually this powerful. There was still a difference there, which was why he was basically unable to move now, and could not do anything but to watch Garen approach him slowly.

Watching Garen’s slowly crawling body, the red light in his eyes died down, and they gradually lost their glow, returning to their original state that was no different from a normal person.

After the red light faded, confusion and dazedness flashed through Slayer’s eyes.

“I think… I remembered something… something I had once forgotten.”

He murmured dazedly.

Garen dragged himself there step by step. The remaining distance between them was the distance of death.

Strangely, however, Slayer was not scared at all. After the red light vanished from his eyes, he seemed to have forgotten fear, and instead, he only continued to search his own memories, growing more lost as he went.

“I once… forgot some very important things, I think… Very important…” His brain was completely blank, but some familiar yet unfamiliar memories were slowly appearing there.

Finally, Garen moved up to him, reached out a hand slowly, and pressed his forehead.

“It’s over.” He heaved a long sigh.

“That’s right… It’s over,” Slayer replied mysteriously. His gaze had instantly become oddly clear, without a hint of red light. “I remember now…”

Before he knew it, a mist began to rise slowly in his eyes.

“Many, many years ago… I wasn’t like this.”

Garen looked at his clear eyes and paused slightly. He seemed to have understood something as well.

Slayer was never any Slayer to begin with, he was being controlled. That red light from before was the source of that control, and now that he was on the brink of death, he could finally obtain release, returning to the person he used to be.

No wonder Garen sensed that he had two different types of forces in his Soul Energy during their earlier battle.

All this time, Garen had sensed that something was wrong with Slayer.

“I don’t have a future life, and I don’t have many attachments at all.” Slayer’s eyes were strangely peaceful. As though he did not see Garen’s hand suspended above him at all.

Garen was quiet for a moment. His hand grabbed downward abruptly.

Pff.

Chapter 1227: Truth 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

At a small unnamed port somewhere in Slann.

Yuria was wearing a black windbreaker, and he leaped lightly onto a little black boat that rocked constantly on the surface of the sea. Looking at the woman in black who stood before him, his expression was heavy.

“Who on earth are you? What are you planning by calling me here?”

Several days had passed since he rescued Mind Reader, and they had been on the run ever since. After he realized that the latter had lost his mind-reading ability, he decided to see this kind deed of his to the end. He had gone to many lengths to get Mind Reader out of Slann, but just as he was about to leave, he received a mysterious message that told him to wait here for someone at this small port at this very time. They wanted to tell him something extremely important, it said.

He was not surprised to see that the one who invited him out was a woman dressed in black. She wore a veil over her face so he could not see her features properly, but Yuria found that there was something vaguely familiar about her figure and posture.

“You’ve probably noticed it, right?” The woman stood alone on a dilapidated little yacht. There were no signs of anyone else around her. A hint of faint red sunlight shone on the line between the sky and the sea, the lingering rays of a reluctant sun that had completely sunk beneath the horizon.

The sea breeze blew constantly at the duo’s hair and clothes, causing them to flap softly in the wind.

“Noticed what?” Yuria was perplexed, but he already had a gut feeling about it.

The woman laughed. “You’re no fool. A lot of things happen right next to you, and yet you pretend to see them. Or rather, you just look right past them,” said the woman calmly. “My name is Parakeet, you may address me as such.”

“Parakeet?” Yuria frowned. “What are you trying to say? You’re also the one who gave me those messages earlier, yes? Am I right?”

“Yeah… That was me.” Parakeet nodded slightly. She reached out her hand and pulled back some of her black hair. “Do you want to know the truth? If you do, come with me.”

She turned around and walked into the interior of the boat, letting down the boat’s drapes to block his view of what it was like inside.

Yuria hesitated. In truth, he already knew who she was with certainty. It was the mysterious girl who had rescued him once, the one who appeared suddenly and disappeared just as suddenly.

If she wanted to kill me, she’s already had countless chances to kill me. There’s no need for her to do it now…

He steadied his heart and strode onto the boat, ducking past the drapes and entering.

As soon as he went in, he felt a soft warm body fall into his embrace. It was Parakeet, and she wore not even one shred of clothing, her hand reaching for his crotch expertly.

The two of them tumbled into the already-made bed inside.

********************

The seawater surged up and retreated, over and over again.

Garen looked at Slayer, who had sunk deep into the ocean. He was expressionless, feeling neither the joy of victory nor the pity that should be there.

He had assumed that Slayer was the ultimate boss, and Slayer was the strongest boss in the plot as well, but over here, Garen had discovered a few puzzling problems with that theory.

“If he was being controlled, then who is the true mastermind behind everything?”

Garen looked at his current Soul Rings. The third Soul Ring was complete, and the fourth was halfway done. Still, his most precious takeaway was not these Rings, it was the nearly endless rush of knowledge and experience regarding martial arts and killing that surged at Garen the moment Slayer’s Soul Seed fell apart. The reason he could use a single Soul Ring to such overwhelming effect was not only because his own Realm was high enough, more importantly, it was because his knowledge of the laws of this World and Universe far surpassed Garen’s.

Compared to an outsider like Garen, Slayer was a powerful being born and bred here, so naturally, his understanding of this World’s laws went far beyond what an outsider could emulate.

Now that he had this experience and inspiration, Garen finally noticed that his power usage rate, especially when it came to the usage of his Soul Rings, had only risen from what was about half previously to about 80% now. That meant that his power had more than doubled, right!?

“Slayer was so overpowered, and someone was still capable of controlling him… This thing behind him sure is deep…” Garen’s heart was slightly heavy.

He took out his Lighthouse communication device. At this point, there was no longer any more reason for him to continue staying here.

He activated the communication device with a smack, and as soon as he opened it, he received an influx of many messages from Nine-Tailed Fox and the others.

“Where are you? Garen! If you need help, just say it!” Nine-Tailed Fox’s message was very sincere.

“You dead yet? If not, gimme a beep!” Kong Xinxue seemed cold and distant, but there was a hint of concern.

And then there were the messages from his cell phone that had been transferred to the communication device.

“Minister, the east side is safer, and the search team probably won’t actively search for you. I’ll be waiting for you at the little green port, come here if you need any assistance or support.” Yuria sent a message.

“They’re such small fry, and still they dare to block your path, Minister? They have a death wish! Hahaha! Remember to call me if you have any new missions!” Butcher was as brash as ever.

“Sorry, Minister, we couldn’t do anything when you needed us.” Double-Tailed Scorpion’s message.

There was a long list of messages just like those.

Garen read them all, one by one, and then replied to a select few, like Nine-Tailed Fox’s and Yuria’s.

After that, he turned on the communication device’s projector.

Swoosh.

A three-dimensional transparent screen was immediately projected onto the sandy beach before him, and there were several options printed clearly on it, one of which was the option to leave this world. Others included forums, inter-World communication, item transfers, and so on.

Garen stretched out his hand to the ‘Leave World’ option and found that it required a certain number of contribution points.

Beep beep. Suddenly the communication device rang again, and this time it was Yuria.

“Minister, I might have discovered Illusionist’s whereabouts.”

Garen’s finger paused slightly.

“Illusionist…” As his disciple, Yuria had learned many of his skills directly from Garen. In a sense, their relationship was much stronger than expected. To Yuria, who respected his teachers greatly, Garen was like a teacher, but also like an older brother. If he had secrets that he would not tell anyone else, he still would not hide anything from Garen.

That was precisely why Garen vaguely saw of Yuria as something of a legacy or footprint that he was leaving in this World. Garen treated him like a descendant and never even thought of absorbing his Cornerstone ability.

“Where are you now?” he replied directly.

A reply came from the other end quickly.

“At a small port, I’m sending you the coordinates now. Master, I might really need you to do this personally this time. The situation is extremely dire and very troublesome.” Yuria’s words were particularly grave.

Garen mused over it. Yuria was a very honest guy, and he would never simply say anything he was not confident about. If he said it was bad, it must extremely bad.

Now that he had absorbed Slayer, this World no longer posed any threat to him. With his current level of Soul Energy, even if he were tossed into the center of a nuclear explosion, only his body would be destroyed at the most. His Soul Rings and Soul Will could easily find another body and be reborn once more, completely unaffected.

In that case, he might as well help his disciple once before leaving. It would be better if he could find Illusionist as well, an extra Soul Ring never hurt. And, from the depths of his heart, Garen had an inkling that the mastermind behind Slayer could very well be Illusionist. Illusionist had never appeared before, and no one knew his true identity. At the same time, he was the only one who could have controlled the terrifying Slayer, one of the Four Great Cornerstones.

After all, from what he had seen of Slayer’s combat power earlier, try as he may, Garen simply could not think of anyone else who could have mentally controlled Slayer.

“I’ll finish this last thing, and then I’ll leave.” Garen put away his communication device and walked toward the sea lightly. His legs rapidly left a long white line on the surface of the ocean, as though he was walking on dry land, and he headed into the distance, moving faster than a high-speed yacht.

*************************

Yuria embraced Parakeet gently, but his hand wandered all over her body slowly. It was not because he desired her, but because he wanted to feel the many scars littered all over her body. It was a dense swarm of millipede-like scars that looked unnaturally ugly.

Bu Parakeet’s superior skill in that aspect had shown Yuria an intense euphoria that rivaled drugs. That was enough to have him hooked.

“They’re real ugly, huh.”

Parakeet lay naked in Yuria’s arms.

The two of them held each other in the cabin of the boat as the boat slowly sailed into the distance, wandering further and further away on the calm ocean surface.

“No, that doesn’t matter,” replied Yuria honestly. “Is everything you just said true?”

“I’ve no reason to lie to you,” said Parakeet calmly. “The real reason I dared to come look for you here is because Slayer is dead.”

“!!!” Yuria was stunned. “That’s impossible!!” He had seen how terrifyingly strong Slayer was with his own eyes, armies from the three countries surrounded him, and most of the powerhouses joined the fray as well, but they could not even grievously injure him, much less kill him.

“There’s nothing impossible about it.” A gentle smile of release rose over Parakeet’s pretty features. “Slayer and I have Sight Sharing, so when he died, I was the first to know.”

Yuria paused.

“Sight Sharing?” He was slightly confused about the true nature of the relationship between this mysterious girl, Parakeet, and Slayer.

Parakeet did not answer immediately, but instead, she buried her head deep into Yuria’s chest. Savoring the warmth of Yuria’s body like a cat. Her own body was so cold, it barely had any warmth at all.

“You…?” As soon as Yuria spoke, she pressed her finger to his lips lightly.

“Did you know?” Parakeet opened her eyes wide, looking up and into Yuria’s eyes.

“I’m not actually as pure as you think I am…”

Yuria did not say anything and just looked at her confusedly. He liked this girl, even though she was mysterious, even though he knew far too little about her, he still liked her. And she had saved him before. That was reason enough.

“I… am the tool Slayer used for releasing himself,” Parakeet said with a smile. “Do you understand? Releasing.”

She moved her body lightly.

“Just like this.”

She instantly used her body to completely envelop a part of Yuria’s. The two of them merged deeply once more.

“Why…!” No matter how generous a man was, he would still be unable to accept that the girl he liked was actually another man’s…

Yuria was the same. He immediately felt as though the girl in front of him was unfamiliar and did not belong to him anymore. That feeling of destroyed innocence and the ecstasy coming from his lower body left him with extremely complicated and conflicting feelings.

Chapter 1228: Truth 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Sexual release is the only way to balance out Slayer’s violence.” Parakeet spoke as though this had nothing to do with her, wearing a faint smile on her face. “Hence, I was chosen. This body had been patched up, repaired, and used for a long time, and it’s also picked up many extremely useful skills to help him achieve release.” She moved her body rhythmically. “See, isn’t this skill helpful? Don’t you feel great?”

Yuria suddenly felt a surge of displeasure and distorted emotions coming from his heart. All of a sudden, he felt as though the girl on top of him was so unbelievably dirty. So much so that he almost wanted to puke, but his body continued to produce that unceasing sense of euphoria.

On one hand, he wanted to escape from here, but on the other, he could not help but continue to meet her advances, thrusting unstoppably.

“Did you know?” Parakeet’s smile faded. “The truth is, my employer is Illusionist. You can send this information to your teacher. I think he would be very happy to know that.”

“What!?” Yuria’s heart grew unbearably pained. “The reason you approached me this time was so that you could reach my teacher?!”

“That’s right… If I could just sleep with him, I’d be willing to do anything. Tsk-tsk… What a powerful man.” A pure smile of adoration appeared on Parakeet’s face. “Did you know? He was the one who killed the practically invincible Slayer with his own hands. Even Sea God had to retreat when faced with Slayer’s final form…”

Smack!!

Yuria slapped her fiercely. He got up and quickly put on his clothes, then he rushed out of the boat cabin, panting heavily.

Parakeet’s left cheek swelled up quickly, and as she dazedly watched Yuria run outside, she suddenly began to laugh maniacally.

***********

Huff… huff…

Yuria panted heavily, his head a complete mess. He tried to find a reason that would justify Parakeet lying, but no matter how he analyzed it, no matter how much he wanted to lie to himself, Parakeet’s expert and exceptional skills in bed, as well as the wounds on all the crucial parts of her body, all proved that everything she said was true.

Ah!!!!

Out of nowhere, Yuria began to roar madly, as though trying to viciously vent the heaviness in his chest. By strangely, his roar shook the fish in the surrounding sea and made them float to the surface, belly up. Large schools of fish had all been knocked unconscious.

The sound waves formed many ripples that spread out wide and crashed into the distance.

The power behind this simple sound wave seemed to be a bit overpowered.

Yuria himself was shocked by this sudden change. He abruptly silenced his voice and looked down. There was a web of tiny cracks on the deck of the boat beneath his feet as well, and the cracks spread outward from the center. They were clearly also formed by the sound waves from his angry venting shout.

“Have you noticed it?” Parakeet’s voice came from behind him. She walked out slowly, wearing white night-robes to cover her heavily scarred body.

“Your power and your body are growing stronger and stronger, and sturdier as well.”

Yuria’s brain was a mess. He did not dare to turn around and look, just the sound of her voice already awakened the unstoppable impulse to kill in his heart. His disappointment and depression kept piling up in his chest, growing taller and stronger.

“Do you want to know why?” Parakeet laughed. “It’s all for one thing. Yuri’s Kiss.”

“Then why did you come after me?” Yuria turned around. He was no longer a young, naive child, he was just emotionally vulnerable. He steadied his emotions and said, “What’s Yuri’s Kiss?”

Parakeet walked up to him, and they stood at the jetty together.

“Illusionist caught them so that they could invent something for you.”

“For me?” The answer in Yuria’s heart was growing clearer.

“That’s right, for you.” Parakeet’s smile grew even more bewitching. “Could it be that you still can’t believe that Illusionist, the leader of White Crab, is actually your younger sister, Yurijue?”

Yuria’s brain was even more confused now.

“Xiaojie… Illusionist… Mother…” He lowered his head and wiped his face forcefully.

“Mother?” Parakeet shook her head. “Your mother died several dozen years ago. Light Path is not your mother, all of it was a dream your little sister made for you. Mother, relatives, friends, family… Do you believe me? I’ve followed you for more than eighty years, and we’ve slept together at least several thousand times, do you believe that? Hehehe…” She began to laugh manically again.

“No way!!” Yuria’s expression sank. “Don’t you try to trick me!” He shoved Parakeet away and walked toward the cabin again.

Parakeet stood alone at the helm, smiling. She looked at Yuria’s back when he walked away as though she was looking at a child throwing a tantrum.

“Tell your teacher that Illusionist is at White Crab Island.”

When he heard the voice from outside, Yuria tried his best to calm down his emotions, taking out his phone quickly and sending a message to his teacher, Garen. But his brain was still a whirling mess of confusion.

“No, she might be lying to me, she’s just saying it to get to me, I shouldn’t believe her so easily. I have to find Xiaojie, and ask her myself! And Mother… Mother…” He remembered that Mother knew perfectly well that he was looking for her and still refused to appear, disappearing without a trace even until now. And his younger sister had suddenly vanished mysteriously too, while others could easily get a hold of his location whenever they wanted, leading to the attacks by White Crab. That included Teacher Garen, Big Sister Nine-Tailed Fox and the rest, everyone had been ambushed.

White Crab’s motives had always been unknown. They defeated him many times, but they never had any intention of killing him.

“I have to get to the bottom of this!” Yuria gripped his fist tightly.

***********************

Under the cover of night, Garen slowly entered the nearest port. There were several large white yachts stopped in the bay within the marina, and one ship was slowly sailing out of it.

The place where Garen alighted onto the port was also the darkest part of it.

He looked into the distance directly in front of him and saw a horizontal road ahead. A car just happened to drive past a streetlamp as he watched, and there was a young man with his earphones on, holding his phone as he strolled past leisurely.

At night, this port seemed quiet and orderly.

“This is the port Yuria mentioned.”

He had changed out of his torn-up rags into a clean white suit, provided by a flashy middle-aged man who had passed by him on a cruise ship. It looked costly and was clearly used for formal dinners.

“Excuse me, are you Mr. Garen?” Suddenly, a woman’s voice came from the darkness on Garen’s right.

“You are?” Garen had noticed this woman hiding behind the crates a long time ago, he simply did not point her out. Now that she had spoken, it clearly showed that she was the person sent here to receive him, waiting for him here in advance.

“I am the person Mr Yuria arranged to greet you, please come with me.” The woman walked out naturally. She wore a black office lady skirt and looked just like a regular white-collar worker. Her looks were very average as well, she was the type that did not catch any attention at all.

Garen naturally followed her to the roadside nearby. There was a white car parked there, and the two of them got in, one in the front seat and one in the back.

At this point, Garen did not worry about traps or anything like that, his abilities allowed him to be completely fearless of whatever the woman might be planning.

“Where are we going?” he asked nonchalantly.

“Lady Light Path has wanted to meet you for the longest time, but she can’t make an appearance right now, so we borrowed Yuria’s name to receive you. I hope you’ll understand,” the woman said in a low voice, finally revealing the truth.

“Light Path?” Garen remembered who that was now, it was Yuria’s mother, the woman who used to be the top bounty hunter in this world. He was wondering why Yuria did not come to meet him in person. It was slightly illogical considering Yuria’s personality.

“You guys sure are something, making me go to her,” Garen said off-handedly.

“No… Please don’t take it that way,” said the woman hurriedly. “We’re very, very sorry, but we have no choice, the lady, she… Sigh, you’ll know when you get there, sir.”

Garen was not particularly bothered, and just nodded.

“Get driving then.”

In the night, the car accelerated slowly, driving toward the main road.

Just then, near the port, Yuria just got out of a cab. He dialed Garen’s number hurriedly, but no one picked up. Glancing at his phone, he saw that there was no signal.

“Damned stupid phone! What the hell is this!”

Ever since he separated from Parakeet on the ocean, he had been in a vicious mood and decided to get to the truth behind all of this no matter what.

It just so happened that he was to meet Teacher Garen here, but he never thought that there would be no phone signal here.

“There’s probably a signal jammer here,” he hazarded a guess inwardly. “Parakeet invited Teacher over here using my name, but she won’t let me receive him. What on earth is her goal?” He was frustrated, but he did not worry about Garen’s safety at all. Considering how strong the Minister was, and how he had even killed Slayer, what were the chances of a terrible situation like the Three Nations’ allied raid happening in a small place like this?

Since the wanted order came down from the Three Nations, the truth was they would be grateful if Garen never picked a fight with them. They would never anger him on purpose first.

Yuria flagged down another cab quickly and drove toward the distance. In the car, he asked the driver.

“Cabbie, does your phone have a signal?”

The driver gave him a strange look and waved his phone slightly.

“That is weird, it looks like there isn’t much of a signal here. Strange, I just noticed it too.”

Yuria instantly felt helpless.

The signal only returned after the car went on for quite some distance.

*****************

“Hello? Yuria?” Garen took out the communication device’s earphone and stuffed it into his ear. “I’m fine, you don’t have to come meet me anymore. Something came up on my side, I’m going to meet someone, don’t worry.”

Garen sat in a bright, wide reception hall. The whole floor of the hall was made of black marble, such that he could almost see his reflection in it.

And right now, there was a young woman sitting opposite him. She wore pearl earrings and a long black lace dress, looking dignified and majestic, beautiful and graceful. The only flaw within this beauty was that the woman was blind in both eyes. She could not see anything at all.

Hanging up the call, Garen sat on the chair with his back held straight. He casually pressed a few buttons on the table, adjusting the brightness of the wall light beside him slightly and turning it dimmer.

“Alright, Lady Light Path, let us now talk about what happened between you and the siblings, Yuria and Yurijie. You said just now that those two aren’t actually your children at all, what does that mean?”

The woman sat properly on her seat and sipped at her tea lightly. If someone could look at the hem of her skirt underneath the table, they would notice that she did not actually have legs. They seemed to have been amputated by someone.

“It’s just as you understand it, it’s exactly what I just said,” she replied, gently and deeply.

Chapter 1229: Truth 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen watched Light Path pick up her teacup slowly and sip from it. The aroma of tea wafted around the living hall.

“It looks like you have been trying to avoid meeting Yuria on purpose.”

Light Path nodded.

“You are absolutely right, I have been avoiding him on purpose. Or rather, I’ve been avoiding them.”

Garen had also collected a significant amount of information in his Energy Machine Imprint, so when he heard that, he could also guess what she meant.

But he still needed Light Path to unveil all of the mysteries. He turned his gaze to the woman seated across from him.

Light Path was a very elegant woman with fair skin and looked like the slightly voluptuous wife from a rich family, rather than a powerful bounty-hunting mercenary.

“I don’t know if you’ve heard the name Zhi Jinqin,” she said in a low voice.

“Zhi Jinqin?” Garen searched through his memories. “Never heard of it.” He shook his head, the name was completely foreign to him.

“Then you must be familiar with her other name,” Light Path smiled slightly, “Yurijie.”

Garen frowned.

“What do you mean? What does it matter if Yurijie has another name?”

“Of course it doesn’t matter,” Light Path continued. “But what if that name was also the Commander-in-Chief of the White Crab Army? Would you still say it doesn’t matter?”

“The Commander-in-Chief of the White Crab Army? Are you joking?” Garen instantly laughed. He knew Yurijie, that weak little girl, and she had studied under him as well, so she could also be considered his disciple, like Yuria. However, Yuria had too much potential, so Garen neglected Yurijie most of the time. She was not very conspicuous, and now Light Path was suddenly telling him that this little girl was the Commander-in-Chief of an international mercenary army like White Crab? It was as absurd as someone randomly running up to you and saying that Old Wang next door was the military commander of some country.

“I’m starting to wonder if you really are Light Path. How can you prove your identity to me?” said Garen casually, leaning into his chair.

“That would be easy to prove.” Light Path clapped her hands, as though she had long since expected this.

The woman who had driven Garen here earlier appeared again and placed a box in front of Garen.

“Please look at this.”

The woman retreated, and Light Path extended her hand slightly, signaling Garen to open the box and check.

“There are pictures of the siblings and me inside, all the photos starting from when they were fifteen, as well as all of my identification documents, and most crucially, my occupational papers. As a mercenary and a bounty hunter, I have my own security code with the National Security Agencies of many large countries, you can feel free to check my information through your connections.”

Garen opened the box and flipped through its contents.

“I can understand that there’s no reason for you to lie to me, but I still find it extremely hard to believe that Yurijie is the White Crab Commander-in-Chief.” He remembered how Yurijie acted around him, she had always been obedient and inconspicuous. No, she could barely even be called inconspicuous, she was practically non-existent.

Suddenly he felt something amiss. He had always been an extremely alert man, but until now, he still did not have a constant, deep impression of the person he had stayed with, day in and day out, while he was teaching her his skills.

Garen instantly felt something was wrong.

Light Path, who had been paying close attention to his expression, smiled slightly.

“It seems like you’ve noticed something wrong as well.”

Garen frowned and pulled up all of his memories regarding Yurijie, checking them carefully. But he noticed that no matter how he checked them, his information on Yurijie seemed to constantly covered in a veil of fog, so everything was blurry and unclear.

His frown relaxed. “That’s somewhat interesting.”

Light Path smiled and took out a phone. The screen was illuminated and showing several pictures of a girl’s life.

“Look at this.”

Garen took it and saw that the phone screen was slowly showing pictures of a girl who looked a lot like Yurijie.

“These are the pictures from the life of a girl called Zhi Jinqin from more than seventy years ago. I pulled them out from a country’s Security Databank. You can check the Databank any time,” Light Path said with a straight face. “Yurijie and Zhi Jinqin are essentially the same person.”

“Then how would you explain her sending the White Crab Army to assault us?” Garen asked, putting down the phone.

“Zhi Jinqin is a psychopath.” Light Path smiled wryly. “If I said that she cut off my legs and blinded my eyes, would you believe me?”

Garen raised an eyebrow. “Just what is happening here? Please explain it to me in detail.” He knew the summarized Plot, but he never knew that there were so many details hidden so deep.

Light Path nodded. She picked up her cup slowly and sipped from it.

“In that case, I’ll need to start from more than eighty years ago…”

********************

International Center of Disease Control.

In the clean large white hall, many medical workers were running past each other, and several emergency stretchers were constantly being sent to the many different research labs. Some of the workers had gone to get samples and reports regarding all sorts of different data, and they walked hurriedly, going in and out of the many large labs.

“How is the situation! Right now!” Inside the Central Information Hub.

Several people dressed in white uniforms were gathered together, discussing how to deal with the disease emergency.

“It’s not looking good! The range of the virus contagion has expanded by fifteen times over one night! Initial evaluations have confirmed that it is an airborne contagion!” said a white-haired old man nervously.

“It feels like we’ve gone back to that Carpo Virus incident back then…” Another old professor sighed. “Immediately the highest Code Red alarm, and inform the National Health Ministries. We have to control the spread of the Yuri’s Kiss virus as soon as possible. Announce the symptoms.”

“What about quarantine methods? And disinfection measures?” someone else asked urgently.

“High-temperature disinfection, the aerial quarantine area must not be smaller than one kilometer!” replied an old professor urgently.

“This virus is too terrifying! The mortality rate is actually higher 99%!”

Beep!!!

All of a sudden, the piercing wail of a siren rang out through the entire center, and a screen instantly appeared on the left of the old professors.

It was a map of the world.

The map started off completely blue, but right now, on the three main continents, a red dot was spreading at a speed fast enough to be seen by the naked eye.

“This is…!!”

Everyone was shocked by the sudden turn of events. Thr live broadcast showed that the spread of the virus, indicated by the red area, was moving faster than anyone could have imagined.

“At this rate… within twenty hours… the whole world will have been utterly infected!!” Someone began to panic.

“Is… Is this the end of humanity?!” The old professor’s voice started to tremble.

**********************

In the busy capital city

The compact crowds squeezed against each other, flowing endlessly along the pedestrian street.

Bang.

A cola bottle fell from the hands of a little girl carrying a doll.

“Yangyang? What’s the matter?” Beside her, her mother seemed to have noticed something was wrong with the little girl, so she bent down and frowned, asking.

“Mommy… My head hurts…” The girl raised her head, her face white and crumpled.

“Did you catch a cold?” The mother crouched down and touched her daughter’s forehead.

But a terrifying thing occurred, the little girl’s eyes began to bleed with bright red blood that flowed down her cheeks like two bloody streams.

The mother was completely stunned.

Just a moment later.

Ahhhh!!!!

The screams seemed to explode from different parts of the city at the same time. Men and women, old and young.

The crowd had been thrown into an uproar. Many people covered their eyes, but the blood kept flowing down their cheeks, dripping onto the floor.

Countless viruses multiplied quickly and without stopping in the air, and flowed with the air currents, reaching further and further out. Humans, animals, even plants, everything became a target for their infection.

****************

Ka-chak.

The picture was set into film just like that.

“Not bad, let’s have one more.” A pair of newlyweds was taking wedding photos on top of the skyscraper.

The photographer smiled wide, telling the two of them to lean closer to each other.

Smiling, the groom pulled the bride into his arms gently, then closed his eyes and leaned over to kiss her.

“Kellen…” Before he touched his girlfriend’s soft and sexy lips, he heard her panicked and terrified voice. “Kellen, your eyes… they’re bleeding!”

“What?” The groom felt moisture on his face, so he reached out his hand and wiped it. The blood all over his hand pierced his eyes.

“Wha… what is this!?”

“Send him to the hospital, now!! Quick, quick, quick!!” The photographer was the first to respond.

****************

“Yuri’s Kiss.”

“Up until now, infected patients have appeared in 50% of the Red Nation’s territory, and according to the report from the International Center of Disease Control, this virus must be controlled immediately, or else it could very well spread to the rest of the world within twenty hours!”

The International Union started an emergency long-distance conference.

“Time is short, I’ve already summoned Special Forces, the special division whose members were modified specially for disease prevention are taking the necessary measures for quarantine and the like.”

The President of the Red Nation looked solemn.

“All factories will stop production and do everything in their power to aid the disease control!” the President of Slann said sternly.

“Seal off all the relevant ports and prevent exit or entry, quarantine the Red Nation for now, and remind all the citizens to wear the emergency-distributed gas masks.” The President of the Black Federation suggested an effective strategy.

“I’ve sent the general proposal to the two of you, do execute it as soon as you finish reading through it. We don’t have much time.”

“We’re putting all our efforts into creating a vaccine for the virus.”

“Don’t we at least have a way to slow down the spread of the virus?”

“No. My team of experts told me that this virus primarily destroys the human brain and nerves, and since it’s too fast-acting and too powerful, the immune system doesn’t even have time to react. Rather than calling it a virus, it’s more like a weapon of war, a biological weapon specially designed to kill people!” said the Red Nation President in a deep, low voice.

“I got some news from my information network, apparently the source of this Yuri’s Kiss came from the inventions of an organization called White Crab Island. The experts told me that the place is now constantly broadcasting a special wave that can use the magnetic field of the planet to spread all over the planet. At the same time, it’s constantly providing this Yuri’s Kiss virus with the best living conditions and even the energy for it to grow!”

“It’s like a wireless charger?” The Black Federation President’s face darkened.

“That’s right.”

“Summon the elite troops right now. Within three hours, I want to see the White Crab Island completely sunk into the ocean,” said the Slann President coldly.

“Why don’t we just sink it with bombs?”

“We need the relevant information to save the citizens who have already been infected.”

“Then it’s decided.”

“Agreed.”

Chapter 1230: Truth 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You mean, Zhi Jinqin and Yuria have been alive for more than eighty years? And because of an accident which caused Yuria to lose his memory, Zhi Jinqin used her identity as Illusionist to weave the dream of a good life consisting of loved ones, family, and friends for her brother?” Garen could not believe it.

Light Path calmly sat in her seat and drank her tea.

“It’s roughly like that. You comprehend it very accurately.”

Garen knitted his brows together.

“If it is as you say so, there are a lot of things which would actually make sense.”

There was a glint of sadness in Light Path’s eyes.

“It is as how you comprehend it.”

“Illusionist, Zhi Jinqin who loved her elder brother very much, was born from pain. She was taken by her father as a experimental subject who killed her beloved playmates her favorite pet. Every day, she could only bear an endless variety of modifications and was regarded as a monster by her mother. She was beaten, abused, and disfigured. She was the most special individual among the Four Great Cornerstones as she possesses the Immortal Body. She could not be killed nor die, but only only live on in suffering. The only warmth she has was her brother, Yuria,” Light Path quietly stated.

“Yuria was a genius and could quickly master any skill and ability he learns, almost like a veteran who has been immersed in them for many years. He was enthusiastic and advocates for justice. Upon discovering that his sister had been abused as an experimental subject, he tried to stop it many times but to no avail and was beaten viciously. Finally, he left out of anger and tried to seek an external aid to rescue his sister but he was accidentally killed by his father. This led to the huge change in Zhi Jinqin’s temperament. She seriously injured and killed her father and after controlling a large group of people, she set up White Crab.” Light Path poured out the story in one go.

“This was how White Crab came about in the beginning.”

“There was a blaze in Red Nation more than eighty years ago. It razed to the ground a huge bio-pharmaceutical base which was worth tens of thousands of investments. It happens to be exactly the same as the starting point of the incident you mentioned,” Garen had also found relevant information.

“You are right. It was that fire, which was only a destruction to cover up all the sinful research,” Light Path spoke in a deep voice.

“So what about their mother?” Garen asked.

“No idea. Maybe she died or maybe she escaped. But that’s not important anymore.” Light Path shook her head. “The most important thing now is that Zhi Jinqin has gone mad.”

“Mad?” Garen had a bad premonition. “What do you mean?!”

Light Path closed her eyes slowly and breathed deeply.

“The truth from decades ago, the tragic fate, and the end of the experiment. All of these had brought tremendous pain to Zhi Jinqin. Besides pain, everything that the outside world had brought her was despair. Being able to hold out and going crazy only now, honestly speaking, I am a little surprised.”

Garen did not say anything but continued to listen to her.

“The most powerful person in the world is actually not Slayer, but Illusionist, who controls Slayer. That is, Zhi Jinqin,” Light Path paused, and her breathing became a little rapid, seemingly recalling some bad memories.

“She modified my memory for decades. Of course, I am still considered lucky as compared to the strongest killer, Situ Ci, whose memory was also modified. Because his will was too firm, and he awakened in advance, he was killed by Zhi Jinqin halfway. At that time, I had felt that something was amiss.”

“Situ Ci? Is that the person who disguised as the father of the Yuria siblings?” Garen asked.

“Yes.” Light Path nodded. “It is him.”

“I didn’t know him at all. I originally had my own lover, my own family… But because of Zhi Jinqin, who thinks that we are very similar to their parents, so everything had changed…” She showed a tragic smile. “Everything is ruined and destroyed.”

“If everything you say is true,” Garen calmly said, “then what is the purpose of you specifically inviting me over here and telling me the truth?”

“You’re indeed the rumored Sword Master. Your words are as clear-cut and prompt as your sword,” Light Path complimented slightly in a sentence. “I just want to have a request, a small request.

“Presumably… There are already elite troops heading to White Crab Island at this moment?” She was being a little mysterious.

“What do you mean?”

Garen had just popped the question when his communication device immediately rang out wildly. It was not a call request but a large number of text messages.

He quickly took it out and scanned through the vast messages. His expression changed instantly.

“Yuri’s Kiss?!! Zhi Jinqin??” There were Nine-Tailed Fox’s text message, as well as Night Water’s, the never-met-before Sea God’s, his original subordinates, Kong Xinxue’s, and etc… They were the text messages from all those who were related.

The most prominent of these was Yuria’s. Nearly all the causes and consequences of the matter were stated in the text message.

In the end, he still regarded Garen as his teacher.

“If this is the end of the world, then maybe I will become the final protagonist.” There was a big smile in Yuria’s final text message.

“This bastard!!” Garen was enraged. Zhi Jinqin’s identity had been proven without a doubt. If the cure for Yuri’s Kiss was not discovered, and the source was not resolved in twenty hours’ time, the whole planet would turn into a dead zone.

Although Garen did not care about the life and death of the people on the planet, at least there were friends such as Kong Xinxue, Yuria and others whom he cared for a little. Sitting idly and being indifferent was not his style.

“Only causing trouble,” Garen was speechless and stood up. “It feels like I’m watching a movie, even more so the big scene in a sci-fi movie. I’ll ask for the last time. Are you sure everything you said is true?”

He looked at Light Path solemnly. With his close-range sensing ability, he could observe all of Light Path’s physiological activity indexes. Sensing whether a person was lying was not the only thing he could do. He could even tell when someone would want to go to the toilet, or when would someone completely digest their food, or when someone would burp. All these small details was clearly grasped by him.

Garen’s gaze slightly radiated a powerful sense of pressure. Through this, he was finally confirming whether the information from Light Path was true.

“I dare to guarantee with my life and glory,” Light Path answered affirmatively.

“About Yuri’s Kiss, speak out your request,” Garen felt that time was running out. He did not want such a beautiful planet to become a dead zone. That would be too boring. And without people, there would no one to produce products for eating, drinking, and entertainment. It was also unknown whether he, as a Transmigrator, was immune to this kind of virus. He had already planned to head to White Crab Island to personally check whether the situation was true.

“My request.” Light Path paused a little. She looked up and revealed her bright forehead. “You must kill Zhi Jinqin. This is my only wish and prayer.”

Garen knitted his brows slightly together. He saw that Light Path was gently pressing her forehead onto the table. Her expression was full of sincerity and determination.

“There’s no need for you to say that. If she is really a scoundrel like what you’ve said and has created all these deceptions, I will kill her.”

He turned around and walked out.

When he was about to reach the door, Light Path’s voice came again.

“Zhi Jinqin has completely gone crazy.”

Creak. Garen turned the doorknob and walked out slowly. His figure disappeared into the night on the outside world like a wind.

His mind was still playing back the previous text message from Sea God.

“Zhi Jinqin wants to destroy all human beings and annihilate all life except for hers and her brother Yuria’s. I am asking you in the name of the Lighthouse Alliance in the hope of getting your help.”

“She wants to become the first Eve and create a new world. She thinks that everything is out of control, so she has decided to simply turn the table. This time it all depends on you! The strongest Sword Master Garen, you are now saving the world on behalf of all mankind. By the way, I have been infected along with Kong Xinxue and Li Hua. If you don’t succeed, then…” Night Water’s purposely relaxed tone was filled with an irrepressible panic.

“Also, before we can get rid of the infection, we cannot leave this world. Lighthouse has issued a directive for the prevention of the epidemic, completely cordoning off this area we’re in. Only after the epidemic is resolved then can we leave.”

“Giving me another reason,” Garen murmured. He never thought that he would lose. Be it Slayer or Zhi Jinqin, they were just a small stepping stone he had encountered by chance in this world.

*********************

A huge tornado-shaped silvery-white mountain stood on a vast blue sea.

The sea crashed against this several kilometers-tall giant tornado-mountain from the side. On the vast blue sea under the night sky, the moonlight shone onto the sea surface, reflecting a large armada of ships and warships on the surrounding sea waters.

The combat helicopters and drones that took off from the distant aircraft carrier were as dense as a swarm of bees as they circled around the tornado-mountain, shooting down bright and clear white light beams.

There were Red Nation’s fleet, Slann’s fleet, and the furthest Black Federation’s fleet of aircraft carriers.

Yuria half-squatted on the bow of a white warship. Unlike the bustling marines on the deck far behind him, he was holding a cigarette in his mouth and the red cigarette smoke was slightly shining in the darkness. The sea breeze was blowing the collar of his windbreaker upwards.

With the inexplicable advancement of his strength, his previous memories were also restored.

“Qin…” Looking at the several kilometer-tall giant tornado-mountain in the distance, his memory returned to the time that was decades ago.

Who was always looking out of the window at the distant world? The blurred shadow of that figure, from young until now, slowly emerged from the depths of his memory.

“I once said I would give you a surprise and a miracle,” Yuria whispered. “Forgive me for not accomplishing it.”

The more than eighty years of memoryies was chaotic, but he did not blame Qin. If there was anyone in the world who really understood her, perhaps there was only him who was left.

Pain, despair, darkness, and endless gloom.

Being unable to see, hear or smell, and only being able to feel the world by depending on other people’s body; to others, immortality was a wealth, but it was only an abyss to her.

Yuria stood up, and a silvery-white light flashed in his hand in a trice. It was a short, sharp silver dagger.

“Brother, are you here too?” A familiar voice suddenly broke into his ear as if it had directly sounded in his mind.

“Qin?!” Yuria was stunned. “Is it you? Qin!?”

The night gradually brightened, and on the horizon behind the tornado-mountain, a dazzling touch of gold gradually lit up.

The sun slowly descended from the horizon, and a head emerged, slowly releasing an infinite vast light and heat.

Chapter 1231: Ending 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Brother, have you come to save me? Qin is so happy…” The voice was soft and warm as if directly permeating from the air.

Yuria was silent and unable to speak.

Smack.

A big hand landed hard on the back of his shoulder.

“What’s wrong? Standing here daydreaming all alone?”

The Commodore of the ship was also one of those who had been infected. One could say that everyone here came with an intention to die. They were deployed as they were discovered to be infected with Yuri’s Kiss.

If this mission could not be completed, then they would also be dead anyway. So there was no need to worry about boosting the troops’ morale because everyone understood that if they did not fight, they would die.

The Commodore was a northerner, tall and strong, cheerful and bold, and clicked with Yuria, who was on-board.

“No. Nothing,” Yuria smiled. His emotions were somewhat down. When he thought of everything in the past about Yurijie, or Zhi Jinqin, there was always a kind of unspeakable blockage in his heart.

“Don’t worry! This time, there’s a large number of powerhouses. No matter how powerful she is, all the three nations’ elites are all here. There will be no mistakes!” The Commodore was very confident.

“Maybe…” Yuria barely managed a smile.

“Black Federation’s strongest King Thunderclap has also come. With Red Nation’s Prince Huang Gu, our Vulture No.1, and adding on each of their respective elite guardian powerhouses, dealing with White Crab is definitely a piece of cake. If it wasn’t for the rush for time, a few long-range missiles blowing up the place would directly settle the matter,” the Commodore said dismissively.

Yuria responded with a smile at the side, but his mind was still recalling the sister’s voice he had heard just now.

“Look! Someone went on the island!” Suddenly, the Commodore pointed to the distant sea.

Yuria followed his gaze and just happened to see a small group of people wearing stealth suits sneaking onto White Crab Island. This kind of stealth suit did not really cloak the body, but it was an optical camouflage suit that could automatically change color. The luster of the color would continuously change accordingly with the environment, causing the human body to integrate into the environment as one.

The small team of people could hardly be seen moving from afar.

“That is the Special Operations Team from Black Federation. They should be going to test the water first. The radio notice has been sent over ten minutes ago, but there is no reply at all. Could it be that these White Crab Army have fled?” A few people came from behind the Commodore and sneered loudly. “Damn, making us come all the way to specifically fix the position. Is this rubbish virus really so terrific?!”

“What do you think?”

“Yuria, is this stuff really produced by your sister?” Some people did not believe it.

Yuria could only smile bitterly with silence and apologies.

Not only their ship, but many other fleets were also watching and waiting for the small team of elite powerhouses who entered the island to send back news.

There was still communication at the beginning. However, after that, it had been silent. Suddenly there were a few screams on the radio, and then everything was calm.

**************************

“Still resisting stubbornly!”

On another black ship, a tall and thick-haired man in a military uniform took on an unsightly expression. As the highest commander of Black Federation’s current operation, he had actually lost more than a dozen of the powerhouses whom he sent out, and no accurate intelligence was transmitted back at all.

“Prepare the fleet. Indiscriminate bombing for ten minutes!” He waved his hand, and the adjutant behind quickly began to convey the command.

Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom! Boom!!

The continuous booming of the bombardment instantly thundered rhythmically. The shells landed on the tornado-shaped silvery-white mountain and blasted innumerable holes of different sizes on its surface. Smoke and dust suffused, and gravel scattered. There were tall splashes of sand waves everywhere on White Crab Island, and the sea surface shook slightly. More than a dozen warships from Black Federation launched the attack simultaneously, coupled with aircraft bombing, in which countless incendiary bombs were dropped. White Crab Island was completely caught in a sea of flames.

“King Thunderclap, what are you doing!? We need the data inside. Who asked you to directly order indiscriminate bombing and use the incendiary bomb?” Dissatisfied voices came from the other three forces through wireless communication.

However, Black Federation could not be bothered and was still bombing away.

“Don’t mind them! Continue!” King Thunderclap was arrogant and never listened to other people’s opinions. He felt that since his strength and capability were far more powerful than the others, even if the strategy was wrong, he could still correct it with his own strength.

****************

“This scumbag of Black Federation!!” On a Red Nation fleet, a handsome man in a red coat flashed a stern look.

“Failing to see the larger issue and disregarding the overall situation. I will surely storm the Federation Capital one day.” The man held a scarlet wide-blade sword in one hand. There were some delicate and complicated patterns engraved on the hilt which looked quite extraordinary.

“Your Royal Highness will surely reinvigorate the situation in the country and re-establish the true centralization of monarch power.” A person behind him in a black robe was acutely flattering.

“Pass down the command. Prepare to charge onto the island. Time is running out.” Prince swept a glance across Black Federation’s fleet coldly. “If such a virus data can be obtained, and the virus was released in Black Federation, I’m sure Father will be very pleased to see that spectacular scene.”

“What if the people of Black Federation are still shelling non-stop?”

“Then just kill them first.”

The black-robed man instantly chuckled menacingly.

The three forces were each the primary force, and the Black Federation’s fleet had to stop the bombardment. Vulture No.1 led a few Vulture powerhouses and entered the island from the right side on foot.

Two people from Red Nation’s Prince’s side went onto the island by themselves from the left.

On Black Federation’s side, King Thunderclap personally brought along two big fellows who were wearing silver-like armor and looked like robots and approached the island from the front with heavy treads.

After the three forces took the lead to enter the island, they were quickly followed by several small reconnaissance units in order to quickly grasp the situation on the island.

Yuria mingled in the second wave of the teams entering the island and quickly moved in from the periphery to the inside.

He believed that his strength was good, but it was not the top of the list, so he let the strongest powerhouses of the three forces test the waters first.

Moreover, he could not believe that Zhi Jinqin was the mastermind of the entire deception. There was still a trace of luck in the depths of his heart.

**********************

On the surface of the sea, the sun had just radiated a trace of golden color, shining a vast golden light over the horizon.

A clear white line flew straight into the distance. It was an extremely fast-moving ship, which seemed to be a military ship. There was half a logo on the side that was not completely covered with paint as if it was hurriedly launched before the cover-up procedure had finished.

Garen stood at the bow and looked at the boundless sea.

“How long more until we reach?” He frowned and asked. It was night time when they departed and it was already dawning here.

“An hour more and we should be able to catch up. Don’t worry.” Nine-Tailed Fox was operating the boat. She and Kong Xinxue accompanied Garen to hurry over. Previously, she had coordinated with Yuria to leave one of the fastest ship models for Garen to ensure that he could get on board right away as soon as he flew over so that there would not be any delay at all.

Although Nine-Tailed Fox was operating the ship, her face was very pale, almost colorless. There were still traces of blood in the corners of her eyes. It had just flowed out and was not completely wiped clean.

Blood flowing out of the corners of both eyes was the most prominent feature of those infected by the virus, Yuri’s Kiss.

The room where they were operating the ship was quarantined, and Garen could not enter without violent destruction. This was to prevent Garen from being infected. Although it was only a delay, it was impossible to completely isolate this kind of airborne virus no matter what measures one took. Even the little time that could be dragged counted.

There were also some infected crew members on board, all of whom joined with a resolute determination.

Garen lifted the new mechanical technology sword which was full of fine mechanical gears on its body. It looked like a layer of metal wrapping around the complex parts on the inside. It was very delicate but it gave people an assumption of not being very practical like it could be broken with just a simple strike.

“Is this knife really hard and tough?” Garen asked casually.

Nine-Tailed Fox had no choice but to explain through the pager.

“This is the technology of a place where I have been to. I assure you that the technology is definitely far beyond this era. Using ordinary materials and substance to make the hardness and indicators far beyond that of the material itself was the characteristic of that place. Even if you have the power of Sea God, this sword is enough for you!”

“I hope so,” Garen was uncertain.

*******************

White Crab Island

In the central area, there were only empty buildings on the entire island. Some of them were high towers, some were round research rooms, some were hanging the technology incubators signboards, and some were public leisure facilities. If there were not the various kinds of signboards and titles, this would not look like a biochemical research base at all but more like an unknown style of amusement park.

Yuria followed a small team and found no White Crab soldiers obstructing them.

After encountering several traps, these scattered teams of more than a dozen people managed to pass through without any harm.

“Come in, come in. Unit No. 2 has successfully passed the checkpoint, reaching the predetermined location. Please advise on the next step.” The captain kept speaking into the walkie-talkie.

However, the screen on the walkie-talkie showed that there was no signal. There was clearly some kind of large shielding installation.

“Hell! I can’t hear anything.” The captain was agitated and hammered the walkie-talkies a few times, but it still did not work, and he could only put it away.

“Lord Yuria, what do you think we should do now?” He looked at Yuria, who had the most right to speak. When they departed this time, the Commodore had passed the command power to Yuria alone. In the case of losing the highest level of instruction, everything will be based on his goals.

“Can you find the other reconnaissance units around on the island?” Yuria felt that something was amiss. There were no more than one thousand if not eight hundred people on the island and it was impossible for one not to meet another. After all, the area of this White Crab Island was only wide to a certain extent. Even if there were buildings blocking their line of sight, it could not be that not even a little sound was heard.

“Since we have reached here, there’s no point in retreating,” Yuria spoke directly. “Continue moving forward.”

“Alright.” The captain was also a decisive person. Since he was now at this place, he had also put his own life and death behind his mind.

The group continued to move between the white buildings. Their surroundings were silent, and there was not any sound from other teams, not even a gunshot. It was very bizarre.

They continued for another few kilometers, marching toward the tornado-mountain, and soon there was a very tall white icicle in front. There seemed to be a person frozen inside the icicle.

The group had already felt that something was amiss. The island should not be this huge! The length and width were only a few thousand kilometers. How could it be that they had not arrived at the tornado-mountain after so long?

Chapter 1232: Ending 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Yuria raised his hand to stop the group. Looking at the icicle from afar, he realized that it was only an illusion as the icicle swiftly disappeared.

A very light, white mist gradually began to hover over the entire island, but he felt as if there was something wrong with the fog.

“How come I can’t see anything?” A soldier suddenly said.

“Me too.”

“Captain! Aix!” Someone called out.

Yuria turned back and was about to look at what was going on when he found that the voices behind him suddenly disappeared. It was all empty in the white mist. There was nothing. No unit, no soldiers. It was as if the previous voices were also just an illusion.

“We have convened.” A familiar voice came from in front of him.

“Parakeet!?” Yuria once again saw the Parakeet. She was wearing a white dress and slowly emerged from the white mist.

“This is the Hallucination White Mist. It can confuse the five senses people have and randomly create illusions,” Parakeet said indifferently. “Come on. They have already started to fight. Follow me.”

Yuria watched her turn around and walked towards the depths of the white mist. After hesitating for a moment, he immediately followed closely. Under these circumstances, the soldiers around him had already completely disappeared. They had either gone far away or gotten lost. In the case that the radio could not be used, it would not be a bad thing to follow Parakeet, who had no malicious intent towards him.

He gave a final attempt to wave his hand around and called the names of his teammates, but there was no response. He could only follow Parakeet who was in front of him.

********************

The underground White Crab central stone pillar

In front of a huge silvery-white metal funnel, a petite girl sat quietly on a big white bed. She was staring into the distance and there were no pupils in her eyes as if she was looking at something but at the same time, being in a trans.

“Hahaha!! It seems like I’m the first one here!” King Thunderclap wore a blue metal tight-fitting combat uniform and held a black metal rod in his hand. The top of the rod flashed a blue electric light from time to time.

He walked out of a cave mouth with two assistant adjutants. His sight was locked on the naked petite girl sitting on the big bed. Although there was a white blanket obscuring, one was still able to see that the other party in the wanted posters was Yurijie, who was also Zhi Jinqin.

Rated as the most dangerous among the Four Great Cornerstones, she had the absolute Immortal Body. This had been heard of in the sharing of intelligence, which was also one of the reasons why King Thunderclap was so aggressive. Even though he was not infected, he still quickly rushed over as soon as possible.

Immortal Body! What a wonderful term. The moment he heard it, he decided to make acquiring the Immortal Body his biggest goal of this lifetime!

“Illusionist!” King Thunderclap pressed a button on the right side of his thigh.

Snap! Hiss…

Suddenly, his back opened up and pieces of black metal modules which looked like black bricks started coming out. More and more black cubes surged out from King Thunderclap’s back. These cubes had a metallic luster on their surface, and as they came in contact with the air, they expanded rapidly.

In less than a few seconds, his body was covered with a thick layer of black cubes, which had assembled into a black robot three times larger than his original body. There were densely packed honeycomb-like cannon ports on his chest and shoulders. The vilest thing was that the critical part between King Thunderclap’s legs was actually inlaid with a blue gem. The gemstone was slightly fluorescent, and it seemed to be able to launch a powerful laser beam at any time.

“Hehe! Looks like I get to be the first to seize the opportunity!” King Thunderclap was now more than four meters tall. He took a step out and the ground shook a little. His black metal block-armor swayed like a wave. Rubbing against one another, vast amounts of large blue arcs appeared across the entire body’s surface.

“Go to hell!!” He stomped the ground, and the rocket thrusters which were mounted on his back ejected right away. In the fiery yellow flame, King Thunderclap swung his fist with the blue electric light and slammed it at the little girl on the big bed.

“Every one of these modules can withstand heavy bombardment for at least ten minutes. With so many modules combined, I am now undefeatable!!!” King Thunderclap laughed hysterically, and his fist struck the side of the little girl’s head.

Pooh!

A splatter of blood plasma splashed directly onto the facial part outside his armor.

King Thunderclap’s complexion changed.

The person he struck was not the little girl Zhi Jinqin at all, but instead, it was one of the adjutants behind him!

“Sir…” The adjutant’s eyes widened, his face was full of disbelief and his chest was punched through in the middle. He fell to the ground with a thump.

Not only him, but the other adjutants had also fallen to the ground at this moment. It was unknown whether he was dead or alive. There were obvious traces of electric burns on his body.

“This… This is hallucinogenic!” King Thunderclap’s face darkened. Only then did he realize that he had attacked in the wrong direction. He looked back and saw that Zhi Jinqin who was still behind him and still maintained the original dull and absent-minded look.

“You… This fellow!!!” An incomparable anger surged out from the bottom of his heart. One of the two adjutants was actually his nephew!

“Tsk tsk tsk… King Thunderclap, bungled and killed his own nephew. What rare news.” A handsome pale man came out from the other side. Behind him was a shorty in a black robe whose face could not be seen clearly.

Unlike King Thunderclap and others who arrived here smoothly, these two men were covered in blood. It was apparent that they had gone through many battles before reaching this place.

“Red Nation’s Prince?” King Thunderclap turned his head coldly. “Say another word, and I will kill you!”

“Oh, I’m so scared~~~” Prince mocked and put on an act. “The honorable King Thunderclap, you actually didn’t figure out what an Illusionist’s basic ability is before bringing along two subordinates who didn’t have any resistance. I really don’t know if you are recklessly confident or arrogant.”

Boom!!!

King Thunderclap’s right arm punched into the air, and the hugely distorted airwave hit out a clear sunken fist print on the wall beside Prince’s head.

Large amounts of broken earth and gravel fell, and the entire cave trembled violently as if it was about to collapse.

“How oafish.” The black robed person behind Prince sneered. “Does King Thunderclap think that Illusionist, the most powerful of the Four Great Cornerstones, could be dealt with so easily? Moreover, having the strength to swing your fist at the allies.”

“The most important thing now is to get rid of Illusionist first.” Vulture No. 1 and others walked out of another cave mouth. He held a dark green gem-like device in his hand, and it was constantly emitting a circle of light green glow, protecting more than a dozen people behind him.

Vulture No. 1 was wearing a large trench coat and a military cap. His face was cold and solemn. His strength was actually not comparable to that of Red Nation’s Prince and King Thunderclap. Slann was initially the weakest in the highest individual martial power. After Garen came along, it became the strongest player on par with Black Federation. But now with the Sword Master’s betrayal and departure, Slann had lost its highest martial power and was once again restored to its original weak position.

“Slann’s scumbag.” King Thunderclap’s mouth attracted hatred the moment it was opened.

There was a glint of anger in Vulture No. 1’s eyes, but he still suppressed it to ensure there would not be a dispute between them. However, the rest of the people behind him could not hold it in and opened their mouths to mock and ridicule.

King Thunderclap could not be bothered to reply. He raised his fist and punched to the side, instantly stopping the voices.

With a boom, there was a half-a-meter deep fist print on the ground beside Vulture No. 1 and the group.

More and more people started arriving but the numbers seemed to be much lesser than when they first set out.

Gradually, everyone formed a circle around Zhi Jinqin and the big bed at the center. The danger of bombs and various kinds of traps had been ruled out.

The funnel-shaped silvery-white metal attracted more attention straight away.

Suddenly, the metal surface slowly extended soft silvery-white tentacles at the empty space above the big bed. The tentacles were as if they were not made of metal. They were liquifying and condensing into human lips.

“Welcome to my paradise…” A weird, overlapping voice rang out slowly. It was as though an old man and a youthful girl were talking at the same time.

“Hand over the data, Illusionist. You have no chance,” Vulture No. 1 spoke confidently on the surface, but there was a hint of vigilance in the depths of his eyes, ready to retreat and escape any moment.

“Let’s play a game first…” The voice did not take note of him. This made Vulture No. 1 a little embarrassed. However, at this time, no one noticed his embarrassment.

Everyone’s attention was on Zhi Jinqin, who was on the big bed.

This was the first time anyone saw her move after coming into the cave.

Zhi Jinqin gently lifted her left hand and opened her small white palm.

She opened her mouth and began to say something softly, but there was no sound coming out.

At that moment, the crowd made a depressing swallowing sound.

One could only see Zhi Jinqin’s entire left palm melt like a candle, turning into drops of wax and dripping onto the floor next to the bed. What was uncanny was that each drop of wax gradually expanded and became larger.

“Kill her now!!” Someone shouted. “She must be brewing something! Open fire!”

Bang bang bang bang!!

Some people actually brought heavy autocannons in. Booming sounds were heard as the huge autocannons fired directly at Zhi Jinqin.

But there was no point as the numerous bullets were blocked by a layer of air in front of Zhi Jinqin, and they all fell to the ground.

Whoosh!

A circle of red flame blazed up on the floor around her bed. The flame was half a meter high, and self-ignited without any material.

“The unclean world… The sinful world…” That weird voice sounded again.

Zhin Jinqin was expressionless in the flame but was eerily giving people a kind of feeling that she was happy.

“Attack!!” King Thunderclap roared. Feeling something was not right, he bumped both his fists together and hammered them down fiercely.

Krak!!

Numerous violet-blue currents flowed from the ground to Zhi Jinqin, directly fanning out to cover the entire silvery-white metal funnel.

Red Nation’s Prince carried a scarlet ruined sword, reduced a few steps to a leap, turned over, and struck out his sword!

Clang!

“Annihilation Ring!” The sword in Prince’s hand turned into a red ring, and the surrounding area of the high-speed rotation had a faint black line. No one knew what formed it.

Vulture No. 1 took out a pistol with a large barrel. The muzzle was illuminated with a faint white light, and he solemnly aimed it at Zhi Jinqin.

At this moment, the wax liquid dripping beside Zhi Jinqin quickly grew big and tall to form a slightly black triangle-headed humanoid monster. The monster held a double saber and its body was densely covered with hard metal scales.

Every drop of wax had turned into a monster, and instantly, at least tens of hundreds of monsters darted towards everyone around.

Chapter 1233: Ending 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A large amount of triangle-headed monsters with double sabers lunged at everyone. The sabers in their hands could instantly block the high-speed bullets that were shot at them. Guns were fired and bombs were thrown out as both parties engaged with each other in the huge cave.

From time to time, some monsters and outsiders would be chopped and killed.

King Thunderclap and Red Nation’s Prince rushed towards Zhi Jinqin straight from the left. All the monsters in between were like pieces of paper. They were no match for the two at all and could not last for even one round of fight.

The crowded monsters were like a light gray torrent, madly rushing at everyone. The two lighted up a grand-blue light each and darted at Zhi Jinqin as if going upstream. In the process of sprinting, the two exchanged glances as they leaped into the air.

“Thunderbolt Eye!” The rod which was previously brought out was now in King Thunderclap’s hand. It automatically extended to a sleeve-length spear and a dark blue electrical eye emerged from the spearhead.

“Go!”

He hurled it forward.

Whish!!

The spear drew out a horrific dark blue trail, arousing the surrounding air and creating a vast spider web-like white mist silk thread. It flashed past and hit the position where Zhi Jinqin was at.

Boom!!!

Countless smoke flares exploded with the booming sound, and some of the monsters near Zhi Jinqin were swept off the ground and blown up into pieces.

King Thunderclap panted heavily as he descended. Before he could be at ease, vast red lights suddenly lit up before his eyes.

Whish whish whish!

Several red steel needles shot out from the white mist, which was produced by the explosion of the thunderbolt, and headed straight towards his face.

Ding ding ding!

In the continuous sound of impact, King Thunderclap’s facial armor had several white dots right away.

He was also hit by the huge impact force and was forced to retreat. He abruptly halted his steps and moved his body slightly sideways, avoiding a red arrow that broke out from behind him.

Red Nation’s Prince slowly put away his longbow. He was wearing a red electronic eye mask for aiming which he had put it on who-knows-when. The mask was a half-faced mask, but it looked exquisite and gorgeous, giving people a strange temperament.

The arrow he shot out suddenly exploded in mid-air, transforming into countless red spots and darted towards Zhi Jinqin from all sides in a densely packed formation.

A large number of monsters flew up and desperately blocked these numerous red dots. But even so, there was still one-third of the light spots plummeting down on the big bed where Zhi Jinqin was at.

Pooh, pooh… In the light sound, all the red dots were blocked by a transparent barrier.

Zhi Jinqin lifted her small face and her glassy eyes looked straight at Red Nation’s Prince.

“Huh…” There was a subtle noise from her mouth, which seemed to be a special kind of electric sound and was not human-like at all.

King Thunderclap sneered.

“If you don’t hand over the virus data, you and this place will be wrecked.”

He strode forward and landed a single fist fiercely on the waist of a monster that was blocking the path in front. He stormed forward like a tank and headed straight towards Zhi Jinqin.

Whish!

A red arrow aimed at his hindbrain was shot out from behind.

Boom! King Thunderclap was caught off guard and was hit. The armor at the back of his brain immediately melted and a small piece of it was broken off. His head jerked forward a little.

“Who!?” He turned his head around furiously and saw Red Nation’s Prince with his electronic eye that was flashing a red light getting increasingly closer.

“Are you crazy?!!!”

King Thunderclap and Prince slammed together with a boom, and the dagger and metal arms between the two interlocked, bursting out ear-piercing sounds and innumerable fine golden sparks.

Prince revealed one dull eye, and the attack from his hand was exceptionally fast. There were sharp blades on both sides of the tip of the longbow and invisible circles were drawn out as he madly swung the longbow, slashing at King Thunderclap.

“He’s being controlled!” Someone exclaimed from the rear.

However, King Thunderclap’s position was too deep inside the cave, and no one but he and Prince could go this far.

King Thunderclap was about reply when all of a sudden, he spotted a strange curl on the Prince’s lips. He instantly felt a chill.

“Illusionist’s control can stimulate one’s strongest potential. You deliberately let yourself be controlled to trigger all of your strength!!”

He suddenly understood.

Illusionist’s control was like the highest level of hypnosis, which could maximize the full potential of the human body and make a mediocre person become a genius in a very short time, even though the cost was the exhaustion of one’s life and vitality.

“You are all having an infighting so soon? Tsk tsk…” The voice sounded again.

“Infighting?” Vulture No. 1’s voice spread out. “This is not infighting.” He was carrying a huge and complex shoulder cannon that was more than one meter thick and over four meters long.

The position of the muzzle was aimed directly to where King Thunderclap was at.

“What are you all doing!!?” King Thunderclap slightly panicked. Even if Prince and Vulture No. 1 were the scums he did not care about, it was impossible to not have any qualms even for someone as strong as him when being hemmed in by the two from behind in this kind of environment.

Boom!

What replied him was the action of Vulture No. 1 firing a shot.

“We must kill him as quickly as possible! Otherwise, we will suffer even greater losses!” Vulture No. 1 calmly said.

One side of King Thunderclap’s body was hit by the shot in a flash, and the whole person was shrouded in a golden fireball that was of a person’s height.

Ah!!!!

He screamed desperately in pain and the tearing of his body continuously twisted his will, causing his eyes to suddenly become clear for a moment in the bundled flames.

At that moment, he noticed that the scene in front of him had changed abruptly.

He was not cooperating with Red Nation’s Prince to kill Zhi Jinqin at all, instead, he was rushing into the crowd by himself and massacring the troops who had come to besiege Illusionist!

“What exactly is going on!?”

His mind was chaotic.

The image before his eyes changed one moment and blurred another moment.

**********************

“Black Federation sending King Thunderclap here is just to have him die.”

Vulture No. 1 lowered the shoulder cannon and shook his head slightly.

“King Thunderclap belongs to the type of monster that only focuses on the robustness of the physical body and so it is normal for him to be constrained by Illusionist.” The black-robed person behind Red Nation’s Prince was now standing together with the Vulture.

“He was controlled from the beginning and thought that he was killing the monsters, but in actual fact, he was killing our own people. Since the people of Black Federation hopes that he dies, then what reason do we have to keep him alive?” No. 1 calmly said.

“Most of what he saw and heard should be true. Illusionist actually only did one thing, which was switching the identity of the monsters and the people who were besieging.” The black-robed person shook his head.

No. 1 nodded, and soon after, someone quietly came forward from the cave entrance behind and whispered something to him.

“Almost here?” No. 1 frowned slightly. “Then we better pick up speed. We don’t have much time.”

“What’s almost here?” Asked the black-robed person.

“Our biggest reliance this time.” A hint of confidence rose in Vulture No. 1. “Even if Garen is here, he will still not be as strong as him.”

“Oh?” The black-robed person made a doubtful sound.

“Alright. Prince, this way, please. We have found the real virus database.” No. 1 took a final look at the people who were still fighting the monsters, turned around, and walked toward the exit behind.

The black-robed person was the real Red Nation’s Prince. He faced the other Prince who was still fighting with King Thunderclap in the crowd of monsters and lightly pressed some kind of remote control device in his sleeve.

That ‘Prince’ instantly leaped into the air and flew directly toward him.

“Retreat!! Retreat!!” The people from the Vulture began to convey the order. As for the rest of the forces, mercenaries, and those who had come to snap up some gain, they were discreetly placed to fight at the front line where it was closest to the monsters, while their own people silently withdrew toward the periphery.

“Looks like someone wants to leave early…” The strange voice sounded again.

Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince instantly quickened their pace and swiftly entered the exit.

However, they suddenly found their field of vision changed in an instant. Their direction of running towards the outside had now changed to rushing toward Zhi Jinqin at the center.

“This!!?” The green gem in Vulture No. 1’s hands was covered with cracks. There was no green light at all.

Just then, King Thunderclaps’ fist fiercely slammed into his face and his eyes widened.

Which one was the illusion and which was the real one!!?

************************

“If the real Zhi Jinqin can’t be found, then there’s no need to talk about killing her,” Parakeet spoke softly as she led Yuria forward in the thick mist.

“She is your biological sister. But now, she has almost integrated with your father into one body. They are influencing each other and suppressing each other. Perhaps only you can help her. ”

Yuria followed her and looked at the empty white buildings they passed by on both sides. He seemed to be walking on a spacious street.

“What is your actual purpose?” He returned his gaze to Parakeet.

“That depends on what purpose you actually have.” Parakeet did not turn her head around but replied in a low voice. “Do you want to save your sister, or do you want to save the whole world?”

“What does this have to do with the whole world?” Yuria frowned.

“What does this have to do?” The Parakeet sneered and turned back. “Because your sister wants to wipe out the whole world right now! Tell me, is it not related?”

Yuria was silent.

“Qin is not that kind of person. It must be Father’s will polluting her! We just need to kill and erase Father’s part, then we will definitely save her!”

“Huh…” Parakeet could not help but snicker. “You don’t even know how many people she has killed… Or do you still think that she is still the Zhi Jinqin who held the doll and asked for your help back then? Ridiculous!”

The two kept moving forward and neither of them spoke again.

Yuria’s heart was preoccupied. He did not know how to face this sister of his from decades ago.

Parakeet was just silent and thinking of who-knows-what.

Krakk.

Suddenly, Yuria’s step forward produced a clear crack on the ground in front. The hard surface of the rock actually cracked under his effortless step.

Yuria was slightly stunned and did not expect to encounter such a circumstance.

Parakeet turned back abruptly and looked at him with a weird gaze.

“Your strength has increased again…”

Yuria was shocked. He quickly waved his hand against the space on the right side and his palm made a knife-hand strike.

Whish!

A clear and transparent distorted wave shot out and hit something in the mist with a bong creating a chain reaction of countless sounds of metal colliding.

“This!”

Yuria was stupefied. His original physical strength was far less powerful than this.

“How much has it increased?” Parakeet asked quietly.

“… At least six times,” Yuria was silent for a moment before replying in a low voice.

“The advancement of your strength and Zhi Jinqin’s are enjoyed together, which means that someone very powerful has died.” Parakeet suddenly smiled. “And it’s more than one. Their power has been apportioned to both of you.”

Yuria gritted his teeth. He had confirmed the source of the increment of his strength from Parakeet and others, and so there was no longer any hesitation in him.

“Must find Qin as soon as possible!”

He said decisively.

“After finding her?” Parakeet asked in reply.

Yuria trembled and did not answer right away.

Chapter 1234: Ending 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Snapped.

Garen’s feet landed lightly on the sand of an island.

“Wrong. This is not White Crab Island.” He frowned.

Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue’s expression was unsightly as they followed behind him. They had also gotten off the ship and were looking around.

“We were misled!” Nine-Tailed Fox’s face turned blue as she spoke. She took out a positioning device and had a look. The words of White Crab Island were clearly displayed.

“It’s the same with my device.” Kong Xinxue also inspected her device on one side.

“Looks like some people don’t want me to arrive at White Crab Island in advance…” Garen remarked. “Is there still a way to position the coordinates?”

“All electronic devices look the same. They are either being interfered or the other party has directly tampered with a large number of the satellites, causing everyone to be unable to locate it. My communication device is not working as well. Clearly, there are Transmigrators on the inside causing trouble too.” Nine-Tailed Fox looked at Kong Xinxue. “Ah Xue, it’s up to you now.”

Kong Xinxue nodded. She turned over her hand and took out a small calculator, not the ordinary small calculator but a real multi-function complex calculator. She then took out a nautical chart.

“Looks like we can only use the most primitive positioning method.”

She looked up and began to study the sky. Just a few moments later.

Whoosh!

Kong Xinxue picked up the calculator and unfolded the nautical chart simultaneously, her fingers quickly moving across the keys with lightning speed. Her fingers on the calculator were not performing continuous calculations at all, but it was more like she was using the calculator to assist her own algorithm.

Garen frowned. As he felt her body temperature rising rapidly and her heartbeat speeding immensely, he understood Kong Xinxue’s calculation.

She was forming a circle through a large number of multi-sites global positioning, surrounding the location of White Crab Island and positioning the location of this island at the same time. She was using the astronomical phenomenon, magnetic field and some well-known island locations to calculate the relative position. However, since the specific coordinates of White Crab Island were wrong, what algorithm could she used to calculate?

Garen could not figure it out.

However, after a few minutes, White Crab Island was instantly marked by Kong Xinxue at a certain point on the nautical chart.

“It’s here. The error will not exceed fifty nautical miles.”

“Let’s go.” Nine-Tailed Fox did not say anything else and turned around to board the ship.

Garen followed closely behind.

At the last moment right before going on board, Garen turned around and looked at this island.

“Looks like I have to give some people a lesson.”

He smiled slightly, raised his right hand, and a cloud of white mist slowly gathered around his palm. That was the air vapor atomizing naturally due to the high-speed vibration of his hand.

Whoosh!!

He struck out his palm.

The Palm Cut was incomparably sharp, and it exploded in the air directly, splattering a glaring gold light.

There was no loud noise and the golden light was only the size of a fist. His back was facing the others on the boat so no one realized it.

The golden light went out, and nothing happened.

The palm was drawn back as if nothing had happened. Garen turned around and followed Nine-Tailed Fox onto the ship again. The ship was steered into the distance and was speeding up. Soon, the ship disappeared on the horizon.

Hum…

Just then, the small island, which was hundreds of meters wide, vibrated violently.

Krakk!!

A straight fissure appeared in the center of the island, like a cake being cut into two halves right at the center with a knife.

A huge amount of sea water rushed into the fissure, and the whole island was actually divided into two!!

On the other side of the island, a black submarine floated to the water surface. The knife mark separating the island directly spread to the submarine, and a clear crack appeared in the center of the entire submarine. The crack was getting brighter and brighter, and there was a faint yellow glow coming out of it.

Boom!!

Suddenly, the entire submarine exploded, and tons of flames and smoke skyrocketed. Splashing several meters high, some machine parts and the like fell into the sea again with a burning flame.

Behind the submarine, another small boat fled away into the distance, fleeing for their lives. Panicked faces could be seen on the boat from afar.

*******************

The blood wound along the ground of the cave, creating a river of blood in the entire cave which had had all its exit sealed off.

King Thunderclap laid on the ground and it was unknown whether he was dead or alive. Red Nation’s Prince manipulated the handsome fake prince to madly kill the numerous oncoming monsters.

Vulture No. 1’s hands were covered in blood, and most of the subordinates behind him were already dead.

As for the rest of the people who came in, only a dozen or so powerhouses were still left and barely holding out.

They had tried countless methods but no matter how they attacked, they could not penetrate the barrier in front of Zhi Jinqin. That transparent barrier was like the strongest defense in the world and no one could break it.

“The first game is over.” The strange voice sounded again.

All the monsters retreated. A majority of them were dead, and there were only about ten of them left. If the combat were to continue, they would all be wiped out.

It was apparent that Zhi Jinqin’s hand had melted earlier on, but now it had grown back and was intact.

“Alright?” Vulture No. 1 went to the Prince.

“Still alright. Looks like this Illusionist is very troublesome. Why not we move in together since the data has been obtained?” Prince was also a little fatigued, which caused his voice to sound low.

“If that doesn’t work?” Vulture No. 1 frowned.

“If that fails, we’ll retreat together and demolish this place another time!” Prince sneered.

“Then let’s do it. Try one last time. If can’t, we’ll retreat!” Vulture No. 1 had also made up his mind.

The two each took out a green jade-like crescent and pieced them together. The two crescents fitted together perfectly.

A number gradually emerged on the joint crescent. It was 3.

The air around the crescent suddenly puffed up and was filled with a cloud of mist. The mist condensed into water, and the water then turned into ice. Pieces of ice crystals gradually appeared around the crescent.

A large number of ice crystals gradually covered the ground around the crescent, and pieces of white crystals were formed.

In the corner where everyone was not paying attention to, the crescent quickly grew from the size of a fist into an ice-crystal humanoid with the height of a person in only a few dozen seconds.

“Self-propelled Ice Fission Bomb.” Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince quickly retreated. The power of this ice-crystal humanoid was like the general nuclear bomb. Even though its range was far from a nuclear bomb, its power was awfully horrifying. The ice crystal on the outer layer was just to provide it with the ability to move about by itself as well as to lower the temperature to prevent an explosion. Once the ice crystal was removed…

This was beyond half the scope of technology and was closer to myth.

At this time, Zhi Jinqin abruptly stood up from the bed.

Her naked body which was originally covered by a blanket, now exposed part of her lower legs. However, what was unexpected was that the lower half of her body was not human legs at all!

Instead, they were innumerable densely packed grayish black octopus-like tentacles, and there was mucus and white liquid between the tentacles.

Zhi Jinqin suddenly bellowed and her skin arched from the inside as if she was an inflatable doll. Her skin suddenly puffed up and became swollen. From a petite body of less than one point six meters, she actually expanded to more than two meters.

Her white skin turned grayish black and her head transformed into a triangular shape as if the head was pressing against a hard triangular disk.

White bone spurs extended from both her shoulders and the most disgusting part was that there was a big mouth opening and closing non-stop at her abdomen. The mouth was filled with lots of blisters in it. Some of them were punctured and stinky thick yellow pus was flowing out of it, while some were like densely packed yellow grapes.

“Huh…” Zhi Jinqin roared loudly as if wanting to make a sound but there were no specific decent words.

“This is the second form!! Not good!” Vulture No. 1 seemed to know quite a lot. He promptly turned about and threw himself onto the ground. Layers of metal armor automatically covered his back.

Red Nation’s Prince was also not slow in reacting. He fell prostrate on the floor, his face complexion changing slightly and an anti-virus mask automatically extended from his mouth. He had prepared well for this battle.

Pooh pooh pooh!!

In an instant, a large amount of yellow pus was directly spewed out from the big mouth at Zhi Jinqin’s abdomen and the foul-smelling liquid filled the entire space and fell like raindrops on everyone present.

Some people did not respond in time and the pus directly hit their bodies. Those body parts soon began to rot and maturate, and the whole body also began to grow a vast amount of blisters. It was exceptionally disgusting.

The crowd was screaming. Firearms were wildly sweeping across, killing a few of those who were caught off guard and not defending.

As each person was killed, the size of the monster that Zhi Jinqin transformed into expanded a little.

Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince blocked the blister droplets and flew directly to the exit, using their whole body’s strength to slam against it.

Whish whish. A gap was created in the high-strength metal door at the sealed off the exit. The two were about to charge through it when all of a sudden, their waist was firmly entangled by a large grayish black tentacle.

The strength of the tentacle was so astounding that the armor at the waist of the two men were crushed and became out of shape.

“No!!!” Vulture No. 1 screamed in pain.

Red Nation’s Prince used some kind of technique to chop off the tentacle at the waist and continued to rush out

Boom!!!

Just then, a glaring white light exploded from the inside of the cave. The ice-man that the crescent had turned into had finally closed in and detonated.

Similarly, in that instance, the white light was immediately frozen by some inexplicable force, and everything was still.

The falling human body, exploding bombs, flying bullets, even the blood river that was flowing, and the stones that had fallen half-way and was suspended in the air.

It was as if time stood still. That inexplicable power seemed to have felt a threat and stopped the white light instantly.

The huge monster that Zhi Jinqin had transformed into had risen to over four meters tall.

A red glow was spinning in the abdomen and a beautiful fair-skinned little girl in a red dress was hovering in it.

“Brother…” The little girl opened her eyes and looked delightfully at the person coming out of an opening of the cave mouth.

Chapter 1235: Wind Up 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“What time is it?”

“My Lord, it is nine o’clock in the morning,” a medic in the hospital carefully answered.

Vulture No. 2 stood in thought in the hospital’s main conference room. She lowered her head to looked at the mobile phone in his hand. She was still holding on to a walking stick but her thoughts were somewhere on White Crab Island.

“Based on the rough estimate of our data, the entire East side of Slann has been infected by over two million people. It’s still unknown on the range it has spread out but we are trying our best to transfer everyone into quarantine.”

The Sanitary Minister sitting beside him drew large breaths on his cigarette. He was pale white as he hadn’t slept all night. A man who was only sixty-five years old had a face full of wrinkles and was overwhelmed with fatigue. He looked like he was over eighty.

“And all that could head up are dispatched?” No. 2 asked in low voice.

“What more can we do?

“We have done whatever we should.”

“You and I have done whatever possible all night and we have just received news that the Presidential House has obtained knowledge of the situation at Black Federation and Red Nation.”

“They’re worst off than us!”

The Sanitary Minister coldly blurted, “At least thirty million people infected over there in one night, thirty million!!” The mention of this number had his face more and more upset.

Both his hands grabbed into his hair as he coarsely ran through them, lowering his head.

“What has the world come to!?”

“Yes, what’s wrong with this world? How did it become like this?” A streak of sadness flashed past No. 2’s eyes.

“It would be better to follow them to White Crab Island. It’s better than not knowing anything!” The Sanitary Minister shouted out.

“This is a world war. We can only wait now,” No. 2 shook her head and said. A old granny like her has lived most her life and was only a step away from her grave so dying was no big deal. However, her children, grandchildren and the fate of Slann were just unfolding. It couldn’t just come to an end because of this.

However, there was nothing they could do besides wait.

******

In a cave.

Countless people, countless objects, rocks, and blood froze as if time has stopped.

Only Zhi Jinqin quietly hung over the monster’s abdomens in the center. She looked on with glee as Yuria slowly walked in.

“Brother… You’re finally here?” Zhi Jinqin complicatedly gazed at her brother who she hadn’t seen in decades, or maybe she should say, a family member that she had accompanied for decades. She had made so many sacrifices for this only family member.

Yuria bore no expression as he scanned the surroundings. People who died, dismembered bodies, blood spilling like a river, nothing was out of his expectation.

That moment decades ago was the same as present.

There was no sadness in Yuria’s eyes, only peacefulness.

“Brother…” Zhi Jinqin gave a gentle smile, “come with me and create a new world that only belongs to us…” She slowly raised her arms and extended towards Yuria.

“Decades ago, we failed but this time, I will not…”

“Qin.” Yuria quietly cut her off. “Decades ago, we had already missed it once.”

Zhi Jinqin was dumbfounded.

“No.” She put down her arm. “We are not wrong. What’s wrong is this world.”

“So you plan to destroy the entire world?” Yuria could not comprehend.

“We are creating.” Zhi Jinqin argued. “Brother, isn’t having both of us together forever great?” She looked at Yuria with naiveness.

“A world that only has the both of us… Isn’t that, what you and I always wished for?”

“But the others are innocent!!” Yuria shouted.

“Innocent?” Zhi Jinqin lowered her head. “There are too many innocent people, I can’t handle them all… Brother, why can’t you understand where I’m coming from?”

Yuria was silent for a moment before lifting his foot and walking towards Qin.

Crackle…

A spider-web like space rift immediately cracked open beneath his foot.

Clatter!!

The still space broke and crushed into pieces. Large amounts of transparent glass projected and scattered everywhere. Yuria was stunned as he stood where he was, watching Zhi Jinqin slowly fade and diminish before him.

“Qin!!!”

He extended his arm out in an attempt to grab his sister but felt the world spinning.

“Brother, father said that this way, I will be all better… But why do I feel pain…”

Zhi Jinqin laid weakly on a white hospital bed. One of her eyes had been removed.

“What did he do!!?” A young Yuria looked at his sister in disbelief. One of her eyes was…!

“I’m going to look for him!!” He turned to run out as if he lost his mind but was grabbed by Qin on the wrist.

Her strength was extremely weak but Yuria couldn’t bring himself to shake it off.

“Brother… If there’s one day where there’s a world with just two of us, will you be happy?” Zhi Jinqin whispered.

“I…” Yuria suddenly awoke and saw Parakeet sitting beside him. She looked at him with worry. In front of him was a bonfire.

He sat up. His body was drenched with cold sweat.

“I…” He opened his mouth but did not know how to answer that question. He wiped his face with his hand. He felt chills all over.

“Did you see her?” Parakeet asked with a low voice.

“I… Don’t know.”

“It’s a dream. Her powers are getting stronger and have started to radiate the entire island,” Parakeet said in a deep voice. “We must hurry.”

She stood up and threw a water bag towards Yuria, “It all depends on you, whether you choose her or this world…”

Yuria sat by the bonfire without saying a word.

******

In a cave.

Those who could stand up were sparse. Only Prince and No. 1, as well as a handful were left. Such a large amount of blood and flesh piled on the ground to the point where the actual rock surface couldn’t be seen any longer.

Those who entered had all died.

No. 1 and Prince sustained wounds all over. Their waists were severely injured and a few areas were obviously festered and infected. They were fatigued and did not know how long more they could hold on.

Their gaze at Zhi Jinqin were complete with fear, anxiousness, and insecurity.

So many had given their lives yet Zhi Jinqin did not suffer a scratch.

If it weren’t for Prince chopping off a section of Zhi Jinqin’s tentacle that she retrieved back, everyone on site would have probably died.

“Where’s the Ultra Channel Saber?” Prince whispered as he looked at Vulture No. 1.

“Here.” No. 1 took it out with a bitter smile and handed it over. This thing was his biggest trump card for his trip, but it was no longer now. It was now Prince’s only chance to hurt Zhi Jinqin. All hope was on him.

Thinking about this, he swept a glance around the cave blankly. All he saw were corpses, flesh, blood and festered gunk. Stink and smoke engulfed the entire cave.

He had predicted extremity of this encirclement, so he brought along a few secret weapons but he didn’t think they would be at such a losing end.

At this point, he didn’t even know if he would make it out alive.

“What’s the situation?” He was staring at Zhi Jinqin who was instantly frozen by the earlier white blast and was swiftly defrosting her way out while looking at the only seemingly wise Red Nation’s Prince. They had met before and have been in contact.

“Looks okay. It’s still good for one more usage.” There were two scars on Prince’s face. Blood was seeping through his ferocious yet handsome face, delivering an aura of gloominess.

Both their teams shrunk themselves into a corner in the cave and stared at Zhi Jinqin in the middle trying to break free from the binds of the earlier blast. All of them had long ceased fire as no bullets nor bomb prove effective on Zhi Jinqin. If it weren’t for Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince keeping their cool from the beginning and instructing appropriately as their only way out, the last few on the teams would have been overwhelmed by fear.

“This time I really brought out the two weapons of mass destruction in the country. Whether it works or not, we will find out here and now!” Prince was intrepid and ambitious. He had placed all bets on this as he declared viciously with a pale face.

“Zhi Jinqin has a parent virus crystalizing rapidly in her hand.

“Her intentions are clear.”

“The density of the parent is high but it will not be airborne.”

“It fares high on waterborne,” Vulture No. 1 coldly spoke.

“She wishes to contaminate the entire ocean!!”

“This maniac!!” Prince couldn’t help but gasp. It wasn’t just her, the remaining few subordinates’ faces darkened even in a state of extreme fatigue and carrying severe wounds.

If polluting the entire ocean was successful, then no matter how they fought, there would only be one ending. That would be to be infected and perish.

“The plan to extinct humans was the intel the spy I placed in White Crab obtained,” Vulture No. 1 said in a low voice. Even for someone as deep as him, he couldn’t help but gaspwhen he heard the news. Those from White Crab weren’t loyal soldiers who would willingly forgo tranquil days and destroy the world with Zhi Jinqin? It wasn’t their style to do such a silly thing so once the people from the research center had an inkling, they spread the news and naturally, all soldiers of White Crab fled. Two or three countries’ allied forces turned up with full force, nipping what was left of Zhi Jinqin in White Crab Island headquarters.

It was also why there was no one defending at White Crab Island headquarters. No one was willing to die with Zhi Jinqin.

“You and I understand and at this stage, if she doesn’t go down, we all be going down.

“There’s no point escaping to the ends of the earth today.

“It’s just death at the end of the day, we just have to give our all.” Red Nation’s Prince gritted the words out of his teeth.

“If this does nothing to her, then what else can we do?

“Blast her one more time and what if it doesn’t work?” Vulture No. 1 asked in a low voice.

“We have done what we can.”

“Being pushed here, we all know that we’re just being used as a human shield,” Prince didn’t bother to cover up his face of sarcasm.

“Those impure bloodlines hiding outside the quarantine area being onlookers while we fight for our lives here, we have gone above and beyond!”

Chapter 1236: Wind Up 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As they were both in conversation, the dagger in Prince’s palm appeared to have a silvery-white square glow. It seemed to be some sort of jewel emitting a gentle yet blinding shimmer.

As for Zhi Jinqin, the earlier self-denoting ice person had caused the majority of the cave to be frozen. A peculiar transparent radiation had suppressed the movement of the monster Zhi Jinqin became.

However, this wouldn’t last very long.

The ice surface on Zhi Jinqin was cracking and melting with lightning speed and her body was once again expanding.

“Last bet!” Prince’s eyes redeemed as he saw the development of Zhi Jinqin, it could not be delayed any longer. Once Illusionist’s powers were activated and broken free from the boundaries of the earlier blast, only death would await this limited group of manpower!

The lines of whatever international citizen were blurred and the fear brought upon by Zhi Jinqin’s disease had forced them to the edge!

“Go!!” Prince let out a roar and charged from the right whereas Vulture No. 1 dashed from the left.

Illusionist’s abilities encompassed the illusion field, making them lose their sense of direction as well as their ability to break free from it.

At the stage they were at, the only thing they could do was give all they had.

As Vulture No. 1 sprinted, he gently pressed on a little button in his hand.

******

Periphery of White Crab Island.

The ocean was rocking hard wave after wave. A large group of warship could not contact those within. The acting commander’s heart was in his mouth. Although many elite experts went in so there wouldn’t be much of a situation, a lingering feeling of oppression hung over him.

A few of those who knew the inside story remained in their respective cabin and dared not come out. They were afraid the officers and soldiers could get an inkling and affect their spirits.

The sun was rising from sea level like a brilliant golden wheel, radiating the entire sea territory, warship and helicopters into a soft golden glow.

Rumble…

Suddenly from beneath the ocean, deep on the seabed, a large dark figure slowly emerged.

The warships floating nearby started to roll badly as if a massive object was shaking the ocean surface.

However, everyone had received information and instruction before to leave out a vast empty spot of the sea. Nobody knew why such a big piece of the ocean was left out for. There were even people complaining about how such a large territory could accommodate quite a number of warship but now seeing this, all the soldiers and officers held their breaths. The surge of the wave was so high, almost the coverage of half the White Crab Island that if it were to emerge out of the surface, it would be a sight.

Howl…

They hadn’t let go of their breath when suddenly, a deep bugle-like howl of a giant beast was heard coming from beneath the water surface.

The howling was endless with inexhaustible energy.

“They pressed the final key I gave them.” Beneath the ocean, a large voice echoed. It was of a human but a whale wailing-like sound.

“Lord Sea God…” On the largest few ships, transmigrators from various places communicated through a contact device as they solemnly stared at the large black figure emerging from the sea.

“Sword Master Garen has not arrived?” Sea God asked in a low voice.

“No, he should be on his way.”

“No, I suspect that we’re locked in by Illusionist so all satellite communications are down.

“She must have used some tactic to isolate us here,” one of the transmigrators spoke with an upset tone. They only came over to lend a hand because they were infected as when transmigrators die, they could still continue to reincarnate so their fear towards death wasn’t as strong as the locals. For a moment, they appeared in vigorous high spirits. However, no matter Sea God or the rest who knew what was going on did not let them know that Illusionist Zhi Jinqin was at a level of affecting Soul Ring and Souls just like Slayer, perhaps even stronger. Once they were killed, it wasn’t as simple as reincarnating. The possibility of reincarnation would perhaps be stripped away.

“I suspect that she may have long known the existence of us transmigrators,” Sea God said in a deep voice. His voice was so loud that no matter what tone he used, everyone’s ear would rumble.

“No matter her plans, as long as Lord Sea God is around, any resistance is futile.” A transmigrator had witnessed the strength of Sea God and was confident.

“Do we need to wait for Sword Master?” A transmigrator asked. “This is a crucial battle involving the entire fate of the planet.”

“No matter how strong Sword Master is, he’s still only one person.

“Even if he settled Slayer, he can’t be of much more help than Lord Sea God at a battle of this large of a scale,” one of them rebutted.

“We’re not waiting.” Sea God made a decision. “Pressing the button would mean that they are at the last critical moment in there. They wouldn’t press the button if they hadn’t exhausted all resources.”

He paused, “Prepare to cooperate attack.”

“Understood!””Yes!” The group of transmigrator couldn’t answer in unison. It was obvious they weren’t organized.

Sea God’s large black figure slowly surfaced from the sea. From afar, it was a speck of its back yet almost the size of a large warship. It was terrifying.

Before the other soldiers on the warship could react, Sea God swam to the back and gently flicked his tail.

Pulling such a distance, it made a flip and its massive black tail violently swayed. Its large body of an island rammed onto White Crab Island with accelerating speed as though it was a collision of two planets.

Was it trying to destroy the entire White Crab Island!!?

Yet at this very moment, a wave of Soul Power ripple that couldn’t be seen by the naked eye was spreading out from the center of White Crab Island and swept past the surrounding warships, dodging transmigrators and even massive Sea God who was ramming at full speed.

******

“What is it? Another resonance in dreamland?” Parakeet held onto Yuria’s shoulder with worry and gave a few shakes but Yuria’s eyes were rolled back and showed no signs of response.

Yuria had earlier inactively resonated in a dream, went deep into a cave and saw Zhi Jinqin. Could it be the same situation as before?!

Parakeet had actually taken Yuria on a detour. It wasn’t foggy and it was a small island, yet they had been traveling for a long time but hadn’t reached the core. The only possibility was that she was leading Yuria in circles.

Yuria was the only one that could turn the tables while the rest could be used to exhaust Zhi Jinqin.

That was her plan but she didn’t think that the dream resonance could bring to this uncontrollable phenomenon.

Kaboom!!

Something was going on on the island as it started to tremor. It was as if they weren’t standing on an island but rather a floating plank that could flip over any time.

Parakeet had undergone years of training after all and could naturally find balance with one hand supporting Yuria, but was pushed away out of the blue.

“You’re awake!?” Just as she was at a loss, Yuria’s pale-white face came to sight.

“I must hurry! Or else it will be too late!!” Yuria shouted and dashed out, disappearing in the thick mist without Parakeet leading the way.

******

“There’s still thirteen minutes to go,” Nine-Tailed Fox reported to Garen in a low voice on the surface of the sea.

“And then we’ll reach White Crab Island. No mistakes this time!”

Garen nodded and did not say more. Up to this stage, he didn’t care about the livelihood of this planet but to a minority as well as the path to Lighthouse sealed, he bore a different attitude. Lighthouse was the only place he could keep his body and ability while reincarnating. He was now at the peak of a Low-Level Demon Class. He had four Soul Rings and close to twenty Soul Seeds. He was no longer the regular void hunter exploited by body-snatching Black Sethe.

Even when placed within Endor, he was a strong force to be reckoned with.

Demon-Class was not that easy to achieve. Not one didn’t have a bloody past. Even a top Legion Class, Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia managed from countless killing spree.

His thoughts lingered off elsewhere.

Garen retrieved his line of gaze.

“Sea God must have arrived. Perhaps there’s no chance for my grand entrance,” he joked.

Nine-Tailed Fox was smiling at the side. She was at ease. Sea God was the representative of this planet’s strongest that even nuclear bombs posed no threat. Such a terrifying tactical expert couldn’t be defeated by a single entity.

All transmigrators never doubted Sea God would fail. At most, it would be how it succeeded.

“After this battle, I really am sick of it. I plan to retire to a librarian position at the Lighthouse.” Kong Xinxue seemed burnt out. “What’s the point of reincarnating when all our traces will be wiped away anyway?”

“Are we in the same boat as these locals?

“The only difference is living a single lifetime and several lifetimes.”

“It’s just that our opportunities and our world are larger and more vast than theirs.” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded.

“Sounds good. I will accompany you too. The knowledge of various energy system recorded at Lighthouse’s library is bountiful. Even if they’re at the beginner level, we can still prolong our lives regardless of how dumb we are. Living up to a hundred is no problem.”

“Don’t worry, after this battle. The chance of encountering such is rare.” Garen comforted them.

“You should worry about yourself first,” Nine-Tailed Fox rolled her eyes at him.

“Don’t get used to the free time now, you’ll be occupied once you’re at Lighthouse.”

“You’re basically the first fierce expert in all of Mother Stream that could fight against an ancient Demon Class.”

“Killing Slayer proved your strength.”

“The forces of us transmigrators are still weak and would need to rely on you for many things.”

“Of course, we’ll count you in on all intel for various worlds.”

“A place like Lighthouse, as long as you’re strong enough, it’d be heaven…” She softly sighed.

“How many Demon Class experts like me are in Lighthouse?” Garen casually asked. Although he could find such a thing on forums, he was simply too lazy to visit the forums. It was more convenient to ask an alive person in front of him. He could verify these things then anyway.

“Not more than six.” Nine-Tailed Fox shook her head.

“The strongest is Magic Lamp Alzara. He was sealed in a magic lamp of the universal civilization for over six thousand years due to a racial war. Now that he’s out, he is still partially impacted by the magic lamp.”

Chapter 1237: Wind Up 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A white ray of light burst to full bloom above White Crab Island.

It was a white light that not everybody could see. It was a huge ripple triggered by the Soul Energy Force.

With White Crab Island as the median point and at a range of tens nautical miles was a hazy view as if a white mist had spread out.

Snap!!

In the vast clear skies, a lightning struck by.

Sea God crashed its head onto White Crab Island. However, its massive collision force was stopped by an unsighted resistance several hundred meters from the island.

The large force counteracted against a boundless barrier before Sea God. They were in a standstill.

“How??!!”

Sea God roared violently. Its giant black tail was wagging so ferociously that it swept up ripples of waves towards both sides behind it.

Many of the warships were rocking from the man-made tidal waves. They rushed to distance themselves.

“Idiot.” Right in the center of White Crab Island, the white mist evaporated, revealing a piece of vast white open space. The surface of the open space cracked open into a pitch dark hole and a voice was heard coming from it.

A giant monster almost ten meters tall slowly erected from the hole.

The monster was brown all over as though it was wearing a leather dress but with closer inspection, it was actually naked and its body naturally grew brown flesh. Its head was triangular in shape as if it was wearing a hat and bore three eyes but no mouth. Its trap was on its abdomens and blisters densely formed above and below the cavity. Yellow pus was oozing out of the blisters.

“Why do you want to protect this filthy world?” The monster flew up and looked at Sea God at a stalemate with the barrier.

“Filthy?” Sea God retreated back. “In the eyes of the filthy, there is only filth in the world. In the eyes of the kind, they will see the world as kind. The problem is yourself.”

It took one swirl with its tail.

“Fossil Sand!”

At the sound of its voice, Sea God’s muscles began to expand rapidly. Lines of a Red Cross stretched out from his back to the front of its head.

Sea God’s already massive body expanded to at least twice its original size.

Large amounts of seawater were pushed away from both sides. Just the movement of its body caused the surge of a huge wave.

Boom!!!

Sea God violently, crazily charged at the barrier. It opened its mouth wide, chomping at the barrier with its razor-sharp teeth.

With a rustle, the barrier could not withstand such strong force and broke. Sea God’s massive figure took flight and was smacking down onto White Crab island. Its large body was almost as large as White Crab Island, forming a black shade blocking the sunlight and descending from the sky.

The triangular-headed monster lifted its head. Compared to Sea God’s massive body, it was as tiny as a sesame seed.

“The world is born again from destruction.” It vaulted up and both arms projected sharp stakes. It began to twirl with a high velocity, forming a spinning grey shadow in midair.

Swish!

It suddenly paused before raising the sharp stakes with its arms and charging at the large black figure in the sky.

Very minimal sound could be heard.

The monster soared to the sky and the moment it was about to collide with Sea God, no noise was made or could be heard. All the sounds were covered up by the roaring of the waves and Sea God.

Slosh!

A round of black ripples burst open between heaven and earth, oscillating around in a frenzy. Everything the ripples touched became a black and white world.

Anywhere the black light swept past would turn dim. The black ball of light extended in range of several thousand meters, wrapping all the warships around before shrinking.

Everything resumed to its peacefulness.

“Hahahaha!!!”

A roar of laughter rung Sea God and the monster met.

Boom boom boom!!

The warships around started to fire cannons. They were all aimed at White Crab Island at both the monster and Sea God but it could be seen that a majority of the cannons were directed towards Sea God and not the monster, which was rather strange.

Shells after shells exploded on Sea God’s back, bursting into red flames and blazing black smoke.

The transmigrators on board who were wearing items that could prevent manipulation of heart and mind instantly exploded. Apart from a minority of transmigrators and experts with strong Willpower, the remaining soldiers and officers on the ships were all controlled and treated Sea God as their biggest enemy and therefore, opened fire.

Rounds of cannons were fired nonstop. The soldiers numbingly closed their eyes to execute the firing the same as they would with their eyes opened.

Clang!!

A white line far from where the sea and sky met shot over.

An old man with white hair and a beard held a silvery-white long sword and crossed the ocean from afar. The sea water beneath his feet was a shallow stream as it never went past his ankles.

His blade drew a white line as it stabbed at the monster beneath Sea God.

Swoosh!

A white imprint made its mark on the monster.

Not wasting a breath, the old man moved at lightning speed. Striding a few thousand meters with just a few steps and crashed into the monster like an arrow. Both parties were in close combat.

Sea God hung in the air and opened its mouth to take a bite down.

Kaboom!!

Breaking noises were heard as the boundless barrier keeping it out broke once again. Sea God’s massive body came crashing down with no resistance.

A cloud of dirt and fog towered to the sky. Dirt, trees, broken rocks as well as pieces of buildings, everything under Sea God was crushed to nothingness.

Bang!

The warships around on the ocean started to blow up in flames. The scarlet red flames rocketed. The remaining warships were caught in the fire after the first report of cannon ignition.

No one was bothered by the flames of the explosions. Even though there was a fire, the soldiers that were controlled by illusions still operated the cannons at Sea God with their eyes closed.

A few of the transmigrators jumped ship but most of them took off with the warship’s escape bot.

The battle situation here was beyond anyone’s expectation.

It was only one White Crab Island, yet, it was hard to infiltrate a White Crab headquarter. Not only did the people that entered lost their lives, those on the outside were somehow controlled and firing cannons at their own people.

Amidst the raging waves, a few figures were tossed high and far. It was chaos on White Crab Island. Broken pieces of unknown substances scattered around.

Dirt and seawater splattered so high above that it wasn’t clear what they actually contained.

Yuria had two people pressed under his arm as he rode a wave out of the water surface and climbed up a warship.

Cough cough!

He coughed with intensity, spurting sea water as he bent down.

“It’s been tough for you.” Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince whom he rescued were at the verge of death but maintained their consciousness.

The warships rocked violently and pushed far in the ocean by the waves.

Roar!!

Sea God’s enormous howl echoed large ripples on the ocean.

Yuria carried himself emotionless as he leaped into the waters and fished up a figure. It was Parakeet who was with him.

Whizz…

A fighter plane descended from the sky and two missiles were launched, tailing a white smoke as he shot to the core of White Crab Island, detonating at the monster below Sea God.

Yuria lifted his head to look at the fighter plane.

“There are still people that are conscious,” he muttered.

He then shifted his head to where the battle was most intense. Waves of tens of meters whirled and stirred everything outwards. Nothing could be seen standing on such a warship.

Yuria saw this horrifying end-of-the-world scene.

“The parent virus is in Zhi Jinqin, which is your sister’s hands.” Red Nation’s Prince smiled coldly. “What do you plan to do?” He wasn’t kind to Yuria who just rescued him.

“You just came like this? No backup plans?” Yuria’s voice clearly traveled to their ears despite the waves.

“Sea God was our biggest trump card, we thought it could be done with ease but now it seems…” Vulture No. 1 frowned and looked around. Waves were whirling to the point where the ships could not be sighted. It was unknown how many ships had sunk or remained from that pounding surf.

“Our final plan is if we come up empty or are left fruitless attack in half an hour, the outside world will use the final strategy nuclear weapon to destroy everything here,” Vulture No. 1 continued, answering Yuria’s question.

“It’s useless.” Red Nation’s Prince calmed down. All the bones in his body were broken. He lost his arms and his legs were twisted beyond recognition. The wounds on his body were soaked to paleness in sea water.

“Strategic arms with GPS would still be affected by Zhi Jinqin.”

“Then what do we do now?” Vulture No. 1 asked. “What about the world?”

Yuria was silent for a moment. Standing on a heavily rocking ship, the three were lost for words. They had given it their all up to this point yet they reached the limit of their resources. Whatever that could be used had been used.

“I’ll go.” Yuria was expressionless as he turned and leaped into the waters without waiting for the two to respond.

“Is it right to force a young man like this?” Red Nation’s Prince smirked at Vulture No. 1.

“Force?” No. 1’s face was cold as ice. “No one forced him. Everything is predestined.”

“How??!!”

Suddenly, Sea God let out a painful screech. Its large body was tossed and smashed on a nearby ocean surface.

Wham!

Countless waves surged as Sea God laid in a pool of blood and hissed in pain. There were spider-web scars all over its body and there wasn’t one spot that was intact on its gigantic black build.

On a large wound, there were even yellow blisters on it.

“Retreat!!” On Sea God’s final struggle, it turned and wiggled its tail away. Rumbling like the sound of thunder, its large body sprung away.

It just pulled away like that!?

Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince both stood in shock as they watched Sea God make its escape.

The other old man’s whereabouts were unknown but it bodes ill rather than well.

Hiss…

The sky burst open a black and white ring. This ring was several thousand meters in circumference before swiftly shrinking back to the monster hanging on top of White Crab Island.

It grew a long brown tail, wagging it slowly like a lizard as though the center of gravity of the world was concentrated on its body.

“Watch,” the monster said with a sharp shriek.

“Selfishness, hatred, anger, pain… This sort of world should not exist in the first place.”

It extended its arm and in its palm was a large yellow blister. The blister burst open and out came tree roots growing in a ball.

The round ball twirled on its own as the roots within intertwined as complicated and sophisticated as a metal instrument.

Ding…

A beautiful harp sound was heard from the twirling of the ball.

“The last world…” The monster’s voice went from shrieking to a hoary man’s.

“The last anger.”

It lifted the ball up in a position of giving an offering.

Chapter 1238: Wind Up 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Swoosh!!

Large amounts of black roots in the ball shot in all directions. With a click, the black roots exploded out and grew to ends of the air.

At the same time, a shadow just beneath the monster towered to the sky, knocking the back of it.

Bang!!!

The airspace where the monster hung erupted in a mist of yellow fog.

“Four Directional Winds!!” A hysterical scream of coldness, anger, viciousness with a tinkling of silvery-white glow blazed within the yellow fog.

Clang clang clang clang!!

With four flashes of the silvery-white light, the yellow fog dispersed.

Yuria held a dagger as he hung in midair. A vast forcefield was lugging him straight into the air.

A few meters opposite him was the monster with clear dagger scars. Yellow blood was seeping from the wounds.

“You!!” The monster staggered backward and stared at Yuria with disbelief. “How could you be this strong!!??”

Yuria raised his arm where the back of his right hand bore a sarcoma glistening in white light.

“You’re not Qin.”

“Parasitism breed… I should have thought so… Should have thought so earlier!! Hahahaha!!” The monster burst into laughter. “Qin? That trash that suppressed me all those years? If I knew then, I wouldn’t have birth you!!! Ruining my plans!”

“What’s the point of bringing it up now, Father?” Yuria’s face was filled with never-before-seen coldness and composure.

Rings and rings of white ripples spread beneath his body. It was a basic way using overwhelming energy and vibrations which allowed him to levitate in midair.

“That’s true. Everything is a foregone conclusion now. I will personally rectify everything!!!” The monster was not the original Qin Jinqin but the source of all their sorrows, their father.

Swish!

Both of them disappeared on the spot and repeated close to each other.

Bang!

The blade and the monster’s arm intertwined in a collision. Yuria’s movements were like lightning, they contained heavy force but yet, they were violently swift.

Each collision of combat brought about them in mid-air exploded dynamically, releasing blast after blast in the air.

Those who were slightly closer had their eardrums rumbling from this noise.

The strength of these two were from the same source so they were basically equals. Nobody had the upper hand.

The real deal breaker would be the technique they used.

“Four Directional Winds, Reverse Trace!” Yuria held his blade with one arm and swept past the monster. In the high velocity of combat exchange, the dagger ripped several white lines backward in a flash, spreading to the back of the monster.

Shhh!

Blood spurted out.

The monster howled in pain. Yuria was a researcher who spent all his days studying techniques, after all. This monster could not keep up with Yuria who received killing techniques directly from Garen himself.

Moreover, Yuria’s memory recovery coupled with Garen’s technique and his personal killing experience birthed a new secret technique of his own.

“Windless.”

Yuria pressed on his blade with one arm. His body was burning in white flames. He had realized Garen’s move.

This was the distillation of the Sword Master state that Garen forcefully upgraded with his Soul Power.

With his current identity as the Four Great Cornerstone, he started to borrow the power of those around him.

On the ship, the remaining survivors were watching the ground-breaking fight from afar. This level completely surpassed any stage a human could achieve.

This included the transmigrators. A calm and peaceful voice appeared in everyone’s awareness at the same time.

“Are you willing to lend me your strength?” It was Yuria’s voice.

Any and all information was immediately exchanged from Yuria. His will, his hopes, his desires were transmitted out, into the hearts of these survivors.

At the same time, more than eighty percent chose yes.

The majority of them only had one thing in mind, one consensus.

Streams of air current naturally gathered by Yuria, rotating around him, forming a windless ball.

He pressed on the blade and raised it high. Large amounts of air current accumulated behind him, becoming a close transparent giant blade.

Hiss…!

All the air current and air were sucked into this transparent large blade, compacting together.

The monster was forced back from the strong currents. His face reeked of fear.

“What technique is this!!??”

It could sense that all of Yuria’s energy was focused onto this point. This sort of technique at this level exceeded the stage of pure body combat.

The energy gathered on that blade was enough to destroy it.

It was seemingly tiny yet harbored all of Yuria’s mind, body and spirit.

“Windless!”

Yuria’s dagger was raised high.

Swoosh!!!

With a flash of blade light, the giant blade cut the air open with an explosion. Yuria’s body was gone without a trace as if he had vanished into thin air.

Everything resumed to its peacefulness, leaving only the monster in midair. It was holding the black ball without moving an inch.

A clear blade cut stretched from its head to its abdomen blossomed in a dim white light.

Its entire body was ripped apart by this cut and separated in half.

“I…” The monster opened its mouth but was unable to finish his last sentence.

Boom!

It exploded into raining white liquid, splattering everywhere.

No one would have thought that within the monster was a smaller sized giant monster. It had the head of a little girl but its lower body was a distorted being with octopus-like tentacles.

Yuria stood behind the monster. He gently pointed the tip of his foot, spreading waves of white ripples, knocking off the splattering yellow liquid.

He calmly stared at the little girl that appeared from inside the monster.

“Brother.”

The little girl slowly turned around and calmly stared at Yuria. One of her tentacles grabbed the black ball and hung beside her.

“I’m finally able to meet you face to face… in this form.”

The dagger held by Yuria was gently put down. His hair wavered at the wind that it covered his eyes. He lowered his head.

“Just how did we, end up like this?”

“Why?” A confusion streaked past Zhi Jinqin’s face. “I really don’t know but is my own brother going to stop me?”

Her eyes fumed of innocence, “Isn’t it alright if we eat this entire world, together?

“Have everything belong to us.”

“What is the point?” Yuria gazed at his sister. Pain flashed past his eyes.

“The point?” Zhi Jinqin smiled. “This filthy world brought us nothing but pain.”

“Sometimes I feel like I am sent from above to create a new world. ”

“Everything was going on fine and there was no stopping.”

“This is the general trend!”

All her tentacles spread open into a round wheel and slowly rotated behind her.

A peculiar forcefield encircled her. For a moment, she looked like the descending demon in the legends.

“General trend?” Yuria looked at his sister who had become unfamiliar.

“Come, brother. We will create a new world together.” Zhi Jinqin reached out to her brother with one tentacle as though she was reaching out her arm.

“I have an Immortal Body, Everlasting Body.”

“If I can’t die or change myself, then I can only change this world.”

Zhi Jinqin carried a smile.

Yuria looked at the tentacle extended before him.

“We will be the Adam and Eve of the new world.”

“The origins of Eden.” Zhi Jinqin’s face was flushed with excitement as though she could see the far future.

“I…” Yuria extended his arm, “reject!”

With a smack, he knocked away the tentacle before him.

The smile on Zhi Jinqin’s face froze.

******

White Crab Island was far in sight.

Garen stood at the bow of the ship while looking at the ruined island from afar. There were large amounts of shipwreck floating around.

“What about Sea God? And the Three Countries’ Allied Forces?”

“Looks like it is all wiped out.” Nine-Tailed Fox walked by him with a stunned face. No one could have predicted Zhi Jinqin of White Crab Island would be this strong with Three Countries’ Allied Forces, top experts as well as Sea God and Yuria together. Under these circumstances, Yuria’s powers as Saviour would be overwhelmingly terrifying once he lent everyone’s strength.

“Is this world going to end?” Kong Xinxue walked behind the duo, looking at White Crab Island from afar.

“Contact Sea God.” Garen remained calm. The Energy Machine Imprint could reenact the earlier battle scale in a matter of seconds and such a scale and level surpassed his expectations.

Kong Xinxue and Nine-Tailed Fox beside him immediately contacted Sea God with a communication device.

“I’m sorry, I have retreated to beneath the sea.” Sea God’s voice came from the communication device and automatically translated to a common language. “The opposition is far too strong.”

“The world of humans will be over before we know it.” Sea God’s voice carried a sense of helplessness and fatigue.

“This level…” Garen’s arms pressed on the railings, “surpassed the peak that this world could accommodate.”

“I have informed the specialists of the special team.”

“The situation will soon be conveyed to the highest members of Lighthouse.”

“Perhaps here, only Suppressor could resolve everything,” Sea God spoke in a deep voice.

“Suppressor…” Nine-Tailed Fox covered her mouth as she raised her voice.

“Illusionist is currently blending Savior into one,” Sea God swiftly explained. “Once she succeeds, the world is done for good.”

“I am not used to putting hope on other people.” Garen cut him off. “Just because you guys couldn’t do it, it doesn’t mean I can’t.”

“You have no reason to risk it,” Sea God advised. “I know you killed Slayer and most probably are stronger than me but the opponent this time is different. We transmigrators don’t have to take a risk. We just need to wait for Suppressor and everything will stabilize.”

“My disciple is there.” Garen lifted his long blade. “I will always personally take care of my people. Always had been and always will.”

He carried his long blade and gently leaped towards the frontal ocean surface.

Swoosh.

The moment he had almost fallen into the water, Garen vanished.

Chapter 1239: Departure 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bang!!

A white flame detonated above White Crab Island.

The flames slowly subsided, revealing Zhi Jinqin’s monstrous body without a scratch.

“It’s useless.” She glared at Yuria opposite her. “Brother, have you forgotten about my special attribute? This sort of attack can’t even let me suffer a slight pain…”

The many black tentacles underneath her white skirt were dancing furiously. One of them whipped out vigorously, smacking Yuria.

Wham!

Yuria was beaten down from the sky, crashing into the surface of White Crab Island in flying dirt and rubble.

However, immediately, Yuria erected back in the air, fusing himself into the blade and forming a silver light shooting towards Zhi Jinqin.

“If the high temperature doesn’t work then I shall attack with pure physics!”

That earlier blast on Yuria was by creating a high-temperature explosive bomb with current technology but this was useless towards Zhi Jinqin.

Having been treated as a lab rat by father all these years, she had produced an adaptability to attributes of most attacks. Regular high temperature served no purpose.

Immortal Body brought about absolute adaptability and as long as there was energy, the body would slowly evolve to adapt to the worst conditions of the environment.

At the stage of Zhi Jinqin, it was no longer adaptability but an extreme mutation.

Swoosh!

Zhi Jinqin didn’t even dodge but remained afloat on the spot as Yuria waved his dagger. Her tentacles were chopped off by Yuria’s massive strength but once they were chopped, more tentacles grew back. Yuria was putting in a lot of effort into chopping, but chopping off two tentacles only caused three more to grow.

“Wind Trace!” Yuria shouted out. His blade cut thirteen stabs and each cut drew a transparent yet sharp current as they intertwined and shot towards Zhi Jinqin.

Bam bam bam…

The wind blades slewed at Zhi Jinqin without resistance.

“Brother… Have you forgotten?” Over ten deep cuts were inflicted on Zhi Jinqin’s body but in the blink of an eye, the wounds healed up. It was futile.

Zhi Jinqin extended one tentacle and placed it by her mouth like a finger and licked it.

“Aren’t you familiar, with my body?” She asked with a devilish glare which streaked past her eyes.

“Shut up!!” Yuria was huffing and puffing when he blurted in anger. He regained his spirits to chop off three tentacles around him and retreated a far distance before stopping.

“You’re not my sister! Qin is not like you!” Yuria’s face flushed red. “How sickening!”

“Sickening?” Zhi Jinqin paused. “You dare say your own sister is sickening…” One of her tentacles stretched down and extended swiftly, diving somewhere on White Crab Island before swishing and shrinking back.

Whilst her tentacle shrunk, it grabbed a female body that had lost consciousness. It was Parakeet.

“Then, what do you think of Parakeet?” Zhi Jinqin looked more and more devilish.

“Let go of her!” Yuria’s grip on the dagger tightened. Seeing his sister that was a complete stranger now, his heart was burdened with an accumulation of torrents that could explode at any moment.

“Her?” Zhi Jinqin uncovered a sense of wickedness. Wham!

Her tentacle tightened and squished Parakeet by the waist. The two parts of Parakeet’s body in the white dress fell in two directions as it broke apart.

“Brother… Do you feel good?” Zhi Jinqin opened her mouth again. What caught the stunned Yuria off guard was that she was using Parakeet’s voice.

“You!!” Yuria took a few steps backward. He stared at Zhi Jinqin in disbelief.

“Parakeet is just one of my clothes… What? Did brother fall in love with her?” Zhi Jinqin’s sickening smile deepened, “That won’t do… You belong to me, only to me forever… Even if she’s a clone, it won’t do!”

“You’ve lost your mind!” Yuria really did not know how to face this chaos.

Qin was completely out of it. She was no longer that cute and sweet sister he knew.

“You’re not Qin… You’re not…”

With a swish, he charged forwards, wielding his blade from side to side into a silvery-white ball of light. He shot it at Zhi Jinqin.

At the same time, his other arm tossed out a silvery-white little ball from his sleeve, fusing it into the ball of light.

Zhi Jinqin showed no resistance and allowed his random attacks.

Boom!

In the area the both of them at, the sky exploded in blossoms of ice. White snowflakes scattered around.

Yuria’s right arm held on to his saber that was frozen in a flower of ice and stabbed deeply into Zhi Jinqin’s right breast.

“It’s useless.” Zhi Jinqin chuckled as though it wasn’t her that was stabbed.

Even the frozen bomb was useless…!?

Yuria scattered to retreat as he struggled to land to his original position.

He watched with wide eyes as Qin’s penetrated breast healed immediately as though nothing had happened.

“There’s one more move.” Something quietly appeared in Yuria’s hand. He held it tight behind him as he held his dagger with one hand, but he realized that his blade broke into pieces.

After experiencing fluctuating high and low temperatures in such a short time frame, the dagger could not withstand it any longer.

He tossed the dagger aside. Looking at his sister opposite him, the person before him was definitely not Qin. For all these years, the sister that was gentle and sweet was not a twisted monster. Only by knocking her awake, there would be a possibility of saving this disease riddled world.

Thinking of those that may die from this crisis; Nine-Tailed Fox, mother Light Path, his former classmates, teachers as well as countless innocent people, Garen felt a lump in his heart.

“My last attempt.”

He raised the thing he held in his hand. That black metal ball was heavily engraved with a dark blue character. It was not known what character it was. The character was reeking a pale blue fluorescence from within.

“This again? It’s useless.” Zhi Jinqin laughed. “But I guess it’s okay. What’s one more attempt to have you give up?”

She spread open her arms as if trying to embrace Yuria.

“Come.”

Yuria’s face remained unchanged and his body shot away in a swish. The distance of tens of meters was breezed through and in an instant, he appeared before Zhi Jinqin to smash the ball into his sister’s chest.

And at this moment, the black ball with blue characters turned red.

“This is!!??” Zhi Jinqin’s face changed. “Heavy Acidic Thunder!”

Kaboom!

With a dull rumble, the area between them blasted an air of red mist. This mist was like a living being absorbed into Zhi Jinqin.

Ah!!!

She lifted her eyes and grumbled in pain. The tentacles beneath her skirt started to scramble in berserk. A few of the tentacles started whipping at Yuria.

With a wham, Yuria lost consciousness. It was as though a train rammed into him as his bones crackled. He crashed into the ground like a rocket, splattering a fog of debris and smoke. It was not known how deep the pit was but it was at least tens of meters.

A white fog was steaming from the hole. Yuria laid in the center of the core covered in wounds. Rock and dirt around started to melt in red. The high-velocity friction had caused an astoundingly high temperature.

After the red mist was completely absorbed by Zhi Jinqin, her body revealed herself again. Her clear upper body skin rotted and half the flesh of her face corroded into a wax form and was dripping.

“Brother… I’m in pain…” Zhi Jinqin was sobbing but her eyes were mixed with the hissing and howling of some monsters that it sent chills down spines.

The bones of Yuria’s legs were completely broken as he struggled to get up from the ground. Although the vitality of his body was much stronger, facing such a hit and without the Immortal Body such as Zhi Jinqin’s caused unbearable pain. Sweat mixed with blood from his wounds were bleeding from his broken legs, causing a bloody smell of metal as it evaporated on the high-temperature surface.

He had borrowed all possible powers and the abilities of Savior had wielded to its maximum to try to injure Qin’s body but he was still powerless against her Immoral ability of unlimited recovery.

He grabbed onto the walls with his arms, disregarding the hissing sounds on his palms from the high temperature.

Staring at Qin who was waving her tentacles about in the air, his heart sank.

“So it ends?…” He lowered his head to look at himself. He was powerless to continue.

For a mortal to achieve such power, wounding a terrifying monster that even missiles and cannons could not harm, there was no hope.

“Didn’t I already predict this outcome?” Yuria smiled bitterly. Qin’s Immortal Body was an outcome he foresaw but he still came, not to put in a last effort but to bet on the possibility of awakening his sister’s awareness.

“Perhaps I still carry a slight hope with me, that it was Father’s plan and not Qin’s…” Yuria felt confused but surprisingly calm.

Muddling away his life all these years with his sister changing his memory and strolling away, his companions that died in the fire, his friends, brothers, one by one were still standing before him as though they were still alive.

“After living all these years…” He stretched out his arm and looked at his young pale arm. It was obvious that Zhi Jinqin has used some technique to reinvent his body to prolong youth.

“It’s time to put an end to it.”

“Brother… Why are you still so silly?” Zhi Jinqin’s voice was heard from the sky. “You’re always playing a fool, this is really causing me trouble…”

A rumble was heard and with a dull crash, countless tentacles fell from the sky and smacked at Yuria who was in the pit.

Chapter 1240: Departure 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Why can’t you stay on the same page as me?” Zhi Jinqin’s tone calmed down. “Perhaps there are a few screws loose in your head. Let me do a quick check for you again…”

Yuria mustered his very last strength as he raised his head, looking at the great number of hands coming down from the sky.

“Alternating my memories again?” He smiled wryly as he pressed his hand onto his forehead. “I do not wish to live an ignorant life anymore.”

“Do you have a choice?”

Zhi Jinqin smirked as she swiftly grabbed his hand which was raised up. Without a moment’s delay, the defenseless Yuria was lifted up into the air.

The sunlight pierced through the clouds and shone between them. The golden sunlight was extremely pure as Zhi Jinqin’s insanity and ugliness was clear as day under the sunlight.

She saw her own reflection from her brother’s calm eyes.

She suspended her finger gently in front of Yuria’s forehead. The tip of her finger gradually became thin as it started rotating. Then similar to a blooming flower, it opened up and revealed a tiny mouth with a substantial amount of thin grey brownish teeth.

“Brother, you’re always so disobedient.” Zhi Jinqin put on a gentle smile on her face once more as the tip of her finger drilled into Yuria’s forehead.

Boom!!

A blinding light dazzled.

************************

“That is… the light from an explosion! Why is it so intense!??” Vulture No.1, who was in the rocky boat, raised his head as he looked at the silver light bursting out in the sky.

“No… That’s not a light…” Red Nation’s prince was lying just beside him as both of them had miraculously survived. However, they were completely immobile and could only move their eyes.

“It’s a saber…!”

“A saber?”

Slash!!

In that instant, the silver afterimage of a saber that spanned a few kilometers struck down to the ground from the sky.

It landed silently on White Crab Island.

The whole island slowly opened up from the center without displaying any other movements. It had been sliced into two!

Then, an enormous amount of seawater started gushing into the empty space between the island that had just been split into half.

“It’s Garen!!”

Vulture No. 1 quickly looked over to see where the trace of the saber originated. There, he saw a shadow of a tall and muscular man.

He was levitating in the middle of the air as he looked down at Zhi Jinqin and Yuria below him. He had a three-meter-long thin silver saber in his hand and was in a black, tight body suit. The suit did not flutter at all as if it was not affected by the surrounding air current.

“He has finally arrived…” Vulture No.1 looked at Garen, who was in the sky, with a complicated feeling as this level of battle had far surpassed their expectation from the very beginning.

“There’s still ten minutes left before the final bombing…”

“When the time comes, everything here will be turned into ash.” The Red Nation’s Prince continued his sentence. “Our respondents have yet to even appear before us. It seems like we have been abandoned.”

“That’s right…” Vulture No.1 sighed. “We’ve served the nation with everything we have for most of our lives and we’re going to die in this place. This is totally unexpected.”

“This is what politics is all about. Aren’t we used to this?” Prince smirked.

************

“You’re a disgrace, Yuria. How could you be beaten up by your own sister this badly.” Garen did not know what to say as he looked at Yuria who had barely escaped from her grasp. “It’s really a disgrace to have you as my disciple.”

“Brother Saber… I didn’t wish for this result as well…” Yuria forced a smile on his face. He seemed to be still in the mood to crack a joke. “You have no idea how powerful Xiaojie is.”

“I really have no idea how powerful she really is…” Garen gently puts Yuria down and out of the battlefield far away via the air current. “Be careful. It’s been a while since I go all out so don’t blame me if you were accidentally killed.”

“Hey!” Yuria still had something to say but was already sent far away.

Garen turned around and looked at Zhi Jinqin. All of her tentacles which were cut off by Garen’s strike just a while ago were already growing back. The Ring of Energy Field behind her had become even clearer as many more of them had started rotating, and a pair of eyes glowing faintly in red stared right at him.

“Do you have any last words before you die?” Garen said casually.

“Last words? Hehehe… It’s supposed to be me saying that… Master Garen…”

Shush!!

A huge amount of tentacles rushed towards Garen from all directions, covering all the lights around him in an instant. It was as if the day had instantly turned into night.

As the tentacles reached a few meters away from Garen, they started exploding, turning into countless yellow-green blisters packed with a voluminous amount of yellow and viscous fluid that lunged directly towards Garen.

“Let’s see how you can dodge them!!” Zhi Jinqin relinquished a huge amount of her tentacles in an instant as she retreated swiftly while she stared at Garen and scoffed.

The area was already surrounded by a pile of grey-brown tentacle meatballs.

Pew!!

A blinding silver light flashed across at high speed where she was earlier at, flying far away into the sea. No one knew how far it had gone as it disappeared in the horizon.

Pew pew pew pew pew!!

In an instant, the meatballs collapsed as a black human silhouette rushed out from it, slicing all of the tentacles easily as if they were tofu. The afterimages of the saber beside him had turned into a storm of sharp sabers as not a single drop of viscous liquid had stained his shirt.

Countless of the saber’s afterimages converged into one point and combined into one saber. With Garen as the wielder, nothing could stop its advancement as the blade moved.

Zhi Jinqin could not react in time as she did not expect Garen to break out this quick. The saber cut across her waist in a single strike and was instantly retracted back to Garen’s side as he held it with only one hand.

“I…” Zhi Jinqin opened her mouth but she could not emit any noise. Then, with a pop, she melted and exploded out of the blue, turning into a liquid bursting out in all directions.

Then, there was a sudden change below the two of them as half of the White Crab Island exploded up into the sky. The few hundred meters wide mountain was shot up into the sky towards Garen.

Kaboom!

The grey-white mountain rolled as it charged towards Garen. As the explosion was too powerful causing the mountain which had an incredibly huge surface area to have an incredibly high velocity, Garen had no choice but to take the collision head-on as he did not expect this unforeseen circumstance.

Shing!!

A silver line of the saber was released, splitting the mountain in half from the center.

Garen remained levitating in the middle of the air. He casually waved the saber in his hand, cutting the huge mountain in half with ease. This cleared a passage big enough for him to pass through it.

Garen’s physical abilities had reached an extremely powerful level ever since he had absorbed Slayer to further enhance his Soul Ring. The immensely powerful Soul Ring was constantly supplying energy towards his physical body. If not for the restriction of this universe, the current Garen would be in his strongest state compared to his past. The Garen in the Mech World was no match compared to his current strength. Although there was a huge difference in strength due to the universe’s loose laws in the Mech World, Garen’s physical abilities were no match compared to his current strength which was induced from the Soul Ring.

“Hehehe… This is amazing. I’ve got to give credit to a powerhouse who can kill even the Slayer!”

Zhi Jinqin, who was clustering back into existence revealed a twisted smile.

“But, so what!?”

A black tumor appeared on her arms and was then shot towards Garen as it detached from her body.

Pew.

The tumor exploded at least ten meters in front from Garen. It was cut in half even though the reflection of Garen’s saber could not be seen.

Boom!!

What came next was an intense radioactive light.

The black and white halo spread everywhere. As Garen was unable to surpass the speed of light, he was engulfed in it since he was caught off guard.

The world around him turned black and white regardless if it was the sea water or the sunlight.

“Radiation, huh?” Garen held the saber with both of his hands as he straightened his posture. He could feel that the radiation was eroding his skin.

He then jolted his saber.

Buzz!!!

The reflection of the sabers gleamed up around Garen instantaneously after giving off the low buzzing noise before the saber in his hand vanished.

The intense radioactive light was directly reflected away.

Boom!

The black and white radioactive ball collapsed from within. Garen rushed out like a canon and struck Zhi Jinqin who had just morphed back into existence.

Kaboom! Zhi Jinqin was mercilessly hit down to the sea as the impact created a thunder-like roar. The white water splashed up in the sky and was cut in half by a single strike from Garen.

He had no intention of letting his enemy live as he immediately plunged downward.

He raised his saber over his head and struck down once more.

The deep blue sea was separated in half similar to a blue transparent fruit being cut in half with that single strike. The sea cracked open, revealing Zhi Jinqin who was lying on the bed of the seafloor.

She was wounded all over. All of her tentacles and limbs were broken and the left side of her head had even vanished. However, she still looked up and stared at Garen who was in the sky.

“You can’t kill me! Hahaha…!!” Zhi Jinqin laughed maniacally.

Garen frowned as he rushed down and performed a quartered dismemberment^1 with a few slices with his saber.

Although Zhi Jinqin’s limbs and head were completely dismembered from her body, half of her head was still laughing like a lunatic.

“It’s useless. Father spent decades to try and kill me with a variety of methods but to no avail. Do you really think you can kill me with your technique?”

Her words were no longer intelligible but she was still laughing maniacally.

“Something’s wrong.” Garen tried to sense the fluctuation of Zhi Jinqin’s Soul Energy. Nothing. She was not emitting any Soul Energy at all.

The Energy Machine Imprint analyzed.

He did not believe that nothing could not be killed in any world, as immortality was nothing but a subjective term.

Zhi Jinqin took the opportunity to attack when he let his guard down. She rose up into the sky as her entire body exploded, turning into yellow-green viscous liquid as it converged together in a sphere.

The viscous spherical liquid shrunk before rapidly expanded like a balloon. It became larger and voluminous as if someone was inflating it from the inside. Its diameter quickly went from ten meters to tens of meters, a hundred meters and finally a few hundred meters!!!

The viscous liquid sphere had turned into a huge grey brown balloon within a short amount of time.

A huge fairytale face similar to of McDonald’s appeared on the surface of the sphere, it opened its mouth as it tried to swallow Garen up.

Standing on the bed of the seafloor, Garen raised his head up looking at the weird looking balloon monster coming after him.

“What a pointless struggle.”

His face was calm as he slashed with his saber with only one of his hands.

Pew!

The trace of the saber which spanned a few hundred meters was shot out, slicing through the huge face from the front to the back as if the huge face was nothing but liquid and gas.

It was then Garen set his sight on the transparent Ring of Energy Field behind the huge balloon.

“That is…” He squinted.

Chapter 1241: Volatility 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen moved sideways as he illusively evaded ^1 the attack from the giant face. Perhaps it would be effective going against a typical powerhouse with such speed, but it was completely ineffective against him who stood at the pinnacle among the powerhouses. Despite all of these, he was still unsure of Zhi Jinqin’s ultimate goal.

“Perhaps this is her defense is at its peak in this form?”

Garen recalled the effect of his slash a moment ago. It did not seem to be effective against the monster in front of him at all.

He leaped to the right side of the face monster as he threw his sword to pierce through it.

Pew!

The trace of the saber pierced through the face as if it were air and there was no effect on it.

“I see.” Garen had somewhat understood the situation as the Energy Machine Imprint instantly analyze the basic reasoning of this giant face. “The source of immortality should be that Energy Field Ring on her back.”

He then laid his sight on that giant Ring of Energy Field behind the monster’s back.

In just a single step, Garen leaped hundreds of meters and appeared behind it. He was now less than ten meters away from the Ring of Energy Field.

Garen raised his saber high up as his Soul Energy started to boil. The effect of the Soul Ring was to raise one’s martial prowess. He would be able to increase it by one level with one Soul Ring. Garen, who had three, completed Soul Rings had only been using one of his Soul Ring to increase his strength.

He now planned to activate the strength of the second Soul Ring.

“Burn.”

He reached out his hand and a red fiery fire started to ignite on his left hand. It was not white but pure red similar to blood.

His left hand’s strength, speed, toughness and everything else was greatly increased to the point they were doubled up in an instant.

Everything happened in an instant, which the face monster had yet to react and turned around.

Without any expression on his face, Garen reached out his left hand. Although he was still ten meters away from the Ring of Energy Field, he reached out his hand to grab hold of the Ring of Energy Field as if there was an invisible and huge hand.

In an instant, Garen felt that he had touched a circle of cold, hard metallic item.

He was not physically touching it but instead, his Soul Energy’s fluctuation had sensed a certain cold object as his Soul Energy was being utilized.

“Burn.”

Garen thought.

The bloody red fire then propagated from his hand to the Ring of Energy Field.

Kaboom!!

The entire Ring of Energy Field was on fire as it lighted up the entire sky.

Psst!!

The face monster started to become flat like a deflating balloon as the air inside was ejected out turning into gales. He no longer needed to continue attacking.

Garen levitated behind its back, unaffected by the current by the slightest. He was staring at the Ring of Energy Field that was in front of him.

The Ring of Energy Field started slowing down as a black crude oil-like viscous fluid started flowing out from within.

Gush!!

A terrifying Soul Energy Aura had turned into the wind as it blew towards Garen, fluttering his shirt and hair to the back.

He remained unmoved as he squinted at the Ring of Energy Field in front of him. An extremely familiar aura was slowly emitting out from the Ring of Energy Field.

The sky had turned red without him realizing, blood red bubbles started appearing around Garen in the sky. These bubbles seemed to be made from blood and each of them ranged from ten meters to hundreds of meter in diameter.

These bubbles would pop and resurface over and over again as if the surrounding had instantly turned into a Dream World.

The black crude oil-like liquid propagated around the entire surface of the Ring of Energy Field, turning the Ring into a black mirror.

Hehehe…

A sharp and playful laugh traveled out from the black mirror.

“What a rare occurrence.” A deep-tone and majestic voice rang within the sharp laugh. “To be able to meet someone of the same level here. How fortunate.”

“The Void Language…” Garen was slightly startled. The language Void Creatures used was actually similar to Ancient Endor’s language. As both of them had battled against each other for a very long time, both parties had learned their respective languages. Naturally, as a Void Pursuer, it was necessary for him to be able to communicate with them.

“Who are you?” He was lazy to figure out the origin of his opponent and asked straightforwardly via the Void Language.

“My ancient name is too long, so you can call me Canster.”

“Canster? Holy Voice?” The word Canster was the pronunciation of the word Holy Voice in Void Language. Garen frowned. “What’s the purpose of you appearing before me on your own accord? You’re exhausting a huge amount of energy to talk to me from such a far distance. Please don’t tell me you did so because you’re bored.”

“Bored?” Canster laughed. “You’re right. I was really bored to the point I wanted to see what kind of a person is able to kill two of my generals. I wouldn’t have believed it’s someone of the same level and existence as me without witnessing you with my very own eyes. Tell me your name.”

Garen did not feel any ill intention from the opposing party. It was obvious that the distance was too far apart and the opponent could only transmit his voice as this action alone required a lot of energy from him.

This distance could not be measured via light years as it was the distance between universes. Garen did not know how many universes he and Canster were between and the amount of energy required for them to communicate for every second was astronomical.

“I have too many nicknames and you won’t be able to remember them anyway. You can just call me Garen.” He said calmly. “Your purpose of coming to this universe is because of the Soul Ring as well, right?”

He did not care if anyone could understand him as the Ancient Endor Language and Void Language sounded like a meaningless howl towards humans and they would not be able to understand anything. If it was not for Black Sethe and his incredibly powerful attribute abilities, he would not even be able to learn these two languages.

“It’s unfortunate that you were one step ahead of me.” The opponent laughed. “However, the Illusionist is mine.”

“Since the result has been decided, what’s the purpose of you coming out?” Garen asked calmly.

“There’s no purpose and it was a whim to meet the person who took all the goods away from me.” Canster paused for a moment. “By the way, there are too little amount of people who are of the same level as I. The two sides of the Mother Stream, the Void, and Ancient Endor will soon become a relic of the past. Compared to the current generation, we are just ancient relics who refuse to step down from the stage… I forgot to mention to you that I have another identity as well. I’m a Warlock Pursuer.”

“Oh?” Garen recalled his identity as a Void Pursuer and realized that both of their identities were relatively similar. However, it was strange that there was no reaction from the oath towards the Mother Stream when he was facing a Void Demon Lord.

“Do you feel it?” Canster laughed. “The strength of the Mother Stream is weakening. Hence the constraint towards me is wearing off as well. The True Soul… The True Soul within the Mother Stream has started to perish.”

“Impossible!” Garen was shocked. “The True Soul is eternal. How could it perish!?” Regardless if it were the Ancient Endor or the Void Creatures, those who pursued to reach the pinnacle of the world were actually pursuing to reach the True Soul Level. The difference between them was that the Void Creatures had found their own path to the True Soul after learning from the Warlocks. One could say that Warlocks and Void Creatures were enemies and tutors towards each other simultaneously. The Warlocks learned Inherited Secret Technique from the Void Creatures and paved their paths forward, expanding their civilization’s vision and height. On the other hand, the Void Creatures had learned the truth and knowledge towards reaching the pinnacles of existence from the Warlocks – True Soul.

One could say that the True Soul was no longer just the pinnacle of the Ancient Endor’s civilization, it had become the pinnacle for both civilizations.

“I’ve seen two Eternal True Souls perished with my very own eyes.” A sense of sadness could be heard from Canster’s tone. “Their bodies had disintegrated into countless of galaxies and had turned into the blood of the universe, supplying nutrients towards thousands of beings.”

Garen was stunned by this news.

It was his ultimate goal to reach the True Soul, which was the pinnacle of this world. But now, somebody was telling him that the realm that he had been pursuing was collapsing out of the blue.

“Are you saying that our path…” Garen held his saber tightly as the bottom of his eyes were filled with an additional layer of sorrow. He had never felt so emotional throughout his travel in so many worlds.

“Our path has been cut off.” Although Canster seemed calm, he was similar to Garen, a volcano that was about to burst at any moment. “I have chosen three representatives out of eighty million citizens in the Dark Void to try to get in touch with the Ancient Endor’s civilization. Now that the Mother Stream’s Oath is unable to restrain everyone, you should come up with a plan as well. As an opponent of the same level, the war between our civilizations has been ongoing for far too long. Both you and I are tired of it.”

“We have been watching you ever since the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen reported your situation to the higher up. We will give you this world as our sincerity in hope that you could select three representatives from your side as well so that we can form a parliament. The Mother Stream is depleting. It is your direct lifeline and our indirect lifeline. With the True Souls perishing before us, a great threat will fall upon us.” Canster explained calmly. “Since we are unable to reach the high-ranking Demon Lord from your side, we have no choice but to request you to inform them.”

Garen bit his lips slightly.

He could not tell them that he was not in touch with the higher ups from Ancient Endor. Other than the ancient secrets that Black Sethe had once told him, he was no better than a typical Ancient Endor’s Inheritor.

“I will notify the upper levels of this news.” He could not reveal that he had no one backing him up here since his opponent was clearly a representative from the highest level. Once they realized that he was alone, it would spawn trouble that he could not handle on his own. The Demon Lord Class was not something he, a Demon Lord Class novice, could handle. He could not simply reveal his background without knowing the exact situation.

“Time is running out. Quickly…” Canster’s voice started toning down slowly. Then, a small black cube item came out from the black mirror. It looked like a Rubik’s Cube as it was made out of many more small black cubes.

Garen grabbed hold of the item.

“A communication device?” His Soul Energy immediately understood the purpose of this item.

Perhaps it was not his Soul Energy that sensed it but the item transmitted a huge amount of information to him the moment he grabbed hold of it.

“We represent the ancient and the highest level of order among the Mother Stream System. Among the countless of life born from the Mother Stream from all universes, our civilizations can only be considered the best. If you can get in touch with the True Soul Level from your side within a thousand years, please inform us as soon as possible. We need to think of a way to stop the Mother Stream from depleting!”

Casnter’s tone became weaker and lower as a faint hissing noise started to appear, disrupting their communication.

Chapter 1242: Volatility 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

As the voice vanished completely, Garen only then felt that his surrounding had finally cleared up. The bloody bubbles had vanished and the sky had returned to its original, clear blue shade. It was as if the environmental change was nothing but an illusion.

“The high ranking Demon Lord is truly impressive. He was able to pull me into the Dream World in an instant.” Garen looked at the black cube in his hand. It was obvious that the enemy had mistaken him for an Ancient Endor Inheritor with a strong background due to his rapid improvement.

“Unfortunately, I am just a normal Inheritor who has no existing background.”

As he transmigrated so many worlds, he had the suspicion that the Ancient Endor’s Demon Lords had all perished. Excluding the remnant soul, Black Sethe, that he had met earlier, he had yet to meet another Demon Lord Class being. On the other hand, he had met quite a few Void Creatures instead.

Sizzle… Clang!

The Ring of Energy Field’s black mirror shattered into countless of black debris which disintegrated into thinner and smaller pieces. Soon, it diffused into the air and had fused together with the world.

Although he was not able to absorb the Illusionist’s Soul Ring, he had unexpectedly obtained a piece of news from the Void Creature. He was not sure whether the news regarding the depletion of the Mother Stream was legitimate hence he had to validate it. However, Garen believed that this news was very likely as there was no need for the Void Creature to lie about it at all.

“I didn’t expect to receive such news instead of absorbing the Soul Ring.” Garen slowly lowered the saber in his hand and the rocky water was instantly calmed down by his intense Energy Field.

With him as the epicenter, all of the waves on the surface of the blue sea within ten kilometers calmed down so quickly that one could see it with the naked eye.

Holding his saber, Garen gently landed on the boat that was approaching him. Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue were on the deck. They looked rather miserable as they were drenched from head to toe from the waves. But they did not care how they looked as they stared at Garen with an unacquainted gaze as he came down.

“How did it go?” Nine-Tailed Fox stepped forward and whispered. “We’ve seen your battle. You’re very powerful. I’ve seen a battle between the Suppressors before in the Lighthouse and they were about as strong as you are.” She tried to retain her arrogant tone but she felt rather helpless as she talked face to face with Garen.

Her gaze was locked onto Garen’s saber that was in his hand.

She was once an incredibly powerful monster who once ruled over a world before and believed that she was strong enough. However, she was only slightly stronger than an average human in this world where the restriction was incredibly tight. Only she knew the difference in strength between her and Garen, who was able to become so ridiculously powerful in this world.

She felt extremely unease as she stared at Garen. She felt that she was a commoner who was standing in front of a murderer who had just killed a person with a gun. Her life would be threatened if the opponent was slightly unhappy with her.

The feeling of her life not being within her grasp made her felt extremely threatened. She, who was already an extremely insecure person, felt even more unease as she stood in front of Garen at such a close distance.

“It’s good because everything has been resolved. Since the host of the virus has been taken care of, it should lose its sustainability and would no longer be a threat. I’m heading towards Lighthouse immediately and would not stay long in this world. Are you guys coming along with me or do you prefer to follow up later on?” Garen casually asked.

“We will catch up with you later on.” Kong Xinxue spoke up as she noticed Nine-Tailed Fox was feeling uneasy. She, on the other hand, was fine with it. Garen had always been rather secretive and people who practiced the Mother Stream System always did things differently from the rest.

Since she herself had not much power, she was used to facing against people much stronger than her.

“You really concealed a lot of your strength. Hehe.” Kong Xinxue walked around Garen once. “I will definitely look for you if I were to be in trouble. You better not reject my request! It may be a life or death situation to us but child’s play to you.”

“No problem.” Garen smiled. He knew that it was all just lip service. Their self-esteem would not allow them to ask for help unless it was an actual life or death situation. In fact, Garen suspected that these two might not even look for him for help if they really were in a tight spot.

“Is there anything else that needs to be resolved?” Kong Xinxue looked behind Garen. “Look, your disciple is coming for you.”

Garen turned around and saw Yuria gliding towards him. He had already gathered all of the survivors at one location when Garen and the Demon Lord who puppeteered Zhi Jinqin were having a conversation. He was currently gliding towards him with a panicked look on his face.

“Run!! This place is going to be completely destroyed!! They are going to use nuclear bombs!!!” He shouted as he was still a dozen meters away from them.

Garen, Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue’s face turned pale as they heard what he had said.

Since this world’s restriction was too great, Garen himself could not guarantee that he would be able to defend against a nuclear bomb’s explosion.

“Let’s go!”

He turned his head around to look at the marines on the ships but he did not see anyone on the ship. It seemed that the marines on the ship had hidden themselves up.

“I’ll go and inform them!” Nine-Tailed Fox reacted.

The trio then started to move swiftly.

Yuria started to move the survivors nearby to Garen’s ship.

Since the Lighthouse’s seal had yet to be undone, Garen could only wait with everyone else in the ship.

The shocked and mentally fatigued marines who had holed up were forced back into their delegated posts. They then started to turn their ships around and left the area swiftly.

Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince were paralyzed as they were rescued by Yuria as well. Both of them had given a lot of strength to Yuria as they had lent their strengths to him when the Savior’s ability was activated.

Both of them faced each other while they laid on the deck.

“I have never expected that things would end like this.” Vulture No.1 was speechless.

“I didn’t expect this as well.” The Prince gave out a long sigh. The clumsy Yuria had just torn his wound on his leg by another two centimeters and this made him felt extremely painful to the point he started to sweat profusely.

“All I know is that when I have healed, I need to skin this kid off or I am not…”

“Hey hey hey!” Yuria was carried over and placed beside them. He was fully covered in white bandages and only his eyes could be seen. “I risked my life to save you two. Can you treat me like a person who had just saved your lives?”

“We would survive even if you didn’t save us. Those who looked down on me, The Prince, are already dead!” The Red Nation’s Prince said with a deep tone.

“You?” Yuria scoffed.

“I hate people scoffing right at my face the most. You’re so dead! You’re dead the moment I can start moving again!” Red Nation’s Prince was furious.

“DIdn’t you say those that look down on you are already dead? Well, I am still very much alive.” Yuria put on a sloppy look on his face.

“Just you wait!” The Prince was obviously pissed as he stared at Yuria with killing intent.

“Alright, alright. Keep those thoughts to yourself.” Vulture No.1, who has always been a good man, tried to dissolve the situation. He was rather speechless towards The Prince. “You’re an old man now. What’s the point of verbally cussing at others?”

“I!” the prince still had more to say but he saw Vulture’s gaze. He looked at where he was looking to see Yuria had his face up, with two streams of clear, crystal-like liquid flowing down his cheeks.

“This kid’s family has completely perished. What’s the point of arguing with him?” Vulture No. 1 whispered. “He killed his father with his own hands and his sister has been killed by his master. Then, he found out that his mother is actually not his mother. He wouldn’t have left the house if his father killed his mother and even planned to murder his sister and him. All in all, it’s a complete mess.”

“What? Such a mess.” Red Nation’s Prince was speechless as well.

“That’s right. It’s a mess.” Vulture No.1 lamented. “What was just a family’s issue had turned into an international mess. Many outsiders had suffered death and injuries.” He sighed and stopped speaking.

After going through a life and death battle side by side, both of them did not put up on a mask between each other as they were both abandoned by their own respective countries. They managed to get along well as they sympathized with each other.

The ships were moving away from the White Crab Island at an increasing speed to the point where it was on the verge of flying away from the sea.

Garen would occasionally release a gust of wind with his palm at the back of the boat as he tried to push the boat forward.

He stared at the White Crab Island from afar.

Suddenly, a pitch black torpedo-like object appeared in the sky. It had a golden-white tail on its back as it quietly dropped into the crevice of the White Crab Island.

Boom!!

An eye-blinding dazzle flashed across the sky, seemingly turning the sky into a pure white paper. It was so bright that everything was dyed white in color.

Garen shut his eyes, but he could still feel the blinding light piercing through his eyelid and into his retina.

He then tried to cover his eyes with his hands but to no avail, since his hands were dyed completely white as well.

Ahh!!

He heard cries of agony behind him as their eyes were excited by the blinding light. They would eventually lose their sight if their eyes were to continue being excited by such blinding light at such a close distance.

“My eyes…!” Garen heard Kong Xinxue’s painful cry.

Garen sighed, and raised up his three-meter long saber and sliced it to the front.

Cling!

A ten-meter tall silver curtain was erected, blocking the crowd from the light.

The majority intensity of the light was reflected back and the deck of the ship was much dimmer than before. Although it was still bright, it was very much better.

“Be careful of the waves!!”

One man shouted loudly but no one could hear him as the explosion’s shockwave had already reached them.

Garen was the only one who could hear him through the vibrations.

He then looked at the White Crab Island and saw a few hundred meters tall tsunami about ten knots away from them. It was fast approaching the ship as it kept folding the sea repeatedly.

The blinding light pierced through the tsunami, dying it completely white. It was as if it was glowing uniformly as it turned into a huge giant water wall which spanned hundreds of meters tall.

Behind the huge tsunami was the mushroom cloud that ascended into the sky. The fiery red fire and smoke fused together as the light dimmed down. What came next was an intensive trembling and roar.

The entire ship started to tremble and shake thoroughly.

“The distance is too close.” Garen frowned.

He held his saber up and gently flicked at it.

Buzz!

The metallic saber started to vibrate as it released an ear-deafening buzzing sound.

Boom!

The saber did not even break as he fought with Zhi Jinqin earlier. However, it had turned into a chunk of debris as it was shot towards the back of the sea. What followed along this debris were those high buzzing noises.

The sound waves canceled out the huge sound created from the nuclear bomb as Garen was able to cancel out the noise with great precision instead of creating a superpositioned wave via his Energy Machine Imprint.

“It’s all over!” He casually threw away the saber in his hand. Everything in this world had come to a closure. The next thing he wanted to do was to deal with the Lighthouse incident.

Chapter 1243: Lighthouse 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After the great battle with Zhi Jinqin, the pandemic, worldwide spread of the virus finally returned to normal. Without the support of the parental host body, most of the virus lost their strong infection rates instantly and were speedily eradicated as if roots without water.

Most of the humans, animals, and plants that were infected had produced antibodies on their own. Without the parental Yuri’s Kiss, it was actually just a normal flu virus.

Garen brought the boat full of people back safely. Unlike the expectations of all the forces, they were not destroyed by the impact of the nuclear bomb at the final juncture. It was evident that this matter was beyond the consciousness of the various high-level major forces. However, Red Nation’s Prince and Vulture No. 1 were slightly discouraged. After returning home once again, they seized control of their influences to eliminate a group of buffoons from the forces who emerged to seize their authority before retiring behind the scenes. As both of them harbored gratitude towards Garen, they would occasionally meet up for a drink with him. They discovered that an old soul was concealed beneath Garen’s youthful appearance. They gradually formed a teacher-student relationship with him that resembled Garen’s relationship with Yuria. Additionally, they discovered that Garen could answer and explain many things to them.

Through Garen’s assistance, the internal situation between Slann and the Red Nation stabilized quickly. Both countries then formed an alliance to counter the Black Federation that possessed powerful forces.

While he was waiting for Lighthouse to open their seal, Garen focused on fully digesting the large amount of Slaughtering Techniques that Slayer had given him. Meanwhile, his physical fitness rapidly increased and broke through to twenty points because of the Soul Ring’s nourishment. This turned him into an actual Humanoid Universal Beast. As the rules of this universe were unusually strict, all kinds of physical strength would certainly correspond to terrifying depletion because of their physical composition.

This caused Garen to encounter situations that he had never experienced in the previous universe.

****************

Boom boom… Hoo…

Boom boom… Shh…

Inside a gigantic soundproofed building somewhere in Slann, the sound of loud surging air currents that resembled thunder echoed occasionally. It entered and exited the space over and over again like a continuous stream of water that flowed steadily.

The colossal white building was built within a military base on the outskirts of the capital. Over a thousand guards were positioned in the surrounding area to defend it. However, the guards were not there to prevent the people inside from exiting but were there to stop outsiders from accidentally trespassing.

Garen sat with his legs crossed inside the building. Black alloy boards covered the long broad stretches of empty space fully. He sat upright on the center of the ground, densely-packed interchanging air holes were above his head.

Garen merely possessed the form of a muscular but normal human who was over two meters tall. However, the gentle sound of his breathing was currently accompanied by the sound of surging air currents that were as terrifyingly loud as thunder.

When most of the air and airstreams were sucked into his lungs through his nostrils, they would spurt out rapidly like cannon balls after being compressed before colliding chaotically inside the building.

The clothes on Garen’s back were constantly blown and upturned by the intense surging air currents as well.

Click.

The building’s main door was opened slowly before Vulture No. 1 who was dressed in a white suit took long strides and walked inside. Meanwhile, Red Nation’s Prince who wore a black, tight suit and a black coat followed him and entered as well.

“Brother Saber, you’ve become even more excessive…” Red Nation’s Prince covered his ears immediately after entering because he felt that his eardrums were numb from the vibrations of the rumbles of Garen’s breathing.

Both of them withstood the air currents to walk to Garen’s front before sitting down with some difficulty and steadying their figures.

The wind stopped immediately when Garen held his breath. Once his body had achieved this grade, holding his breath for a few hours was merely child’s play.

“Why have you come here? Haven’t you been very busy recently?” Garen asked casually.

He had been here for two months already. He had been waiting for the permission on Lighthouse’s part all this time to undo the limits of the virus. However, his physical fitness had undergone frightening increments that allowed him to reach an excessive degree whereby a mere breath was strong enough to send a person flying if he blew them.

On a random day when he accidentally used his nostrils to blow Nine-Tailed Fox away, he could not help but voluntarily seek Vulture No. 1’s help to find a large, specialized soundproofed house for him to stay. This prevented him from accidentally using his body that was constantly getting stronger to kill the people around him as if he was merely stomping on ants.

“How could we not come? We made a special trip to visit you once we finished our hectic task. Didn’t you say that you wanted to go? How is it? Have you finished preparing?” asked Vulture No. 1 directly. They had gotten along for two months without any conflicts of interest. The matters of life and death also allowed him to see many things in a clearer view. Moreover, he grew increasingly open-minded as well. Recently, he had successfully ended the matter with the previous leader with Garen’s support. He was moving towards the position of the first and leading figure in Slann now. If everything went as planned, he could establish a dynasty fully within these few months.

“It’s still alright.” Garen tried to speak as softly as possible but his voice still resembled thunder while the strong air currents that he exhaled caused both Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince’s clothes to overturn towards the back frenziedly. Large pools of his saliva pitter-pattered and sprayed everywhere.

“This is exaggerating…” said Prince dumbfoundedly. He wiped off the spit on his face. “Rumor has it that you can even spit and cover a person’s entire face in drops of saliva…”

“I can’t do anything about it…” said Garen helplessly. He was too strong and a lot of salivae would splatter and fly out whenever he was not careful. It simply resembled rain whenever he was speaking to someone else.

“What about Yuria? How is his situation?” Garen asked casually.

“That fellow has gone to the Black Federation and contacted his former subordinates. When he ran away from home in the beginning, he joined an organization that specialized in countering his father before it disbanded later. Hence, he’s gone to find his old friends now. Now that his sister’s gone while Garen is nothing to him and Light Path’s whereabouts are unknown, I won’t be willing to forgive him again even if I find him. He’s all alone now,” said Vulture No. 1 frankly. “As his master, you should hurry up and keep an eye on him.”

“Keep an eye on him? Everyone needs to experience these things. Isn’t growth only experienced through endurance?” Garen lifted his teacup and sipped it gently.

Shh!

The tea moved and disappeared instantly before the teacup shifted directly into his mouth.

This was due to the fact that his suction was too strong. It caused the tea to move too quickly as if it had teleported and could not be distinguished by the naked eye.

“I don’t think I can hang around here for more than a few days.” Once he had finished drinking his tea, Garen placed the cup down and slowly said, “Once I leave, please take care of Li Hua and the others. This is one of my requests.”

“No problem.” Vulture No. 1 lifted his own teacup and drank from it calmly despite being drenched from head to toe in Garen’s splattered spit. “Can you reveal where you’re planning to go?”

“You wouldn’t even know the place even if I told you,” Garen smiled. “You could say that it’s the depths of the universe.”

“Indeed, a freak like you would simply destroy the balance by living on this planet. I suspect that the current nuclear bombs would not be able to kill you in the explosion either,” said Red Nation’s Prince bluntly.

“Nonetheless, if you ever need some help, don’t forget that there are still two old fellows here who are indebted to your kindness.”

“I won’t forget that, of course.”

Garen briefly inquired about the most recent situation regarding the management of the virus as well as the other circumstances regarding the White Crab Organization. Everything had stabilized now.

Both nations had taken confrontational stances towards the Black Federation and would not lose to them. This allowed him to be at ease completely.

Everything in this world revolved around the rotations of the Four Great Cornerstones. The heavy curtains around the stage were fully opened for Yuria who was the first generation of the Four Great Cornerstones. Perhaps in another ten years or so when the second generation of the Four Great Cornerstones reappeared and walked on the international stage, everything would begin once again.

Nonetheless, that was not a problem that Garen needed to consider anymore.

He had absorbed two of the Soul Rings that belonged to the Four Great Cornerstones of this generation. If possible, he would probably return and absorb even more Soul Rings when the time came. However, these matters would only occur more than ten years later.

The Soul Rings were symbols that the energy of this universe would condense endlessly. After it was lost, the universe’s inexhaustible strength would replenish and condense it again. It was equivalent to the constant bearing of abundant fruits.

Since the Void Demon Lord Canster had already given him this world, Garen did not hold back and prepared to come and reap it once after a certain period of time. Nonetheless, before he did this, he would still want to go to Lighthouse first because he was already looking forward to visiting for a long time. He was not looking forward to Lighthouse itself but rather, the records inside Lighthouse that could provide him with Paramount Sources.

Some people referred to them as Paramount Sources while others called them Supreme Laws. However, the highest leveled powerhouses within Lighthouse purely recorded the things that they had seen and heard initially. That was the source of the Mother Stream and the spring of all life. More people referred to it as the Origin of the Mother Stream.

The Mother Stream was the strongest of the Thirteen Major Existences in the entire Countless Space-Time Universe. According to the sources of the records where it was stored, the Origin of the Mother Stream was a treasure that was sought after by innumerable Ancient Endorian systems.

Of course, reading the Origin of the Mother Stream required one million Contribution Points but Garen had a sufficient amount of them this time. To thank Garen for saving this world, Sea God and another person named Demonic Lamp had each transferred one million Contribution Points to him as compensation when they returned. They did this to show their gratitude when they heard that he wanted to see the Origin of the Mother Stream. After all, this world would truly be in danger if Garen had not been present.

Everything was ready and he only needed to wait for Lighthouse to finally lift the restriction order before he could leave.

He strengthened the bonds between himself, Vulture No. 1 and Red Nation’s Prince and set the tone properly to reap his future gains. Once both of them had left, another new group of visitors soon arrived.

It was not anybody but Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue who were planning to travel to Lighthouse with Garen.

Garen had attended the other Transmigrator’s appreciation banquet last month. He received odds and ends tens of thousands of Contribution Points which was better than nothing. He had already agreed to travel to Lighthouse with the other two people then.

However, when they came over this time, it was obvious that an additional person was hiding behind them.

“Night Water?” Garen looked at the little girl in black clothes who was hiding behind Nine-Tailed Fox.

“It’s me!” Night Water stood forward openly despite feeling slightly embarrassed. “As compensation for imprisoning me for such a long time, what do you think of taking me to Lighthouse with you?” she bargained with him.

“Weren’t you part of an organization?” Garen looked at the three people who had walked over and were now sitting on the opposite side of him, a few meters away.

“I left.”

“You mean you got kicked out,” said Kong Xinxue meanly. “Tsk tsk, poor child. You said you left when you were actually kicked out just for the sake of your pitiful self-esteem. Did you really think that your thoughts could be concealed so easily?”

“Is that any of your business?!” Night Water was slightly furious because of the embarrassment.

“Then why do you want to go with us?” Garen was not concerned about the minor incident that was related to Night Water’s previous group but merely asked the question randomly.

“Just tell me if you agree or not? After all, you’ve imprisoned me for such a long time and I’ve even helped you perform so many unspeakable tasks…” It was clear that Night Water planned to blame him.

Chapter 1244: Lighthouse 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Hey, isn’t this different from what we had decided on before we arrived?” asked Nine-Tailed Fox unhappily. “I know that you’re thinking of using Garen’s position of strength and rank to improve your own social status but you should still behave with a bit of integrity, right?”

“Integrity? Are you actually saying that I don’t have any integrity?!” Night Water yelled. “Do you know who frantically went back and forth to take care the both of you when the after-effects occurred after you fell into a coma suddenly? Do you know who was supporting the rear steadily when both of you left for White Crab Island and were risking your lives there? Do you know who had to risk being discovered to sneakily place the monitoring device in… Mmm!!”

Before Night Water could finish speaking, Nine-Tailed Fox covered her mouth without batting an eyelid, making it impossible for her to make any noises except mumble.

“Aren’t you guys annoying?! You have been yapping all day long just because of some trivial matters! Do you know how to empathize with other people’s feelings?! You were yapping yesterday and today! Don’t forget that I still have nude photos of both of you… Ahh!” Night Water lunged towards Kong Xinxue, causing her to fall down before Nine-Tailed Fox rushed over to help as well. The three of them wrestled into a chaotic and messy catfight.

“Enough!”

Garen raised his voice slightly.

Whoosh!!!

A gust of strong wind was accompanied by a torrent of rain submerged the trio completely.

The trio was soaked to the bones instantly as Garen’s saliva sprayed across their heads and faces.

Splash.

Nine-Tailed Fox wiped a handful of saliva off her face before using both hands to comb her damp sticky hair backward.

“Isn’t it comfortable now…”

“I know! Ptui ptui ptui ^1 !” Kong Xinxue jumped up from the ground. Her entire body was covered in Garen’s saliva.

Speaking of which, ever since Garen’s physical fitness became excessively powerful, his saliva secretions were also sufficiently strengthened. A random drop or sprinkle of his saliva could soak an entire person.

This was not the first time that this trio had experienced this situation.

“Hehehe… Luckily, I came prepared!” Night Water crawled up from the ground. The black tight-fitting clothing that covered her whole body seemed to be waterproof as large amounts of spit trickled down her body from the top. She became spotless once again. However, she had clearly overlooked the fact that her face and hair were still dripping.

The trio sat before Garen again. They were sitting upright despite their entire bodies being in a state of disorder. Moreover, the rising scent of the vaporizing saliva made them seem in an even worse off position.

“We came over this time with Night Water to proceed to Lighthouse together. That’s fine, right?” asked Nine-Tailed Fox formally. After all, it was obvious that Night Water and themselves wanted to go to Lighthouse together this time because they wanted to take advantage of Garen. Thus, they needed to seek his permission.

“It’s fine. Tell me the main matters.”

“From the information that I’ve received, Lighthouse should’ve lifted the restriction order long ago. However, there’s a huge difference on how to treat you,” said Nine-Tailed Fox quietly.

“Differences? What do you mean?” Garen was startled.

“Your powers have already reached the Suppressor’s level even though it’s merely human strength like ours. Thus, the forces of the three main clans in Lighthouse are consulting each other on how to arrange a position for you,” replied Nine-Tailed Fox.

“There are a total of three main clans in Lighthouse. Of course, these three clans are the most important. While there is obviously an abundance of other Transmigrator clans, their powers can be overlooked in comparison to these three main clans.”

“Who are the three main clans?”

Kong Xinxue took over the conversation and explained.

“The first one is the Many-Limbed Clan. Any races that have more than three limbs will be classified as part of the Many-Limbed Clan. The second one is the Many-Eyed Clan. It follows the same principle whereby those with three or more eyes will be determined as part of the Many-Eyed Clan. Our human race is next. All beings that possess human figures or forms will be classified as part of the human race. However, careful and strict classification has determined that our human race mainly consists of human earthlings, merpeople, and winged people that form three groups. As a newly discovered earthling who belongs to the same level as a Suppressor powerhouse, they need to discuss the actual position, attitude, and treatment that they’re willing to give you first. Next up are the attitude, position, and reply within the human race. Indeed, many years have passed without the appearance of a Suppressor level powerhouse.”

“Many years? How many years?” Garen was not interested in these struggles for influence but was focusing on other aspects instead.

“Perhaps about two to three thousand years. Lighthouse wasn’t established for a long time either and has only been around for about over ten thousand years. Only three Suppressors have appeared so far and they are the three highest-ranking individuals within the members association. They are Evil Shadow King, Strengthening Superhuman, and Pure Jade Clan King.”

“What about the other three?”

“The other three’s combat powers aren’t that great. However, they’re very useful and effective in other aspects such as the Worldly Tree of Knowledge Jules. He can give you the answer to almost any piece of knowledge you desire. He’s a superhuman old man who has lived for more than ten thousand years. He will hold classes spontaneously when he’s in the mood. Occasionally, he will sleep or doze off as five or six years pass,” explained Kong Xinxue.

“The inside of Lighthouse has been further divided into Wind Tower, Water Tower, and Spirit Tower. We’re in the territory of Water Tower. This is because the specialty of our race is water as more than fifty percent of our bodies are made up of water.”

“Are the others similar in that sense? Are half of the insides of their bodies made up of wind? Or spirits?” Garen continued asking.

“Yes, the Three Main Tower Territories are each used as the living areas of the Three Main Forces. However, powerful beings like yourself must usually be sealed up first before they are allowed to come out and meet others,” answered Nine-Tailed Fox while smiling.

“I understand…” nodded Garen knowingly. He currently felt that the difference between their grades had grown too far. Moreover, this situation had produced various inconveniences. He could not help blowing a person away if the tone of his voice was slightly too loud.

“So the three of you came together because the restriction order was lifted?” Garen asked casually.

“Yes, it has probably been lifted now after so much time has passed. However, regardless of the forces, at least your strength is powerful in comparison to the entire Transmigrator community. This is extremely good news because it means that they won’t neglect you but will spend to win you over instead,” replied Nine-Tailed Fox, smiling. “When the time comes, everything will be fine as long as there are no accidents.”

“When do we leave?” Garen took the communication device out. No one knew what this object was made of but its quality was unusually solid. The device had experienced numerous battles alongside Garen but was able to persevere without being damaged or breaking down at all. It was truly rare.

“Anytime.” Nine-Tailed Fox stood up.

“We’ll leave now then.” Garen got up before the two remaining people followed suit and stood up as well.

Nine-Tailed Fox nodded and took out her own communication device before tossing it in front gently.

“Open the Teleportation Point,” she said softly. “The largest scale.”

“The largest-scale requires the consumption of the highest level of Contribution Points, are you sure that you want to open it?” A melodious female voice echoed from the communication device.

“I’m sure,” answered Nine-Tailed Fox certainly.

Whoosh!

It moved at a rapid speed. Within the blink of an eye, a white Light Beam that resembled a line was projected from the bottom of the communication device directly.

The white Light Beam pulled itself open from both sides slowly like a folding door that was pulled into a semicircular white light door.

“You can go in now.” Nine-Tailed Fox nodded towards Garen. She finished speaking and took a long stride towards the light door.

A brief hissing noise could be heard when Nine-Tailed Fox’s entire body had just touched the light door before she disappeared completely.

Kong Xinxue took a step forward and caught up to her. She disappeared at the same time at the moment when she touched the light door.

Night Water cast her gaze towards Garen instead.

Garen smiled and walked towards the front of the light door.

He was finally about to leave this world and enter a larger universe and dimension.

His heart grew faintly exited. He was not merely going with the flow and rushing into a world and universe chaotically by trying his luck. Instead, he had chosen his own path to the greatest of his capabilities.

“I’ll go first then?” He looked at Night Water before she nodded.

Garen did not waste time and took a big step forward. However, the moment before he was about to touch the white light, he suddenly felt Night Water’s hand grabbing his arm.

Shh!!

The white light burst open before his eyes and made it impossible for him to see anything clearly at that moment.

**************************

Within the boundless, pitch-black spatial universe, a long stretch of the galaxy was flowing slowly. The countless celestial bodies resembled the most insignificant grains of river sand in the galaxy.

These hundred billion celestial bodies finally formed this entire vast beautiful blue galaxy.

The galaxy moved slowly like the most magnificent whirlpool of flowing water while an imposing white lighthouse stood upright in the center.

The cylindrical white lighthouse stood tall in the center of the galaxy coincidentally while three blinding golden light pillars were projected from the top of the lighthouse. These light pillars penetrated the entire galaxy and illuminated the exterior of the boundless jet-black universe.

It seemed as though these three light pillars were completely motionless. However, if someone could measure the speed of the light pillar extremely accurately, they would discover that these light pillars would occasionally move towards other directions at a slow pace.

Nonetheless, throughout the distance of this vast galaxy that spanned across countless light-years, the speed of the light pillar’s movements appeared to be abnormally slow.

The interior of this white lighthouse was divided into a total of five floors. The highest floor was the control floor that controlled the operations throughout the entire lighthouse while the bottom included two floors of halls which were the High Hall and an observation hall.

The bottom of this lighthouse consisted of the important dwelling areas. The two other layers included the circular plaza and the library area.

The circular plaza was currently bordering the examination area. Within the largest Teleportation Linking Point, Garen appeared at the linking point suddenly with Night Water still holding on to his arm. Faint halos of white light were being released by the side of their bodies slowly.

The white shades before Garen’s eyes faded slowly as he regained his sight quickly. More than ten smiling white-robed people entered his line of sight and welcomed him.

“Welcome to Lighthouse, my dear clan member!” said the leading white-haired man loudly while stretching his arms open. “Sword Master Garen, we’ve heard about your great strength all the way from our headquarters. We’re ready to welcome you to formally join us any time.”

He walked over and extended his hand.

Garen reached his hand out as well before the both of them shook hands gently.

“I’m very glad to be able to come to Lighthouse formally as well.”

Garen surveyed his surroundings. He was currently standing inside a white cylindrical pavilion. There were rows of various white stone pillars beside him that were each larger than the previous one when you approached them from afar. Each of these stone pillars surrounded pavilions of various sizes. It appeared that they were used to teleport and transport Transmigrators of different physical sizes.

The vast blue galaxy was above his head while the white jade colored solid stone floor was below his feet.

“My name is Pera and I’m the main person in charge of the humans here. Our leader Pure Jade Clan King has already given orders regarding your matters beforehand. He will definitely entertain you properly and will meet you personally immediately after returning. The old man is currently handling the sect’s important matters in the local world and is too busy to attend to you for now,” explained Pera while glancing obviously at Night Water, Nine-Tailed Fox, and Kong Xinxue who were standing beside Garen.

There were all beautiful women. His heart knew exactly what it wanted immediately.

As the headquarters of the Transmigrators, Lighthouse naturally possessed beneficial relationships on the inside as well. Places with intelligent creatures would have clashes of interest and could never be that pure. Moreover, the division of profit would naturally be related to the closeness between the strengths and forces.

“I’ll take you to the resting area that has been arranged already. After that, what would you say if I brought you to visit the various areas briefly?” said Pera while smiling. The other people behind him had friendly smiles on their faces as well. However, they were not forced smiles but were smiles that evolved from the heart instead. It was obvious that Garen’s arrival could produce real benefits and advantages to them.

“There’s no need. We’ll take Garen to visit around the area.” Without waiting for Garen to answer, Kong Xinxue stepped forward voluntarily and spoke. She was not an idiot. When she saw Pera coming forward to receive him personally despite being someone whose face she had never even seen once on a normal day, she immediately understood that Garen’s position of strength was perhaps higher than her expectations.

She was not an idiot. If she acted as if she was slightly closer to Garen now and borrowed some of his influence, her life would become much better in a place like Lighthouse where everything depended on power.

Chapter 1245: Origin of the Mother Stream 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“That’s fine as well.” Pera glanced at Garen knowingly. “Cocosher.”

A blonde girl with a tall slender body and charming features who was dressed in a black, tight-fitting silk mini skirt walked out behind him immediately.

“Inform the rest to place the portraits of His Excellency the Sword Master in the various departments with the permission to pass through.”

“Understood.”

The golden-haired woman nodded in response.

“So would you like to have a meal now first?”

Pera smiled while looking at Garen.

“That won’t be necessary. However, I only have two wishes.” Garen lifted two of his fingers.

“Firstly, I’d like to examine and inquire about the situation on Earth before we transmigrate. Is there any way to find out about the whole situation regarding the status of Earth?

“Secondly, in regards to viewing the records of the Origin of the Mother Stream, my Contribution Points are most probably sufficient.”

“Regarding these two questions,” Pera smiled, “I think that it’d be better for us to talk while we walk.”

Pera and ten other people clustered around Garen and the three other girls who were in the center. The group walked towards the interior of Lighthouse slowly along the Starry Sky Sword Bridge.

This was a long strip-like sword bridge that appeared outdoors in the star-studded sky. It resembled a sharp blade that poked straight out of the side of the lighthouse. The top of the bridge was filled with densely-packed Teleportation Linking Point. This place was directly connected to the circular plaza area on the third floor.

As Garen was clustered to walk in the middle, he could occasionally see rays of white light behind him that came from the new people who were being teleported back.

Meanwhile, Pera introduced the fundamentals of the area to him.

“There aren’t many people who are living in the Lighthouse headquarters here because the Transmigrators only occupy one percent of the population. The majority are personnel who stayed back to manage the place while most of the others would rather live in the Plots of worlds that were slightly more peaceful. You understand as well that in many worlds excluding the places in where the Plot is occurring, the other areas are actually very safe because the locations that are involved are not vast.”

“I can understand that.” Garen nodded. “So how are these worlds classified?”

“Classified? No, that’s not quite right. Every world belongs to a universe that contains a myriad of planetary worlds. We don’t have any way of fully probing or determining the true situation of the universe through elimination. The only thing that we can do is contact our companions that have transmigrated and incarnated in different worlds or universes. We can all contact each other to form an organization that provides services that led to mutual benefits. Simultaneously, we can also engage in the trade and optimization of resources.”

Pera smiled and continued. “For instance, Dark Colored Gold isn’t valuable in worlds where they are present because they can be found anywhere and you can obtain a large amount just by grabbing it randomly. However, Dark Colored Gold possesses unimaginably terrifying magic in the worlds where it is present. Hence, they’re a first-rate resource that everyone yearns for even in their dreams. Therefore, we transfer between worlds to conduct reasonable allocation of these resources. This allows us to promote everyone’s development further to obtain an even greater influence throughout the various worlds.”

“I understand what you mean.” Garen nodded. “What about Earth? Since we have so many Transmigrators from Earth, even if everyone’s homes were in different dimensions on Earth that were in parallel spaces, someone would’ve surely engaged in the exploration of this aspect, right? What was the conclusion?”

Pera furrowed his eyebrows slightly when this matter was brought up.

“We’ve always been working hard in this aspect but so far, it seems like we can’t even touch the edges because the distance between us and earth is too far. On the other hand, we’ve discovered numerous similar planets in other universes. These were the additional benefits as some of these planets are very unique. You should visit these places if you have the chance in the future.”

“In other words, you still don’t have any clues regarding Earth?” asked Garen directly.

“You could say that,” Pera exhaled then sighed. “Many of our companions who yearn to return are truly looking for a possible way to go back. However, we currently don’t see any rays of hope from the looks of it. This doesn’t apply to the human earthlings like us only. Many people in the other two clans have the same sentiments but none of them have discovered a path to return yet.”

The group walked through the entrance of the circular plaza and entered it.

They stood on a suspended silver platform that resembled a parallelogram. The platform that was made of metal silently pulled more than ten people through a purple round-arched tunnel.

Pfoo…

A few rainbow-like Airstreams that were overflowing with vibrant colors gradually appeared in their surroundings. These fine, continuous thread-like things revolved and flew around everyone.

“These are Rainbow Elves. We discovered them in a unique universe. They’re considered as a species of microorganism that can purify the air while constantly emitting beneficial magnetic fields that are healthy for us humans. Moreover, they also serve as landscaping ornaments in the city,” explained Pera.

“It’s very beautiful.”

Garen lifted his head and glanced at the translucent, multi-colored Elves that resembled flowing water in the tunnel. They did not look physical but presented a faint illusory impression instead.

Garen reached his hand out and caught the Rainbow Elves beside him gently but could not feel anything substantial.

Pera smiled at this sight.

“Speaking of these increment creatures, the Origin of the Mother Stream, which is also your main goal of coming here this time, had recorded the existence of a being that is of an even higher level than the Rainbow Elves. They seem like pure energy bodies so we’ve named them the Elementals. Perhaps you will gain some things when viewing through the records.”

“I hope so.” Garen smiled and nodded.

“The Origin of the Mother Stream that is a part of the Mother Stream System belongs to a section of the first-rate records that require middle-ranking viewing rights. Regarding the viewing rights, I don’t know whether you’re acquainted in this aspect?” asked Cocosher quietly while standing beside Pera.

“Cocosher’s other identity is of a service person who manages the High Hall. Therefore, she’s more qualified in that aspect than me,” Pera explained while smiling.

Garen shifted his gaze towards the beautiful blonde woman who was dressed in black silk.

“Viewing rights?”

“You still need viewing rights to just look at something?” asked Kong Xinxue, puzzled.

“Don’t tell me that the quantity of the information here is so great that everything has become jumbled, causing most people to be unable to accept the effects of the information overload at one go?” This assumption made it more obvious that Nine-Tailed Fox was more experienced and knowledgeable.

“This is one aspect,” said Cocosher, nodding. “The main issue is that the Origin of the Mother Stream is constantly releasing powerful radioactive rays. We only have one thing to filter these unique radioactive rays to turn them into protective shields that allow people to view them head-on. Otherwise, when we’re unable to proceed with sheltering it, regardless of the greatness of your own power, there’s a probability that you will instantly suffer Soul Beckoning and be drawn into the Origin of the Mother Stream directly.”

“Soul Beckoning?!” yelled Night Water in a slightly shocked manner. As she was also a powerhouse of the Mother Stream System, she was naturally clearly aware of the number of evil ways that existed within these playthings. “The Mother Stream is the source of all life. Therefore, anything that possesses a soul cannot withstand her Soul Beckoning at all! Isn’t this just asking for death? No wonder it’s so expensive!”

Garen knew about this Soul Beckoning as well.

It was as if the Mother Stream was the positive pole of a gigantic magnet while the Soul Beckoning seemed to be the opposite side that also resembled the tiny weak negative pole of a magnet. In other words, viewing the Origin of the Mother Stream was like drawing the distance between these two magnets closer to achieve a stage where it could be felt that they were both pulling each other.

He had heard Black Sethe mentioned this before. It was a first-rate True Soul killing move that existed in Ancient Endor. It had previously instantly destroyed two large armies of Void Creatures and three Demon Lord level powerhouses. It was worthy of being called invincible!

The position of this Soul Beckoning move in the Ancient Endorian civilizations was simply equivalent to super strategic weapons in the civilizations on Earth such as nuclear bombs and hydrogen bombs. They were considered as first-rate mass weapons of destruction.

“Lighthouse actually possesses the materials and resources to counter the Soul Beckoning? That’s truly unimaginable!” Garen sighed with sincere emotion.

“This is another benefit of converging with many other worlds and being entrusted with their resources,” Pera explained. “There’s a world that’s purely a soul world that is abundant with materials that are specially used to counter the traction of souls. We’ve also exhausted a great deal of effort to merely create a tiny amount of it that is only sufficient to be seen once by a single person. Moreover, it can only be seen for ten minutes. Otherwise, even if the resistance of these materials are weakened, that power will still cause living creatures to lose their minds and throw themselves into it voluntarily.”

The group had just entered a gigantic white plaza. The surroundings of this plaza were round while the ceiling above their heads was not the white sky that they had imagined. Instead, it was a cerulean sky filled with white clouds and an additional little golden sun that was hanging there quietly. It seemed as though they had truly entered a whole new world.

“We’ve entered the initial part of the plaza here. If you walk forward from here, there’s a large stretch of land below with an area that is almost equivalent to half the size of the planet that you arrived from earlier, except that its surface area is measured by spreading it out completely. The entire circular plaza refers to this whole area of land,” said Pera while smiling. “Welcome to the third level of Lighthouse.”

He snapped his fingers before the silver platform that was supporting the group accelerated suddenly. It flew quickly and passed this small-scale plaza before arriving at the edges of the said plaza.

The borders of this entire plaza were actually suspended in mid-air while this place was situated in high altitude skies. When they looked down, they could see the terrain of a long stretch of rugged uneven mountainous grounds, lush green forests, and a silver flowing river that resembled a ribbon. There were also flocks of wild geese that flew below them frequently. This was basically another living world.

Garen walked towards the edge and looked down. They were currently situated in the utmost point of high altitude. They were at a height of at least a few thousand meters while the ground below them resembled an exquisite and fine site model.

He looked towards the faraway distance on his front-right side. There was a long stretch of white area that seemed to be a cluster of many buildings there.

“The trade section of the plaza is located there where a myriad of items are sold inside. Transmigrators aren’t allowed to kill each other but other than that, this place permits any meaningful fights as long as no lives are taken,” said Pera while standing next to Garen.

Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue stopped Cocosher who was trying to catch up to Garen on the other side. They asked her random questions and found conversation topics even when there were none. They were obviously trying to prevent her from getting too close to Garen.

Garen had no time to pay attention to their insignificant thoughts now. He was observing the white trading section below from afar.

“So where should I go if I want to view the Origin of the Mother Stream?” The trade section was not that important to him. Other than those with the Transmigrator status, the other people here did not share any similarities with him or provide him with a sense of belonging. As for the rare and strange energy systems, they were insanely suppressed when they arrived in the communal universe here. Although they were not as overpowered as the Four Great Cornerstones, they were considered to be extremely vicious in comparison to most of the other worlds.

Garen’s current power grade had already barely restored itself to the Planetary Level now. He could influence the grades that were on the levels that could balance planets. It was stronger than the world of the Four Great Cornerstones but much weaker than the Mech World.

“The Origin of the Mother Stream is one of the thirteen main sources of records. Since you must go to the High Hall which isn’t on this floor, we’ll take you to your dwelling place first. You can proceed to the High Hall anytime by either teleportation or fly there on your own,” answered Pera.

The group simply used the silver platform as support before flying off the plaza and soaring speedily to the bottom. Along the way, Garen constantly asked about the various situations here before he gained a certain understanding towards almost the entire layout and distribution of Lighthouse. This place no longer gave off the atmosphere of good friends helping each other. Instead, it was a place that was flooded with disputes and the bartering of benefits. No wonder Kong Xinxue and Nine-Tailed Fox were unwilling to return here and settle down. It was not surprising that many other people were more willing to hide in different worlds to live their own lives.

While he spoke to Pera along the way about certain major events and situations that occurred on Earth previously, Garen was certain that the other party did not originate from the same Earth as himself at all. It seemed as though Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue did not transmigrate from the same Earth as him either. Instead, it seemed like they came from certain parallel spaces that were branched out in history.

This declined his interest slightly.

After flying to a silver palace-like place among the mountains, Pera gave Garen a key. The entire territory that spanned a few hundred square kilometers was now Garen’s domain.

Chapter 1246: Origin of the Mother Stream 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Although our surroundings are all wild mountainous areas, I believe that as long as you live here, there will be people who follow suit quickly,” Pera smiled while speaking. “The powerhouses who belong to the level of the Suppressors can befriend others easily even if they have minor flaws. Whether you’re looking at the aspect of exchanging resources or close protection, as long as you have the support of a mainstay powerhouse, you can’t be more secure than that.” He gazed at Nine-Tailed Fox and the other two women profoundly when he said this.

“What are you looking at? We’re indeed planning to stay near Garen but it’s not for that reason!” Nine-Tailed Fox remained silent but Kong Xinxue piped up arrogantly instead.

Pera paid her no mind. However, he was not the only one gazing at the three women as the members of the accompanying entourage around him were looking on in a faintly dubious manner as well.

“Your Excellency the Sword Master, do you require any slaves? There are members of the local Kachusha clan who have reproduced here, and their physical appearance and features are similar to us humans. Although their IQ is slightly lower, they naturally possess loyal personalities and can be considered as a pretty good breeding race.”

“It doesn’t matter, I don’t think that I’ll be staying here for long.” Garen shook his head and declined. The threat of the Depletion of the Mother Stream made him feel an unprecedented sense of urgency. Perhaps viewing the Origin of the Mother Stream would help him. However, he had to know everything fairly well before he could discover what type of path he would thread on in the future.

“Is that so? That’s truly a shame,” said Pera sympathetically. The silver platform descended slowly before Garen and the others walked off and stood before the doorway of a silver palace that was shaped like the top of an onion. He turned back to look at Pera and the others.

“Thank you very much for arranging everything. Please thank Pure Jade Clan King for me. We’ll definitely have a drink together in his free-time when he returns,” said Garen in a casual but polite manner. The other party’s alias clearly indicated that he came from the Immortal Hero World. Therefore, it was traditionally not seen as a taboo for them to drink alcohol together to display gratitude.

“I will surely relay this message.” Pera cupped his hands in salute. “Cocosher will live near you as well so you can seek for her directly if you have any questions or require anything. I’ll take my leave now.”

The platform soared into the sky, taking Pera and the others away before leaving into the distance.

Garen glanced around his surroundings. There were vast stretches of pine trees, and pine needles and nuts covered the ground in thick layers. A few squirrels scurried around, unafraid of people at all. Occasionally, a squirrel that was holding a pine nut would crouch on the ground and stare at Garen and the others blankly.

“Your Excellency?”

Cocosher walked beside Garen and whispered, “There are more than a thousand rooms in the palace. Would you permit the three others and me to live here with you?”

Garen returned to his senses.

“I’ll allow it. You can arrange everything on your own because I might not be staying here for long.”

After experiencing the manner of Lighthouse, his mood was not as excited as he had imagined before.

The Depletion of the Mother Stream would not only result in the discontinuation of his future. Additionally, other related phenomena would probably appear as well. The thing that he was most concerned about now was not his dwelling place in Lighthouse but the issue of finding his own goal and way out instead.

As Transmigrators, they would constantly encounter endless rebirths and reincarnations. This was a type of passive process. If they were unable to grasp this process smoothly or extend each of their lives to the best of their abilities to improve their own souls, the Transmigrators would gradually lose their previous memories as time passed and the number of their reincarnations increased. Moreover, they would also gradually lose more of their Soul Energy to the point where it would be rinsed out completely and transformed into countless nutrients in the universe that would disappear in time and space.

“What methods must I use to achieve eternity? Those who are powerful enough to reach the True Soul level aren’t spared from the threat of encountering depletion.” Garen pondered deeply.

It was because of him feeling insecure initially that got him to thread on the path of martial arts. However, these feelings weakened and disappeared after a period of time. Unfortunately, now with the news of the Depletion of the Mother Stream, these insecure feelings resurfaced once again.

He did not know why he wanted to proceed forward continuously. However, he felt that constantly strengthening his own body would temporarily fill the hole in the depths of his heart that was left by these uneasy feelings.

This normal-looking palace named Sword Master Palace was finally established near the third level of the circular plaza’s trade section.

There were only a few people who knew about this. The news agencies sent beautiful women to try and interview Garen. Unfortunately, they discovered that the main door was tightly sealed and no one responded even when they tried to announce themselves to gain entry. Hence, they were forced to leave with nothing.

Information on Garen’s origins was trending within Lighthouse for a few days before it was immediately brushed aside by other gossip news regarding the other Suppressors.

As time passed, the number of guests who came to visit Garen increased greatly.

Nine-Tailed Fox and Kong Xinxue kept to their words. After staying here for a few days, they went to the fourth level where the library section was located before they found jobs as managers there.

Garen had visited the fourth level once as well. The library section kept books of various power systems that were all very rudimentary. They were nothing but the most basic methods of operation for the various laws of the universe. As a first-rate martial artist, he already possessed a realm of his personal experiences that also stemmed from the Slayer’s diverse killing moves and close combat techniques. His great comprehension of a good deal of strength experiences allowed him to easily abandon a few paths that were connected to the books in the library.

After all, they merely served as popular items that were used to satisfy and guide many people who had recently transmigrated. The library section mostly sold various functional objects that could only be used once. Meanwhile, the information in the library was mainly used by the people who used communication devices to engage in long-range remote-controlling between various worlds.

Garen glanced through the information but was ultimately uninterested. His grade was too high now while these things were overly shallow. They were of no help to him at all.

They served no purpose except for increasing his reading experiences somewhat.

Kong Xinxue and Nine-Tailed Fox left quickly because they were merely here to take advantage of him. Nonetheless, they could contact Garen anytime because they had already exchanged their contact details with him.

Meanwhile, Night Water obtained mid-level authority after taking advantage of Garen’s position and using her powerful connections to intimidate others in the library section. Since she could view mid-level information regarding strength systems now, she moved out happily after vowing solemnly to Garen that they were both even now because the debts between them were reasonably paid off. Not long after, she found herself a boyfriend with wings on his back.

Only Cocosher stayed. It was clear that this woman had impure motives because she took care of Garen every day as if she was his wife. She was clearly planning to keep a tight grip on such a good catch.

She managed most of the tasks inside the palace.

Meanwhile, Garen had a constant stream of visitors. He attempted to find a companion that came from the same Earth as himself among these Transmigrators. Unfortunately, he could not find one as none of the Transmigrators had even heard of a scenario where two of them originated from the same place.

The parallel space was too vast. As numerous Transmigrators from earth had converged here, the probability of finding one who coincidentally came from the same place as he was as likely as getting smashed by a meteor when he was walking on the street.

Other than humans, there were also other races among the visitors. The powerhouses from the Many-Eyed Clan and Many-Limbed Clan who came to visit him where also from the same Mother Stream System as Garen.

Garen put on a welcoming face when he was visited by guests of the same race as himself. After the initial contact, he understood the powerhouses of the Mother Stream System within Lighthouse even more.

None of them were of the Demon Lord Level.

There were two people who belonged to the Army Level. After that, most of them were in the General Level followed by the Division Level and Guardian Level. Although there were only a few of the last two in Lighthouse, their base numbers in the various worlds were very high. It was also impossible to calculate the specific quantity. However, since many people had embellished their Mother Stream Systems, it was difficult to make a distinction.

These powerhouses came forward to ask for guidance humbly when they discovered that Garen belonged to the Demon Lord Level of the Mother Stream System. Those in the General Level asked him to teach them how to break through to the Army Level, while those in the Army Level sought guidance on how to break through to the Demon Lord Level.

The path of the Mother Stream System was actually very simple. Those who had achieved the Demon Lord Level and obtained the foundation of their own Soul Rings could upgrade their Soul Ring through plundering. Previously, they would only be at that stage where they could solidify their foundations. As their foundations grew stronger, it would become more likely for them to absorb and plunder the Soul Rings of others in the Demon Lord Level. However, Garen was different. As the properties of his own Soul Ring carried devouring abilities, the probability of his absorption was many times higher than the others in the Demon Lord Level. Unfortunately, his other abilities were unlike many of the other Demon Lords.

He was reflecting on the Army-Level individual in the Many-Eyed Clan.

There were many Demon Lords who possessed extremely powerful annihilation-type destruction abilities. Some of them were special abilities such as super long-range attacks like Black Sethe’s previous near-death effect that could dull all creatures. However, Garen’s abilities were unusually normal. The only Devour ability that he possessed did not include increment effects. Hence, his actual combat was truly weaker than some of the other Demon Lords in the same situation.

Garen had discovered this point on his own.

In the world of the Four Great Cornerstones, he had always been suppressing his opponents with his Soul Ring Energy and standing on the advantageous side.

However, when he was really about to encounter the Slayer, he would discover that his opponent’s abilities were extremely overpowered and one of his Soul Rings could be countered with many of his enemy’s own. This was the true difference in strength between them.

Garen decided to proceed with viewing the Origin of the Mother Stream after experiencing the initial stages of Lighthouse and understanding them fully.

Other than the Thirteen Ultimate Origins, there was nothing else here that could help him.

*******************

“The Origin of the Mother Stream, huh… Those are the supreme and paramount sources of recorded information. I had previously accumulated a lot of Contribution Points over a long period of them to view that information once,” discussed Hawthorn of the Many-Eyed Clan who was sitting on the opposite side of Garen. “It’s unfortunate that I could not remember anything other than a stretch of light. I could only feel as if something was constantly beckoning me kindly. It was asking if I wanted to stop concerning myself with anything else and break through all of my restraints to cast myself there.”

Hawthorn’s name was not actually Hawthorn. Garen had merely given him this nickname because the pronunciation of his name was very similar to the Chinese hawthorn fruit. As an Army Level powerhouse of the Mother Stream, Hawthorn and Garen could be considered as kindred spirits. He came over frequently to discuss the news of Ancient Endor and Void Creatures with Garen. He had taken great pains to establish a large army of thirteen General Levels, fifty-two Division Levels, and a few thousand Guardian Levels. They were all clan members who had followed him each step of the way and grown together as a family. Therefore, he was much better than Garen in terms of gathering information.

“What happened after that?” Garen was playing a game of chess on his own. He used both his left and right hands to play while listening carefully.

“I woke up after that. I wasted one million Contribution Points without gaining a single thing.” The six eyes on Hawthorn’s head blinked helplessly in synchronization. His eyes were formed in a particular manner. There were two straight lines on both sides of his face with three eyes on each side that descended in size from the top to the bottom. They blinked of pale green light.

“Later, I inferred that it was very likely that my Soul Seed wasn’t strong enough. Thus, it was overly affected by the Soul Beckoning which made it fully impossible for it to be free enough to detect other things. Hence, you should probably be much stronger than us before you proceed to view the records.”

“Have you understood the situation with the Void Creatures slightly better?” asked Garen while changing the subject.

“A little bit. We’re currently worried about the Depletion of the Mother Stream. However, there are probably at least over ten thousand years between now and the Depletion of the Mother Stream. It is completely unnecessary for us to worry about these things so early on because the True Souls would never just sit and wait for death. When the time comes, the things that are completely impossible will be transformed into things that can be done.” Hawthorn disapproved of Garen’s worries. “Rumor has it that they’ve established six associates. One of my friends came looking for me a while ago in hopes that I could contact a few of the Ancient Endorian important figures. I told him frankly that after being mixed up in this for so many years, you are the only Demon Lord Level Warlock that I’ve encountered, Brother Saber. I haven’t seen any others. Ancient Endor has declined for far too long.”

“It has been impossible for the Mother Stream’s Oath to restrain us as well. You can see that it’s already very likely the Depletion of the Mother Stream is right in front of us. After a span of more than ten thousand years, I’m also suspicious that the mist that is being released at the Void Creatures’ area shows that there isn’t much time left,” said Garen while furrowing his eyebrows.

“If you look at it that way, it’s true that this is very likely…” Hawthorn nodded in agreement.

Both of them were speechless for a while as the current situation had changed.

The Void Empire had found three Demon Lords of higher grades to act as their associated representatives. However, the Ancient Endorian side could not even find one because their civilization had dulled long ago. Hawthorn had said that they could rebuild themselves but once the Ancient Endorian souls had formed Soul Seeds, there would be no leeway to backtrack anymore. This was because the Soul Seeds were the condensed bodies of all life forms and their Soul Wills. Once they were abandoned, they could only release Soul Seeds. Therefore, the best possibility was to lose all of their reincarnated memories. If they were slightly unfortunate, their bodies and souls would decay fully before they were turned into nourishment for the universe.

“I don’t know the exact implications of the Origins of the Mother Stream’s Soul Beckoning. However, my instincts from the Kabida Clan that I come from is telling me that the biggest secret regarding the soul of the Mother Stream is probably hidden there,” sighed Hawthorn.

“Is that why you exhausted all your efforts and put yourself and your family on the line initially?” laughed Garen.

“Yes, I owed a huge amount of debts in the end and didn’t even gain anything. I walked out while my mind was still entirely blank,” said Hawthorn helplessly.

“I’m going to the High Hall tomorrow. I’ve already submitted a request today in advance so that I can go there later. A certain amount of time is required beforehand for the preparatory work there,” Garen said indifferently.

“I can only wish you good luck then.” It was clear that Hawthorn did not think highly of Garen.

Chapter 1247: Black Hole 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Good luck?” Garen laughed. “Good luck won’t be enough…”

Since all of the powerhouses of the Mother Stream System were the most direct influences of the Depletion of the Mother Stream, their life forces would gradually become exhausted as well. If they could not find a way to change it before the Depletion began, every single creature in the Mother Stream and the powerhouses who directly or indirectly depended on the Mother Stream to survive would face the threat of their life forces being severed.

“A Soul Seed forms a Soul Ring, the Soul Ring produces Soul Energy and the cycle begins again. These processes are actually supported by the laws of the Mother Stream. Therefore, once these laws disappear, all of the Soul Rings will collapse completely while the components of the Soul Seed will be destroyed as well. When that happens, none of the Soul Seeds will exist anymore. In other words, the rest of us including me will be completely reduced to normal people,” said Garen softly.

“Perhaps this is still a good thing.” Hawthorn of the Many-Eyed Clan lifted the cup of tea before him and drank a mouthful of it. “Great risks also bring great rewards. If we can make ourselves aware of the process that is released and produced by the Origin when the Mother Stream collapses, we’ll have a chance to realize the core rules of Space-Time.”

“So what? Even if we do realize it, it won’t be very useful once the Mother Stream and the greatest aggregate of rules collapse.” Garen shook his head.

Hawthorn chuckled.

“That’s uncertain. Don’t forget that there are thirteen Space-Time Origins and the Mother Stream is only one of them. We can blend in pretty well in other places by becoming aware of a few core laws.”

“You have a point.” Garen was speechless.

“I was merely just throwing thoughts around from the beginning.” Hawthorn shrugged. Suddenly, a little object that he wore on his ear made a brief beeping noise.

“Alright, my time is up. I still have a bunch of things to sort out. I wish you all the best and hope that everything goes well tomorrow.”

He stood up.

“Don’t worry.” Garen nodded while smiling.

He watched on as Hawthorn left.

Garen placed a chess piece down, his right hand finally checkmate his left.

He laughed quietly and shook his head lightly.

Ever since he had reincarnated from Earth, it seemed as though he was traveling forward without stopping. He had formed four Soul Ring Demon Lords and belonged to the middle grade of the Demon Lord Level.

These four Soul Rings could forcibly upgrade themselves by four grades when they were situated in the peak levels of strength in the world. This was an incomparably terrifying increment. It also represented the overly frightening powers of the middle-grade Demon Lords.

Meanwhile, the high-grade Demon Lords were naturally more amazing. The colors of their Soul Rings ranged from being colorless to the rainbow’s seven colors of red, orange, yellow, green, blue, indigo, and violet. All of the Soul Rings had to be achieved and condensed according to the arrangement of these seven colors. An individual could only be bestowed the title of the high-grade Demon Lord once they had obtained a total of eight Soul Rings that consisted of the aforementioned seven colors and the colorless one.

It was rumored that people who had obtained at least seven colors would have achieved the True Soul grade. Currently, although Garen could clearly feel that he had four Soul Rings of his own, they were still extremely unstable. After all, the first Soul Seed was the only one that had come to realization painstakingly while the rest were forcibly snatched and devoured by him.

“In other words, I’m merely a middle-grade Demon Lord on the surface now. In reality, my explosive powers are probably only at the lower grades of the Demon Lord Level.” Garen shook his head.

“My Soul Rings aren’t stable enough yet and I had barely achieved the Colorless grade. I shouldn’t even think of obtaining the colors after the Colorless grade because I don’t know how long it will take to achieve these stages,” sighed Garen. He closed his eyes, adjusting his state of mind with great concentration to prepare to view the Origin of the Mother Stream tomorrow.

********************

Garen’s arrival did not cause any great changes because he merely lived quietly in seclusion. Despite being a Planetary Level source of combat strength, he did not seem to care about extravagance or servants.

The forces of the three main clans noticed his lack of participation and attitude that seemed to be ignorant of everything else. Hence, they naturally and discreetly acted as if he was nonexistent because he did not participate in matters that involved scrambling for benefits.

Although powerhouses were not lacking in places like Lighthouse, Garen was still the strongest one among them. He went to view the Origin of the Mother Stream within a few days of being released. When all of the influential emissaries gained knowledge of this external information at the same time, these forces temporarily gave up on drawing Garen over to their side.

Garen woke up extremely early the next day. The color of the simulated sky was operating according to the natural patterns completely and it happened to be seven o’clock in the morning. He had prepared everything properly before proceeding towards the linking area in the circular plaza.

Cocosher had made arrangements for one of the specialized transportation boards for him here. It was the same flying board that they had used when they came here directly.

Garen allowed Cocosher to remain in the house while he rode the flying board to the linking area alone. The little pavilion began to transport him there directly.

Large amounts of white snowflake-like objects swayed before his eyes constantly. This teleportation process lasted for more than ten minutes.

Garen finally felt both of his feet sink.

“You’ve arrived.”

A deep male voice echoed beside his ears.

Garen’s eyes brightened before him.

When he opened his eyes, he realized that he was standing inside a white, round hall. He was currently standing on the centermost area. A bald black man who wore a gold stud earring was standing before him.

“I’ve received the notifications, Lord Sword Master. Everything has been arranged for you so please come with me.” The bald black man wore a pure white, long robe and spoke to Garen softly politely.

“Thank you for your trouble,” Garen replied briefly in an equally polite manner.

“You’re welcome. These are our daily tasks.” The black man smiled, revealing his snowy-white teeth.

However, Garen was currently not in the mood to observe him now. Instead, he observed his surrounding environment carefully.

He walked out of the Teleportation Point with the black man and pushed open a little door on the left. They passed through a narrow and dark corridor before arriving in a little white stone pavilion that was neither big nor small.

It seemed as though one side of the little pavilion was see-through. A transparent glass was placed over it in one direction. The bright, starry sky that was moving slowly outside could be seen through the glass.

“This is where the Mother Stream is positioned in the High Hall. One of our powerful seniors had previously experienced life-and-death situations to record the information regarding the Origin of the Mother Stream here. The glass here is actually used to ward off the negative side effects that were brought on by the vast information. However, please don’t worry because there will definitely be no hindrances towards your realization process,” explained the black man softly.

“Once I close the door, the records will begin to be released in about ten minutes. Please prepare yourself. The total sustained time is calculated based on your own achievements. Although we don’t know the principles behind the mechanisms of the calculations, we’ve noticed that important figures with greater power tend to have longer sustained viewing times. They can even last up to three days at times.”

“How long does it usually last?” asked Garen.

“About ten minutes. This is the usual continuous state,” explained the black man patiently. “The handle inside this other room can be used to turn on the alarm. You can notify us immediately if you encounter any dangerous situations. We will turn off the transmission at that first instance and proceed to rescue you. This button is used when you require food or drinks while this button is used when you require particular items. Meanwhile, this is used when you require a particular person with special talents to coordinate with…”

He began talking nonstop while introducing each of the functions inside the room in the small pavilion.

Garen listened casually but his thoughts had somewhat shifted towards the walls of the room. Faint shrouds of Soul Energy Aura were constantly permeating throughout the room in the white pavilion.

“No… It’s not pure Soul Energy. Instead, it’s a type of fused Soul Energy that is closer to an actual Aura. The water in the Mother Stream is made up of countless substantial Auras that were liquefied. Could it be that Soul Energy that is fused with Auras will finally turn into a power source of an even higher grade?”

This assumption drifted in his mind secretly.

“… So that is it, we will take one million points from your account as the viewing expenses if you have no other requests. May I ask if you would like to view it immediately?” The black man’s voice echoed, pulling Garen back out from his thoughts.

He scanned his surroundings. There were faint scratches on the walls. There were even a few tiny holes that seemed as if they were created when a person went mad and scratched the walls crazily. It was clear that viewing the Origin of the Mother Stream could produce some unimaginable phenomenon.

“You can start now.” He nodded to indicate that he was ready.

“If that’s the case, please wait for a while.” The black man withdrew from the room and closed the door of the room in the small pavilion gently.

Click. A locking noise echoed from the outside before multiple layers of strength and energy forces drifted over and adhered on the room door fully.

“Are you worried that I’ll become mad and destroy this place after I lose my mind?” Garen had heard that most of the people who had seen the Origin of the Mother Stream would fall into a state of mental confusion and damage the room because of their chaotic madness.

He walked in front of the glass and glanced outside at the boundless starry sky through the transparent icy glass. This place was the High Hall in the interior of Lighthouse. It was completely unlikely that it led outside to the galaxy in the external world directly. Most of the scenery here was simulated.

Time passed slowly before changes appeared in the galaxy on the other side of the glass quickly.

The dark blue then pitch-black starry sky gradually accelerated, moving faster and more frantically.

Garen could only feel that his eyes were now filled with the light of countless blue stars that were moving rapidly. Next, a long slim mark that resembled a line was pulled out.

The entire galaxy instantly turned into a tornado-like funnel that was larger on the top and narrower at the base.

Shh!!

At that moment, the entire galaxy shrunk downwards and condensed into a ball completely. It was actually a little silvery-white button.

Inside the little button that was only the size of a fist was a galaxy that was turning slowly. It looked unusually magnificent.

“Has it started?” Garen concentrated and held his breath while staring at the button carefully.

A thunderous noise could be heard from the button suddenly before an abundance of white light burst forth at that moment. The white light was significantly brighter than the rays of a nuclear bomb. Garen’s eyes could only feel a bout of piercing pain instantly before his eyes closed due to the conditioned reflex.

Hiss!

There was a faint noise.

The white light disappeared.

Garen opened both of his eyes quickly. The scene before him had completely undergone great changes now.

He was not standing inside the room of the little white pavilion anymore. Instead, he was currently floating within an infinite, faint yellow colored space.

Little ball-like objects that resembled liquid and air bubbles floated up beside him before fluttering above.

He could only see an endless stretch of yellow when he raised his head. It seemed as though the bubbles could not float to the end when they drifted above. Instead, they only turned smaller.

“This place is…”

Gurgle…

Another air bubble floated up beside him.

He suddenly saw that there were countless galaxies that were rotating and flowing inside these bubbles. The bubbles that were only the size of an eyeball could actually map out gigantic and uncountable sights.

He could not help but reach his forefinger out to touch one of the air bubbles gently.

Boom!!!

Suddenly, countless terrifyingly vast oceans of information from the bubbles surged towards his brain madly.

His Energy Machinist Imprint instantly turned rapidly. A large amount of Soul Energy was being exhausted. Garen felt as if he was a dried-up sponge that was thirstily absorbing the massive amount of information that was surging over with the bubbles.

Although the contents of the information were extremely vast, some of it was insignificant. That type of information included the history that was formed by countless planets and destinies. Even though it seemed magnificent, it was actually meaningless to him. Each planet had records that were either long or short. Some of them spanned over billions of years while others lasted as long as more than a hundred billion years.

As the information surged into his brain madly, Garen slowly and gradually realized that something was amiss. All of this information was faintly interspersed with a certain strange Aura. It resembled the Aura that was fused with Soul Energy that he had discovered earlier.

Chapter 1248: Black Hole 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Every trace of Information Stream that was enough to instantly cause the brains of ordinary people to collapse was constantly surging and condensing in Garen’s mind, gradually forming golden symbols with a splendid aura.

These were meaningless symbols, yet incomparably complex. Though they seemed unusually concise, if seen in detail, each and every line contained countless terrifying changes and Information Streams.

“The predecessors who were able to record these were definitely powerful to a certain realm already.” Garen sincerely admired the predecessor who established these records of Information.

As the Information Stream gradually increased, every flow contained the history of the Milky Way Universe’s development. Gradually, these new symbols began to stick together slowly and formed a stream of golden symbols, flowing slowly in Garen’s mind.

Instead of water, only a myriad of golden symbols was in the creek.

Garen could feel the inexplicable aura intensified as it got stronger and stronger. As soon as the stream of golden symbols was formed, the aura immediately increased.

The symbols flowing into the stream were getting denser.

The small stream gradually grew to become a river, and still continued growing bigger and wider.

Steadily, the heavy parts of the river descended rapidly, sinking to the riverbed as the clear parts gradually rose. The clearest and lightest part was on the surface, attached with a faint unreal layer of aura. That was the vast aura formed by the golden symbols.

The aura flowed along the huge river, gradually forming a river that was lighter and thinner. It was no longer golden, but translucent and almost colorless.

As the aura increased and thickened as time passed, it began to fade into a pale green shade as it rushed rapidly.

The entire river was gradually divided into two layers. The inner layer was the golden inland river wrapped in the aura as it continued flowing slowly, whereas the outermost layer was just a myriad of aura flowing around.

Due to the different flow rates of both layers, a slight friction was formed. This force had an incredible penetration, and that was a new time. It constantly brushed against all the foreign objects, wearing them out until they slowly declined. From complete to deformity. From their peak until they fall to decline. Thus the creation of a brand new history, a new form of Information Stream. The Information Stream continued to condense into golden symbols and then formed a new Mother Stream.

“What is the origin of Mother Stream then? Where did she originate from? What kind of pull forms such a scale?” Garen still could not see the whole picture. Even though he understood the concept of Mother Stream’s existence, he still could not find the fundamental origin of Mother Stream. Only by finding it would he be able to truly figure out the real reason behind Mother Stream’s exhaustion.

He continued looking patiently. As if responding to his inquiries, the pictures changed once again.

The picture changed from the pale green aura rushing upward. The river surface grew wider as its shade darkened, the flow rate of the gushing water increased as well.

The friction against the inland river was also increasing at the same time. The flow of time had reached an exceedingly terrifying extent, almost thousands of years have passed by. Perhaps another ten thousand years would pass by if he took a nap.

The pictures started to shake.

“I’m afraid I can only get here…” A low, loud voice rumbled from the picture. “My limit, my life, is not able to support itself any longer if I continue moving forward.”

The voice spoke in Endor. Clearly, this snippet of picture was not recorded down by a random transmigrator, but a certain supreme True Soul from Mother Stream.

Garen also knew that he had reached a crucial point, all his attention fixed on the image before him.

The picture swayed more and more but the recorder seemed to be unwilling. It hesitated for a bit before the picture started swaying even more violently than before.

It seemed to have thrown the recorded item to the front.

Garen could feel his head swim for a while, not knowing how far it flew.

With a puff, the picture paused for a moment, completely settling down on a huge bunch of giant dark green balls.

Around the balls were green wired tentacles that were densely grown together, and among the mass of dark green was a small black opening. The Black Hole was so conspicuous that the eye-catching greens around it were not even able to cover up its existence.

Darkness, indescribable darkness. Broad, grand, and vast.

As soon as Garen set eyes on the black hole, the Soul Rings in his mind suddenly started swaying, his Soul Energy was boiling like hot water.

He felt that the darkness was so gentle, so peaceful, and so inclusive as if it could accommodate and tolerate everything.

A sense of security that he never felt before poured into his heart.

It was as if he was back home. His physical body and mental mind were completely relaxed after a grueling exercise, he was sleeping on his bed after a shower and resting face up on his bed. The sort of unspeakable comfort almost made him let his guard down, and so his body moved toward the front involuntarily.

It seemed that a voice was calling out to him softly.

Come on… Come on… Darkness is the source of everything. Darkness embraces everything, derives everything, and it is the mother of all things, the mother of darkness. Before light, before the universe, before dimensional space, everything was in chaos… It was one of the beginnings…

Garen continued staring at the black hole blankly as surges of information flowed into his mind. From that moment onwards, the amount of information that entered his brain increased tenfold, then a hundredfold. His Energy Machine Imprint had completely collapsed as it was unable to deal with the immense information data. Blood started trickling down Garen’s nostrils but he did not notice anything at all.

Instead, he walked toward the glass slowly as if he was a complete, lost soul.

Bang.

He was blocked by the glass. Realizing he was blocked, Garen got angry instinctively. He started to punch the glass that was blocking his path.

The immense force echoed in the entire pavilion room.

The amount of information was getting more as it increased in size. Without noticing, four days had passed already. Within these four days, Garen never stopped his action of punching the glass. His nostrils were still bleeding and his face was getting paler by the day.

Perhaps nobody had ever been able to receive the Information Stream to this extent, but Garen did it.

This was the first Demon Lord Level powerhouse to enter and view this record whereas the previous highest rank was only just an Army-Level.

Garen persisted until the very last minute.

The black hole was constantly emitting an aura that was a combination of highly concentrated aura and Soul Energy. The combination of these formed a substance that was unknown toward Garen. When the substance reached a certain high point of concentration, it naturally produced a huge sense of security, as if everything was one. It was that sort of inclusive feeling.

Not only that, he had also found out something big. This substance seemed to be the main root of Mother Stream’s formation, separating into Aura Outer River and Golden Inland River. The river continued branching out as the different rates of water flow produced a different effect to the flow of time which would then affect the space universe that it flows through, hence generating a different rate of time flow.

Such a terrifyingly enormous river that could not possibly be surpassed connected an infinite universe of time and space and this cosmic time was divided into a different flow of time according to their different flow rates, forming various worlds.

Poof.

The picture disappeared suddenly.

Garen suddenly snapped awake from the recording and he found himself back in the pavilion.

He felt the region below is nose was moist and he reached out to touch it. Immediately, he could see his hands full of blood, most of them already dried into gores, all stuck below his nose and right above his jaw. He felt extremely uncomfortable.

“How long have I been standing?” He was a bit stunned and cast a glance toward the timer on the wall in the room. The clock-like timer displayed the count of fifteen days, twelve hours and six minutes.

“If we open it this way, Mother Stream seems to be a massive Information Stream formed by countless space information substance, but simply because of the innumerable information substance that was not likely to produce entities, the aura flowed from the black hole should be more important. That seems to be the real actual thing that gives Mother Stream substance.”

Garen’s brain was still very clear, though it was slightly aching as it had been a long time since he used his brain.

“Darkness embraces everything, it breeds everything, because it contains everything, it contains an infinite variety of substances. That is why we are able to find all sorts of entities that can match the Information Stream carried by Mother Stream. These entities are the substantial form of the massive Information Stream. They are the materialization of the universe galaxy’s history of development, the history of countless worlds. After they are all loaded, everything will come into place and form the stream.”

Garen calmed his nerves.

“From the looks of it, perhaps Mother Stream can be called the Long River of History, a substantialized version of the River of History, but it was higher than history itself. She did not just record about humans, but more of everything. But now, Mother Stream is almost depleting. If that’s real, that means… The recorded history is about to be destroyed.”

“Mother Stream’s water represented the records of the past. She does not represent the past, just the information records of past history, just like words on a slate. But it is such words that brought out a new meaning of its own, just like how recordings of books have affected time, space, and even life. This process is not normal at all,” Garen’s train of thoughts was clear by now.

“Then, the root of everything should be the Black Hole.” He recalled the mysterious Black Hole he saw in the images earlier on, that was what gave Mother Stream the ability to influence the entire universe.

Surprisingly, the pictures had completely disappeared right at this moment. But when Garen recalled the Black Hole, he suddenly felt that it was still constantly emitting an indescribable surge of aura right in his mind, right in his memory.

He was shocked.

Once the Black Hole was pictured in his mind, he could suddenly sense an inexplicable aura pouring out from the Black Hole into his mind.

Darkness and affability, embracing all things.

“This…!!!” Garen sucked in a deep breath. The aura emitting from the Black Hole in his memory had merged into his Soul Ring. It really did seem real as it slowly absorbed the Soul Energy constantly generated in the Soul Ring.

After he finished going through the Origin of Mother Stream, Garen had a deeper understanding of Mother Stream now.

Mother Stream’s water was not the root of life, but it was the huge amount of different information contained within it, those were the information of the evolutionary history of the natural universe. It allowed life to be closer to the natural universe and integrate with time to gain greater adaptability and many powerful forces.

The waters of Mother Stream were a condensation of numerous information. In other words, the aura condensed by Secret Technicians were actually a vast amount of information from their souls and also their own perceptions, combined with individual natural substances that carry information, finally forming the similar products.

With that, as long as there was a system of means that fit the rules of Mother Stream, even if it was no Secret Technique, other methods would still be able to produce such similar aura energy.

“Mother Stream is indeed huge and complex, but if I’m able to figure out the root of the Black Hole, perhaps I’ll be able to find out the truth behind the Depletion of Mother Stream.”

He was not reconciled at all. With his current soul, a Middle Demon Lord Class, perhaps an average creature would have a soul lifetime that could reach tens of thousands of years. Four Soul Rings represented forty thousand years of Soul Limit life. This was undoubtedly a great success for Garen, who was an evolved ordinary human. An average human’s soul, even a transmigrator, would collapse entirely after three or four times of reincarnation. Three or four times. If it was an average human who did not practice, the longest lifespan was approximately hundreds of years, and the soul would completely collapse after a total of three-four hundred years.

If it were the old men from Mech World who were fully cultivated, they would try to aim to extend their lives up to thousands of years, but Garen was far beyond that. As a transformed soul of Mother Stream System, his soul lifespan was no longer comparable to the general system.

After reincarnating into so many worlds, he was indeed bored of reincarnating already, having to live his reincarnated life repeatedly.

However, if it meant that he would lose his long life, he was not going to accept that as well.

The Depletion of Mother Stream meant all beings of Mother Stream System would lose their support and shelter. If the Mother Stream regulations were to collapse, the existence of Soul Energy of spirits would be fundamentally corrected by the cosmic force. The depletion was not just the cutoff of water, it was the extinction of the fundamental way of existence.

Just like a towering tree which had always been supporting the cave. Once the big tree withered, the cave would lose its support and there would be a huge mechanical gap. The cave would then naturally create a new structure and collapse to fill up the gap that was originally the tree. The force used would eventually crush the big tree entirely and re-establish a new mechanical balance of its own. A new, natural balance.

This was the case for Mother Stream.

In order to fill such a gigantic loophole that appeared all of a sudden, several universes would re-adjust their balance structure. Perhaps at the moment when the cave collapsed, all the small saplings and flowers under the big tree would instantly be crushed to death. All because the universe had adjusted its environment so that there was no more room or space for time to continue surviving.

Chapter 1249: Reincarnation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I… How should I go from here?”

Garen held the intense pain in his head as he stumbled toward the door. He gently pushed a button.

It was a button that reminded the people outside that he had finished watching.

There was no sound at first, but soon, soft footsteps could be heard outside.

Crack.

The door opened.

“Your Excellency, are you alright?” A young silver-haired lady in a white robe stared at Garen with a slightly stunned expression. The instant she opened the door, she was shocked by Garen’s appearance. Blood trickled down his nostrils and had splattered everywhere. He looked extremely miserable.

“I’m alright, I just need a rest and I’ll be fine,” Garen waved her off.

What he was most concerned with now was what kind of substance that was flowing out of the moving black hole in his brain.

Instinctively, he had a feeling that those black hole 气息 were of no harm to him.

The lady hurried forward and helped Garen up. The brushes of her arm released a few pale blue ripples that covered Garen’s body.

Immediately, a cool and comfortable feeling emerged within Garen, but in exchange, the lady’s complexion instantly paled.

“Sorry… My abilities are only barely able to treat you…” She whispered.

“Thank you, I’m already feeling much better.” Garen forced a smile. This was obviously a treatment approach but he knew his own body best. With his strong physique, unless he recovered himself, the external force required to affect his body would have to pay a price that not any ordinary living creature could afford.

Exiting the room, Garen came to the side of High Hall with the help of the lady. They found a chair for him to sit and take a breath.

This time around, Garen had used up so much energy inside out even his Energy Machine Imprint had collapsed. He could now only rely on his brain to deal with the large amount of data that he collected.

He had once encountered the same situation in Mech World, but it was not as troublesome as this time.

Especially that mysterious black hole, he had only watched the records of Information once but Garen already felt something had gotten into his mind.

He quietly closed his eyes and leaned against the chair. He heard faint noises of someone calling out his name softly but he was too exhausted to care about it, and so he fell into a deep sleep. High Hall had the same restrictions as the entire Lighthouse; that no living creatures were allowed to use force at the area, hence he could take a rest without worries.

As his consciousness gradually blurred, Garen faintly felt as if he was wrapped in a never-ending darkness 气息, as if something was holding onto him and moving in a certain direction.

He himself was classified as an Endor Demon Lord, possessing the terrifying powers of the Four Great Soul Rings. Such a level of dream control was practically a natural ability and basically, dreams would not be affected by any external forces. However, such an abnormal situation was currently happening.

With a slight shift of attention, Garen instantly woke up, his consciousness completely waking up from the dream.

The black mist around him dissipated all of a sudden, revealing a misty view of the outside world.

What surprised Garen was that the outside world was not an endless black region of dreams, but the large expanse of green waters of Mother Stream.

The roaring rumble constantly trembled in his ear.

He found himself swimming toward the upstream of Mother Stream. There were numerous 气魄 waters that were getting denser and greener.

“Come on… Embrace the darkness of everything… Turn it into the energy of the universe…” A faint voice that sounded like a summons constantly rang from ahead.

All of a sudden, Garen saw a familiar Black Hole that swiftly emerged before him.

“Black Hole!?”

His heart shook.

(What in the world is happening!? How did I suddenly get so close to Black Hole from my dreams? What in the world is this?!)

Garen thought of retreating. Facing something that he had completely no knowledge of, he was unwilling to simply rush into it. When he was prepared for the next time, with all the complete information he needed, it would still be not too late for him to have a go again.

“Retreat!” He commanded. As Demon Lord, the dream should still be completely under his control.

Boom!

With a loud crash, the surrounding rivers 气魄 was stilled immediately. The immense powers of the Demon Lord started spreading and he was once again in full control of his dream.

Garen felt his position gradually falling back as he began to move away from the mysterious, strange Black Hole.

But it was right at that moment! An extremely massive force rushed out of the Black Hole.

“Darkness… Darkness… Supreme darkness…!”

It seemed as if there were crowds of people praising, praising and singing songs, when an intense silk thread-like power started spreading and entangled Garen, pulling him by force into the pitch-black Black Hole.

“This is!!?” Garen’s heart tightened as his Soul Ring turned violently in an attempt to regain control.

But to no avail, the terrifying Black Hole’s power was like gigantic tentacles of multiple octopuses, and even more like innumerable invisible hairs, wrapping around him all over. In comparison with Garen’s own strength, the force that it had was like a giant’s compared to a baby’s. It was simply incomparable.

“Damn it!”

Everything was out of Garen’s control already. If the power of this Black Hole was really the source of Mother Stream, it was basically impossible for him to compete with his ant-like strength in comparison. After all, it was just a tiny recording image.

“Wake up!!” Stirring up the energy of his whole body, he tried to wake himself up from the dream, but unfortunately, his agitation just seemed to aggravate the Black Hole’s pulling force. An even stronger surge of pulling force spread from its tentacles.

Although Garen wanted to explore the secrets of Mother Steam’s source, he had never thought that it would be under such violent situation.

Suddenly, the Black Hole inflated and with a boom, it covered his entire sight.

In an instant, it was as if Garen dived into a pool of black ink. He could not see anything around him, only the thick, oil-like dark liquid slowly moving about as his body moved slowly like a vortex in water.

With such slow movements, a subtle trace of Information gradually penetrated Garen’s brain.

He vaguely understood what this place was…

“High-Dimensional Universe? The High-Dimensional Space that exists high above myriads of dimensional universes?” Garen identified the content of this Information. These records of Information were clearly arranged and seemed as they have been specially organized to form a method of storage similar to the Endor’s form of textual speech. It was also evident that the content was later on processed once again.

But then, Garen soon felt that his strength was constantly clustered just like a Celestial Body.

All his energy, including his powers, were all shrinking in the depths of his soul.

His surrounding was getting darker as it got denser, moving around was getting even more difficult. The pulling force stopped after pulling Garen in and disappeared completely.

“High-Dimensional Space… Inevitably requires an immense low-dimensional force as the base for evolutionary improvement. I don’t know if it’s enough for my level though.” Garen understood that after the process of improving his dimensional evolution, he would no longer have to worry anymore. However, he was currently worried whether his powers were sufficient to cope with him entering the High-Dimensional Space this time around.

Just like a character eager to break through the frames of a painting, entering the dimensional-space was no different. The price to be paid was absolutely unimaginable.

Since he was already pulled in, he was forced to begin this dimension improvement. Garen could no longer hesitate, and since there was no room for retreat, he could only move forward.

From the Endor Information left from the dark space, those residuals of Information seemed to contain a ton that wanted to forcefully increase their dimensions but failed. Among them were some Army Level ones, some were ordinary people who had acquired powerful treasures, some were the same as him; in the presence of Demon Lord Level when they encountered the existence of the Black Hole by coincidence. After irresistible circumstances, they were pulled in by force and forcefully carried out their dimensional development. Those who succeeded were able to enter the new High-Dimensional Universe whereas those who failed were turned into cosmic fertilizer, nourishing all beings.

Garen stirred up his Soul Ring which released an immense force. This intense force was the ultimate strength of a Middle Level-Demon Lord and it was even able to resist the Black Hole’s pull, even for just a second.

Perhaps a True Soul-Level would be able to completely break away from the pulling force, but Garen did not have the slightest resistance at this moment.

In the dark, the power of the whirlpool was getting weaker and weaker by the moment. Garen was almost in a sluggish state. From the looks of the Information memory that remained in the space, it was nearly impossible for one to rely on one’s energy to recover from a sluggish state. Once Garen’s mind was thoroughly stagnated, awaiting him would just be a moment where he gets swarmed by the huge flow of time as he rots to death.

The rotation of the whirlpool was actually able to largely offset the time flow over here at the source of Mother Stream. Once stopped, it would only need one or two hours to completely erase Garen’s life for ten thousand years.

Along the road, transmigrating through a number of different worlds, Garen had never feared to face death, and he stayed the same as the matter of life or death was right before him.

Being pulled into this Black Hole under odd circumstances, he would just be waiting for death if he did not advance. The only thing he could do was to fight hard.

Deep in Garen’s soul, he had decided that he would not hesitate anymore if he had to fight.

The Four Great Soul Rings started to spin and an immense power combined with his violent physique began a self-destructive nature.

The self-destructive nature would be able to produce a huge amount of aggressive force, but it would cause a permanent and irreversible damage to his Soul Ring. However, a Soul Ring could be devoured and absorbed again, whereas he only had one life.

Garen whipped up all his strength and prepared to release it all behind him.

At that moment, the Natural Attributes Pane below his gaze suddenly burst out a striking red flare.

The endless red light instantly penetrated his eyes, his bodies, and even the darkness around him. It was as if a light bulb suddenly lit up in the dark night.

Magnificent yet crystal clear.

The red crystal-like radiance instantly froze Garen like a bug caught in amber. He was unable to move at all, even the self-destructive Soul Ring energy that he prepared within his body condensed in a blink of an eye.

“This is!?” Garen was shocked. He had investigated the origins of his talents and powers for a long time, but no matter how much he investigated, he had never discovered a specific source. This sort of extreme, abnormal talent and power was just a formidable strength that was discovered by accidental luck.

But in reality, he knew deep inside that just relying on chemical mutation was actually sufficient to activate such a complex ability naturally.

To be able to modularize all the skills and abilities of beings in the world, and to generalize all of that so that they would never be chaotic and develop in a negative direction, every ability was well organized. Furthermore, it solidified his body so his physique would not degrade even if he slowed his training.

Such a strange and powerful talent was still never before seen even now that Garen had arrived at the Lighthouse.

Solidify everything and accommodate everything. These were practically the highest conceptual power.

Chapter 1250: Reincarnation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Once an ordinary person possessed the ability to solidify, if he were to train for two hours today, his strength would gain an adaptive improvement. Even if he stopped training for the next one year, the increase in his strength would remain permanently. In other words, as long as an ordinary person trained consistently every day, the person’s body would sooner or later reach its limit that the universe could only tolerate. After that, the solidifying ability would then exist at its peak and it would never degenerate.

This was the most terrifying part of talents and powers. The more Garen understood its power, the more he was afraid of it. Later on, he even tried to not depend on his talents and powers as much as possible as he was still unable to figure out its specific source.

And now there was finally a clue to the origin of his powers.

“Absolutely.” Garen’s entire body was wrapped in the red light as he began to move forward swiftly.

“It’s definitely from the High-Dimensional Space, otherwise it would’ve been impossible to trigger the Black Hole that easily!”

Garen made a few guesses in his mind.

The sudden outburst of Garen’s talents and powers prevented him from using 自爆魂环, and also temporarily halted the threat and danger imposed by the Black Hole, but the situation was still not optimistic from his side.

As the force of advancing increased, the speed increased as well. Garen felt as if he was drowned in earth, as if he was moving among layers of rocks in the soil. The resistance was stronger as well as the red light started shaking. It seemed that some of the powers were not caught.

Garen started to panic. Once the red light disappears, he would not even have the chance to struggle anymore as he would be instantly turned into cosmic fertilizer by the horrifying flow of time around him.

Fortunately, a glimmer of light seemed to emerge in the darkness.

At the forefront, there was a faint white light and the red light became dinner. As it gradually weakened, Garen took the opportunity and rushed forward immediately.

Boom!!

A scarlet blood-red whip lashed over all of a sudden.

Garen was only able to have a good look when it got closer and he realized that it was not a whip, but a gigantic stream of lava. Floating across the stream were numerous living creatures that were moaning in pain. Some human, some non-human. They were all naked, their bodies scorching black as they drowned in misery in the corrosive waters.

The scarlet red river close to Garen was emitting a ghastly attractive force, but as the red streak of light suddenly accelerated, the force merely rushed over instead, leaving the river far behind.

Soon, an enormous white-golden disc followed suit, zooming by the top of Garen’s head. The white-golden disk, too, had a powerful and alarming attractive force. It was also filled with numerous dignified castles, flying giant beasts, a large majestic army, and a choir that was singing praise.

The red light along with Garen accelerated once more, darting forward.

The white light in front was getting closer and closer. Garen could even see that the white shade actually just seemed to be a thick layer of plastic-like light membrane.

“Ladia… Ladia…” Soon enough, a bunch of galaxy-like vortexes slowly emerged at the left side, sending out subtle ear-piercing hums that emitted an even more horrifying attractive force, attempting to draw Garen over from the red light. However, the red light accelerated one last time, leaving it far behind.

At this moment, the red light has weakened to its limit, only a thin layer remained.

Garen was worried that it could no longer sustain itself and just explode straight away.

He then only noticed that his body had completely melted for some time already, and all that was left was his soul. The four Soul Rings rotated slowly around him, overlapping each other as they let out a bright, colorless fluorescent light.

And compared to before, his Soul Ring was slightly more condensed as if it just went through the previous process. The structure of his Soul Ring was now more stable and the original Middle Level-Demon Lord’s rickety base situation was now solved.

As soon as the white light membrane got closer and closer, Garen felt that his Soul Ring began to shrink rapidly. It became smaller and smaller until it was pocket-sized, becoming one full size smaller than its original size.

Finally, the red light wrapped around him crashed into the thin white membrane.

Boom!!

The crash seemed to explode in his ear.

White light flashed before his eyes and nothing could be seen at all. Garen had completely lost all means of perception.

The white light faded rapidly in front of his eyes and Garen felt as if he had broken a layer of membrane. He then straight away rushed into a brand new space that was more viscous and stronger.

The time flow here was a hundred times faster than the original one. He could clearly sense that the time flying by was tearing up his soul. Right this moment, the red light had completely lost its function of protecting him, hence why he could sense the time flow in the external world.

“So this is the High-Dimensional Universe?” With a slight hint of curiosity and in inexplicable awe, Garen extended his perception and looked outside.

In the dark endless space, appearing right before Garen’s eyes was a bunch of colorful substances that resembled seaweed, floating in the black space.

There was light moving about above the bunch of substances. Some spots were dark, some spots were blue, and some spots were an eye-catching red, but most of the spots were the yellow earth and the blue sea water.

It seemed to be a hefty Sand Table Projection of a world.

Garen found plenty of small disc-like pieces on the top. The pieces were slowly rotating like the gears of a machine, precise yet heavy. They were also all of different sizes and shades of color.

Around the discs were a lot of silk-like tattered colored materials, and some were even fluttering.

Whereas at this moment, he was moving ahead at high speed with the help of the red light’s final inertia, heading straight toward the seaweed-like world.

The bunch of substances itself already had a strong attractive force and as he gradually closed in, the world’s attractive force seemed to become bigger and stronger.

Swoosh!

Garen lost all his senses instantly and he fell into complete darkness. It was as if his speed accelerated to its limits, entering a state similar to teleportation. Suddenly, he entered an unpredictable situation.

*******************

Lighthouse

“Is Sword Master His Excellency still resting?” In the High Hall, a tall man dressed in a white robe walked out of the Teleportation Point slowly as he asked a lady who was also dressed in a white robe.

“Yes, Your Excellency.” The lady responded respectfully and stepped aside, revealing Garen who was sitting still behind her, leaning against the wall with his eyes closed.

Garen still appeared to be asleep. His eyes were shut tight, his complexion ruddy, as usual, nothing seemed to be out of the ordinary.

The man in the white robe’s face was shrouded in a clear light. He cast a glance toward and snorted as if he noticed something.

“No.”

He strode forward.

“Garen, Your Excellency.” He reached out and pressed on Garen’s shoulder.

Hiss…

In an instant, Garen’s entire body toppled over like a sandstorm, turning into countless beads of sand scattering all over the ground.

The lady was stunned and the man in white robe blanked out.

He quickly retracted his arm and went silent for a moment. After a while, he slowly spoke.

“Garen, His Excellency, I can’t feel the presence of his soul at all. His body has been completely withered and turned to sand, even all his life energy has been completely drained.”

The lady covered her mouth as she stared at him in disbelief.

“How is that possible!? He… He’s only seen the Mother Stream source once…!”

“Although I’m not willing to believe this, but it is what it is.” The man sighed in a low tone. “Garen has fallen. Notify the control team of Lighthouse to lower the flag…”

He showed an expression of sympathy.

“How unfortunate, a prodigy powerhouse… Perhaps this was an accident… As for the calling of the true source, maybe Garen was a bit too overconfident.”

*******************

Darkness…

Darkness remained and nothing could be seen.

When Garen woke up from his coma, he did not know how long he had been unconscious. He could feel that his Soul Ring seemed to be slightly cracked, but fortunately, it was still much better than before so there was no major loss.

The feedback from the surrounding powers indicated that he seemed to have stabilized, and the surrounding universe space rules were unusually stable to the point where people could boil in anger. If the rules of the Four Great Cornerstones world were said to be abnormal already, then the stability of the rules here was basically ten times stronger.

Nothing was in sight in the surroundings but Garen could feel that he seemed to be in an oval-shaped space. The space was small enough just for him to stay alone, but the troublesome thing was that there was a small meaty object that was snuggled up beside him. Unsure as to what was it, Garen slightly wriggled his body according to its movements.

This small little thing clearly occupied Garen’s activity space.

Garen could feel his actual body. He tried to hold his hand out but due to the complete darkness, he was unable to see both his hands. However, he could still sense the slow movements of his hands.

“I guess I’ve reincarnated again…” He came to a conclusion. According to his sense of touch, his hands did not feel like the palms of a human being, but something like a bird’s. There were three fingers in the front and one at the back, the tips of his fingers were sharp yet soft, obviously not fully grown yet.

In the darkness, Garen stretched out his claws and squeezed the small meaty object toward the corner. When he finally occupied the large space, he began to explore his current body shape carefully with his small claws.

He touched his legs, which seemed to be in the same position as his hands, his muscle lines were evident. He had no human toes, but the same four toes that were sharp at the tip yet still soft.

Touching his back, he could feel that something seemed to be moving on his back.

As he reached out with his claws, he indeed felt two fan-like things curled up clinging to his back. As his claws felt it, it was just like the feeling of touching his back ribs.

Besides that, Garen felt that his neck seemed a little too long.

His entire neck was one-third of his entire body length. There even something moving behind his butt.

This made him shudder for a bit.

“Is this a deformity!?”

No, it could not be. He quickly calmed himself down. In his four Soul Rings state, even if he was in the High-Dimensional Universe, the meaty object at the side would be a good enough contrast, no? That little guy was obviously a Soul Level-Soul Seed. In other words, even if it was not for the gap in their qualities, his powers were practically twenty times of this little thing beside him. Not to mention that his Soul Ring had a huge different qualitative change in powers in comparison to general Soul Seeds. Even if the wisps of powers were compiled together, there would still be a vast difference in terms of quality.

Garen felt a chill in his heart. He tried to release his Soul Energy to explore the situation outside the space but the oval-shaped hard wall was very strong and his Soul Energy was unable to penetrate through them. After multiple attempts, he gave up.

Moreover, he even found out that once his powers separated from his body, it would be exceedingly tough to unleash it.

Chapter 1251: Clan 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“This space…” After multiple attempts, Garen had completely given up on the idea of using his Soul Energy to explore the area.

At the same time, he noticed that there was a cord-like object attached to the inner wall of the eggshell and a soft liquid was flowing into his body from the umbilical cord.

“So these are nutrients?” He tugged at the umbilical cord and it was indeed very firm.

It was pretty obvious that he was in an embryo inside an eggshell, and such eggshell embryos often only appear with special creatures.

Garen searched through his memories and knowledge for almost half a day and instantly listed dozens of potentially similar species, but further verification was needed.

Time passed slowly.

The exterior of the eggshell gradually heated up as an unbearable heart was transmitted from the outside as if someone was toasting it with fire.

Garen started to feel hot, but the heat just got worse and worse he was almost unable to bear with it any longer. A subtle whining sound came from the small meaty object by the side that sounded like grains of sands, pitiful indeed.

Hu…

Suddenly, a breeze blew by and the temperature of the eggshell dropped instantly.

Inside the eggshell, Garen wriggled his body as he changed his position. Kicking the meaty object aside, he enjoyed the rapid decrease of the temperature.

“Esgula… Mildi…” Suddenly, a loud yet solemn voice rang outside the eggshell.

Garen was startled for a bit. After all, this was the very first time he heard something obvious outside that belonged to a creature, and it was a rhythmic voice, though it was an unknown language.

Hiss…

Soon enough, he was aware that something was not right.

The umbilical cord on his stomach began to glow, giving off a faint white shimmer like a lamp. Not only did it illuminated the inside of the eggshell, it shone on his current weak body.

White…!

Everything was white. Whether it was the inner wall of the eggshell or his body at that moment, everything was completely white.

By the light, Garen lifted his claw and noticed that it was a beast-like claw and there was no sign of humanity at all. The skin of his beast-like claw was covered with tiny scales, reflecting the white light faintly like a mirror. It was unusually beautiful.

“This body seems really weak,” Garen thought. Looking at his Attribute Pane below, there was nothing on display. Who knew when would his attributes restore. However, there was no doubt that his talent and power originated from this world. If he wanted to clear this up, the only chance he had was to be incubated and break out of the eggshell.

Garen tried out his body’s strength and surprisingly, his body’s strength far exceeded what he had imagined.

“Seems like my soul is too strong already, I guess most human bodies aren’t able to accommodate me without modification, and that’s why I’ve entered such a tyrannical creature’s body,” speculated Garen.

As he made various speculations in his mind, a soft and warm liquid suddenly oozed out of the umbilical cord on his stomach. There seemed to be a special unknown Information Stream in the liquid. Just like a trickling creek, the Information Stream poured into his mind along with the liquid, entering the surrounding air of his Soul Rings as if it was engraved, turning into many interesting patterns.

Garen’s immense Soul Energy system quickly rotated, consuming a large supply of Soul Energy. It soon found the language system of the Information Stream and differentiated them properly into his brain’s language region.

Once he was done with all the work, ten minutes had barely passed.

Garen cast a glance toward the meaty object by the side and realized that it was also receiving the Information Stream through the umbilical cord as well. Obviously, it was not all meant for him alone.

“Legend says that certain powerful creatures have an innate inheritance even before they are born, might this be the so-called innate inheritance?” Garen made a wild guess. He believed that his soul was strong enough to a certain extent that the type of body he chose was definitely not any weak types, so it would not be surprising at all if he was to receive innate inheritance.

After the language system passed in by the umbilical cord was completed, he began to use it as a tool to view other information.

With a look, he immediately fully understood what kind of being he was.

‘I’m one of The Great Colorful Dragon Clan, I was born to be incomparably noble, being the apex predator at the top of plenty of food chains. We, the dragon race are born honorable, growing into Level Five creatures. We have brutal close fighting abilities and of course, talent and spells of great lethality…’

An unknown voice swayed in the depths of Garen’s heart, repeatedly narrating the various powers, glories, and honors of the dragon race.

The voice kept repeating over and over again until Garen was annoyed, but the mass of meat by the side was enjoying it. Lying there motionless, slight Soul Energy emitted from it showed that it was extremely concentrated at the moment.

“Dragon race?” From the Information he had, Garen quickly read about the specimen he belonged to, White Dragon.

The voice continued steadily, reading out the information accordingly. It barely reached one-third of its contents before Garen finished all the content sent in from the Information Stream.

He also understood his current identity.

A White Dragon!

To be precise, he was a young dragon belonging to the White Dragon Clan.

“Interesting!” This was Garen’s first time reincarnating into a non-human race. The transmitted Information obviously had personal emotional characteristics, it was evident that the previous generation of White Dragons had amended the contents with their own emotions. In the beginning, it was an explanation of the lofty status of the dragons’ superior position. After that, it was just some basic knowledge of common sense. Then, regardless whether the young dragons were able to stand it, huge and complex knowledge of customs, taboos and other information all swarmed inward. It was obvious that the information were all prepared to store within the minds of the young dragons and as they slowly grow up, the information would all open up. This was the normal growth of a young dragon.

But clearly, Garen did not fit into this normal category. With a few glances, he had already finished reading through the information. This Information Stream in comparison to the Black Hole was practically the difference between an ant and the Sun, even filling a tooth gap was not enough.

However, soon enough, the transmission of the Information Stream came to a halt.

The inheritance had ended.

The outside quietened down once again as time passed by slowly and Garen started to feel bored all over again. The inheritance had allowed him to understand what kind of place he was at.

Main Substance Plane.

His inherited memories called this place as such.

The place was very, very huge. It was so vast to the point that even if White Dragons fly at their highest speed, three hundred kilometers per second, for nineteen years, they would still be unable to see the plane’s edge. Plenty of ethnicities stayed here as well, but humans were the largest ethnic group that occupied the land. They were powerful, greedy, and they were like grass that could not be burned out by a prairie fire. Another group appears in a blink of an eye after one group dies and they had innumerable strong people.

Since the disappearance of the dragon race from twenty thousand years ago, they had completely fallen into a state of decline. Although the inherited memories praised the greatness and glories of the dragon race, Garen’s sensitivity could sense the hatred against humans and dwarves, especially humans. They hunted the dragon race using special crafts to keep the bodies, and they even made all kinds of powerful equipment for the dwarves.

They were more disgusting and greedy than the devils from Hell and demons from the abyss.

Those detailed yet boring contents were quickly swept through by Garen, just so he could instill the hatred and loathing of the young dragons toward human beings.

The main concern of Garen was the environment here.

Clearly, the environment of this world was pretty similar to plenty of Western myths he had once seen on Earth.

What shocked him the most was that there was a God here!

Some Gods descended on gospels or miracles and there was a large number of believers who established organizations and built the country. Some Gods blended into daily lives such the God of Poetry, the God of Wealth, the God of Water, the God of Forests etc…. All sorts of Gods who were powerful and promising. Not only they had ordinary high-ranked warriors as their subordinates, but they had demigods who ignited the sacred fire, Holy Spirits that were pure and innocent. Various religions divided ninety percent of the entire Main Substance Plane.

“Gods… The Gods here, what way of existence do they have?” Garen continued to analyze the inherited Information in the eggshell.

There were no firearms here, no powerful weapons like nuclear bombs and guided missiles, at least. That was because gunpowder was extremely unstable! Furthermore, the powerful force here was way beyond a technological world like Earth.

The more powerful ones here were the wizards.

There were two round moons in the sky. One was the Goddess of Wizards, founder of Weave, and also the Goddess of Magic, Mystra. The purple moon represented the core of the Weave, and was not just any ordinary planet.

On the other hand, the other moon was black in color. Only necromancers and believers who held control over dark shadow energy could see it. That was the Black Moon, and it represented another Weave — Shadow Weave. It originated from the Dark Goddess Shar and it was created to fight against Mystra.

These two Weaves were this world, or perhaps, the main transmission system of this plane.

Garen did not quite understand the concept of this plane.

The planets he was familiar with were the galaxy and the nebula. However, there were no specific forms here, and replacing them instead was the plane, various sizes of plans that constantly changed.

A plane was a sphere that resembled a planet that constantly rotates. From the inherited information, this was the only point he could understand. The others were understandings of Hell, the abyss, and the human world.

Among them, the Information had knowledge of the human world and Hell the most.

Part of the reason was perhaps human beings were their biggest enemy, whereas Hell was an evil plane adjacent to the Main Substance Plane. The White Dragon Clan once recruited young dragons to enter Hell to run training sessions for a period of time as hunting creatures of Hell was a sign of adulthood.

But now, everything seemed different…

Garen could see the end of the inherited information.

Decadency was no longer inevitable for the Dragon Clan. Even though they still existed at the top of the food chain, they could simply no longer live alone because once they were left alone, they were highly likely to be attacked by countless, greedy dragon slayers. Their bodies, their treasures, and all their wealth were completely sucked clean by those greedy maggots.

Even when faced with such evil people, some of the Dragon Race even turned and joined them, which was simply unforgivable!!!

The anger in the inherited information was just like a virus, even Garen was almost infected by it as hatred toward humans grew within him. A burst of Soul Energy exploded from his Soul Ring all of a sudden, canceling out the intense negative emotion he felt.

He then continued watching.

Chapter 1252: Clan 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘Those traitors, those fallen ones who have abandoned their vengeance and race, will soon be turned into Soul Basins by the Great Dragon Goddess Tiamat and burn for all eternity in the abyss!’ That was the loud cry of hatred inscribed in the White Dragon’s inherited memory.

“Alright then… Clearly, White Dragon’s ancestors were badly slaughtered by humans.” At this sight, Garen had basically finished reading all the content.

Throwing aside the parts his subjective emotions got involved, he did get plenty of information about this world.

Priests, wizards, warlocks, and other professions that involved the ability of casting spells were part of the high-ranked combat forces of this world. The cavalry, swordsmen, assassins, thieves and other occupations formed the abnormal yet complete society system of various armed forces.

Compared to the strong human races and the equally powerful dwarves and elves, the current dragon race had already vanished completely. On the other hand, the White Dragon Clan were located in the northern parts of the plane, building their nests deep in the cold northern ice mountains. While this nest Has not even lasted for a hundred years, the White Dragon Clan would move every once in a while to other regions so they could avoid humans who might find them.

The powerful and evil Dragon Goddess Tiamat did not protect her own kind whereas the White Dragon Clan constantly moved around. But as the Main Substance Plane was gradually occupied by more and more human beings, the places they were able to hide reduced dramatically. As part of the evil Colorful Dragon Clan, they were different from Metallic Dragons. The White Dragon Clan had long expected that sooner or later, they would have to battle the humans.

No… Perhaps it would not be a war, but a massacre.

There was already too many inherited members of White Dragon who weakened so much they were not even able to leave the plane. A large part of White Dragons was even just slightly stronger than white lizards. Besides their mighty dragon bodies that were still able to handle close combat, they would just be beasts that were slightly bigger in size.

Their intelligence slumped due to the lack of food.

Knowing this, Garen was completely speechless.

“Such a large dragon race, but even if White Dragons were the weakest among the Colorful Dragons, it’s indeed incredible that they could fall to this point.”

Time slowly passed by as he poured himself into his boring research of the inherited information.

The dragon egg seemed to become fragile over time and inexplicable surges of energy were transported into Garen’s body and the body of the meaty object by the side all of a sudden through the umbilical cord.

Garen could feel his body getting stronger and stronger, his scales and nails getting harder and harder.

Crack.

Suddenly one day, as Garen accidentally scratched the eggshell the inner wall of the eggshell actually broke into pieces.

He glanced at the side, the meaty object had also developed into a Dragon Whelp and it was slamming its four tiny claws at the inner wall of the eggshell with all its might. After that, it started biting bits and pieces of the eggshells as it shattered while showing a look of intoxication.

Staring at the falling pieces that still had white slime here and there, it did look a bit disgusting. Instantly, his appetite went away.

Garen smashed the eggshells for a couple more times before he stumbled out.

Everything was white outside. Meeting his gaze was a piece of white-bluish ice. He was at a huge arched cave.

There was nothing in his surroundings, just a soft grey-white fur padding placed below the white gigantic egg.

After Garen got his entire body out, he heard chewing sounds of the cracking eggshells coming from behind him.

He turned around and have a look.

There were four other white dragon eggs laying in the grey-white fur-padded nest. Among the four eggs, two of them managed to climb out and both eggs were broken. The white Dragon Whelps that crawled out, including him, made a total of four heads, being a two-headed dragon crawled out of one of the eggs.

Garen observed the Dragon Whelps carefully. They do not seem much different from a small lizard that grew out its wings, perhaps slightly bigger in size. They were almost the size of a human’s head. For a wine barrel-big dragon egg that was grey-white in color to have two Dragon Whelps was just nice.

He looked at the Dragon Whelp that came out from his same egg. Its scales all over its body was just like a mirror, reflecting the layers of ice and the cave’s inner walls in its surroundings.

Hiss… Hiss hiss…

Garen’s brother called out to him several times. Though he was unsure what language was it, Garen actually understood his words!

“Still not eating? This is really good and it’s nutritious for us!” The sentence translated like this.

Garen was speechless. He wanted to speak but he soon realized that his breaths were naturally spurted out.

Whoosh.

White gas came out of his mouth, hitting the ground before him. A condensed layer of white frost appeared on the ground and the original ice surface was covered by a whole new layer of white frost.

“You can eat it, I’m not hungry.” Garen only managed to say this finally, relying on the language in his inherited memory to respond.

Garen was a bit embarrassed as he had forcibly seized most of the nutrients of the eggshells, and so he stopped snatching the scrap bits of nutrients left now.

Both brothers stared at the snow on the ground enviously. This was a phenomenon of overnutrition… They could only have enough energy to hold their chilled breaths when they had the sufficient nutrients.

Garen looked at the other two Dragon Whelps. No wisdom or rationality could be seen from their eyes as they fought with each other, snatching the eggshell fragments. Obviously, they were specimens of low-intellect.

Due to the sole nutrients and lack of food, the White Dragon Clan had plenty of multiple births, and multiple births were the cause that brought out weaker and deformed White Dragons that were more adaptable to the environment.

These malformed White Dragons did not have the best mental development and their bodies were weaker by half, but they were more adaptable to less food and a single source of food. They could even thrive in harsh conditions.

Their small sizes also lead to a reduction in their usual energy consumption.

These deformed White Dragons did not even have the rights to fly as their wings were degraded, so they were no different from Earth Dragons. Most of the time, deformed White Dragons were just straight away called Earth Dragons.

“The other two are Earth Dragons, that’s unfortunate,” Garen’s brother sighed, “Why can’t they be the same as us?”

“I don’t know.” Garen shook his head, “Maybe it’s congenital.” They all had inherited memories. That was why they could speak and they were knowledgeable right when they were born, it is just that their minds were not fully mature.

Crack…

The two other eggs seemed to be disturbed by them as they cracked open suddenly. Small Dragon Whelp heads popped out from inside.

Three of them had wise eyes while the other, sadly, was another Earth Dragon.

“Four siblings altogether,” The Dragon Whelp biggest in size spoke up.

“Them too!” Garen’s brother said loudly as he pointed to the other three Earth Dragons.

“No, no! They’re just waste!” The biggest Dragon Whelp was even bigger than Garen, almost as tall as two basketballs stacked together. In comparison to the weak body of Garen’s brother, he was almost twice his size.

“They’re not waste!” Garen’s brother responded unconvincingly.

The two Dragon Whelps at the side stood on both sides as they started their first quarrel since birth.

Garen ignored the group of little brats who were fighting, walked to the side alone and sat on the warm ice.

The surface of the ice was warm, perhaps this was the first time he felt this. The White Dragon’s body temperature was actually much lower than a normal creature’s. Their optimum temperature was below freezing point as White Dragon’s blood were never above zero degrees.

At this moment, Garen started feeling a little troubled.

He had just realized an extremely serious problem.

“My Soul Energy, it can’t leave my body anymore!” Garen felt the seriousness of the problem. If his Soul Energy was unable to separate from his body, his Soul Seed would not be able to as well because Soul Energy was much thinner than Soul Seeds. If this thin energy could not escape his body, let alone Soul Seed which was high-density and not to mention Soul Ring which was even denser.

“This means that in a few years’ time, my soul will completely form as one together with this body! If this body dies, then I’ll die too. My soul will collapse, and even the chance of reincarnation will be completely lost.”

Garen swiftly concluded.

“So this is the trouble with High-Dimensional Space?” He began to analyze and thought thoroughly where the root of all his problems was. The greatest reliance of the Endor Demon Lords was the ability to reincarnate and reborn endlessly. They did not have the innate talents of transmigrators and they would suffer a huge loss if their souls were to transmigrate even just once, but they could strengthen their souls through training and solidifying their souls. With that, they would be able to reduce the amplitude of damage caused when they transmigrate.

The average creature would not be involved in the soul level and they had no way around it all because the Demon Lords’ Soul Rings were able to separate from their bodies, so the death of their bodies would only harm a small part of their Soul Energy. After that, they were able to quickly reincarnate and bounce back.

But now, Garen could sort of feel that he had lost his reincarnation ability, and it was probably related to the exhaustion of Mother Stream. Or perhaps it was also related to the rules of this world.

He quickly scanned the attributes below. Fortunately, his talent and powers had reappeared. He vaguely figured out a little bit of the origin of this ability of his, and he was ready to use this thing once again.

Talent and powers were able to increase various physical qualities of his own body in the midst of developing.

Now that he was reborn as a White Dragon, his foundation was already alarmingly powerful. If he was to add some attribute points to this foundation, the future development would be absolutely unimaginable.

“For the time being, just don’t worry too much. I still have the protection of White Dragon Clan, so my youth days shouldn’t be too big of a problem.”

Garen suppressed the doubts in his mind. Even if it was the Demon Lord, it would for sure take some time to grow after reincarnation. Now that his Soul Energy was unable to get out, he had lost the method of using his Soul Energy to influence the outside world in combat. It also meant that he could only count on this weak body of his to fight now.

The body of a newborn baby White Dragon was approximately the size of a basketball and they would crawl around on their round bellies. At this level, even two ordinary human soldiers could kill them with just a few shots. According to the legendary powerful Dragon Race, even newborn babies had the defense mechanism of a Level Two soldier and they were even able to kill leopards. Their speed was indeed astounding.

But the White Dragon Clad was after all declining.

Garen heaved a sigh. The only thing he could rely on now was this small body. Since his Soul Energy was unable to penetrate through his body, it could only be converted to strengthen his body now.

Originally, his Middle Demon Lord Level Soul Energy could directly Dream Weave and manipulate creatures easily. According to the inherited memory, although the rules of this space were very advanced, creatures could still be born with strong souls, but creatures below Level Four could not avoid having their souls be manipulated by him. But now…

Soon enough, an enormous White Dragon slowed down its wings as it flew in the cave.

A snake’s neck, bat-like wings, a massive body that resembled a lizard, and a white chill slowly spreading from the mouth.

This gigantic creature was almost three meters high and nearly the size of an elephant.

Chapter 1253: Threat 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Although the scale of three meters was nothing in the eyes of Garen, it was different here. This was High Dimensional Universe and the rules here were abnormally limited. A member of the White Dragon Clan could simply grow up to three meters in size, so how powerful would the beings of higher levels be?

It should be known that as the rules tightened, more energy would be consumed to maintain an extremely rigorous internal body structure if one wanted to develop such an enormous body.

“Children. I am your mother, Cocoreila. It is time to accept God’s baptism.” White Dragon fell onto the ice like an elephant and with heavy steps, it took a few steps forward before bending its head and spurt out big breaths of Chill.

However, this Chill that was blown at the Dragon Whelps did not feel cold at all, but warm instead.

As soon as they saw White Dragon, all the Dragon Whelps, including Garen, felt a natural sense of envy from the bottom of their hearts.

“Cocoreila.” Garen remembered the name. If nothing went wrong, this White Dragon would become a protector and relative of his for many years in the future.

“Recently, several Alien Souls have fallen into our region. By accepting the baptism of the Dragon God, we’ll be able to identify these alien creatures. Pastor Pasola has already requested for the Gods so all of you have to go through baptism. Although I don’t think anyone can actually break through our clan’s strong enchantment silently. But the process has to be done.”

White Dragon Mother Cocoreila whispered as she explained.

“Alien Souls?” Garen’s heart skipped a beat. He himself was a typical alien right now since his Soul Ring have yet integrated with his current body. The Soul Ring was his true soul as the Demon Lord and it could be clearly seen from the content of his inherited memories. Once the Gods here found out about the problem, then…

The Gods here could simply destroy the plane or create a whole new plane, their existence was extremely powerful. It should be known that a plane was a lot bigger than a planet, even possibly the size of a galaxy.

He already knew that the creatures he encountered that wanted to gobble him up when he transmigrated through this space were likely to be powerful Gods of the outer domain!

Those powers were so powerful that even talent would hide away as well.

He compared the powers to his own Soul Ring’s strength. The powers of the Gods could almost be compared with Mother Stream’s tributaries, and even one of Mother Stream’s tributaries was way beyond an average True Soul.

“This world is too dangerous!!” A strong sense of vigilance immediately surged through his mind. In the inherited memories, the Wizards and Arcanists of this High-Dimensional Universe often created different weird and powerful creatures of various time and space universes through all sorts of dimensional summoning. From there, the creatures were either enslaved or slaughtered to be used as materials.

This kind of horrible behavior was completely no different from the most prosperous period of the Warlocks, perhaps even tyrannical.

In other words, this world that he had arrived at was probably the most brilliant civilization of the ancient Warlocks, maybe even stronger than the Warlocks.

Garen immediately raised his guard.

God’s baptism, he had no idea whether he would be noticed. But once discovered, even if his Demon Lord Level did recover, he did not think there was a way he could escape from all sorts of Alien Souls and the greedy eyes of the Wizards and Gods with his current strength.

This place was unlike other places. The studies of souls here were far comparable to the other worlds.

“This is troublesome…” Looking at the White Dragon’s intense stare directed at them Dragon Whelps, Garen’s heart sank.

“I must think of a way!” The idea quickly swam around Garen’s mind. He was not sure of what kind of God’s Baptism was it, but if the Gods were to notice something wrong, the consequence was definitely not something he could bear.

“This place is not something I have experienced from the previous worlds… This is a place that can really endanger my soul!” Garen’s mind began to set to work, all sorts of plans popped into his mind. His Soul Rings violently collided against each other, producing colorless sparks of friction that broke out combined with his Soul Energy.

However, without fully understanding the nature of God’s spells, there was no way for him to deal with it.

“Come on children, let’s go.” White Dragon Cocoreila said in a hushed tone. She carried the three Earth Dragons in her mouth as the other Young Whelps fluttered their wings as they flew up shakily.

No matter how much dragons deteriorate, they were still able to fly as long as they were not Earth Dragons.

Garen was no exception. He also flew up shakily as he fluttered his wings. With that, a group of Young Whelps followed behind White Dragon as they flew out of the cave.

Hu…

A gust of chilly wind blew on them.

Garen blinked a little as he looked into the distance, the outside world was wide and open. Numerous ice field of greys and whites were spread all the way to the horizon before his eyes.

Grey clouds loomed, and right below it was White Dragons flapping their wings, flying around the snow mountain they were at.

Garen kept a distance between Cocoreila. Almost all the Dragon Whelps were captivated by the magnificent scenery, except Garen, who kept looking back at the nest that he flew out from.

The sharp white snowy peak was already just a short distance away. Almost dozens of White Dragons swarmed around the sharp mountain peak. Some of them were big, some of them were small, but even the smallest in size was at least six meters long and three meters high whereas the stronger ones were seven or eight meters long.

Mou~~~!

White Dragon’s roar sounded extremely weird. It was long and it seemed that they did not have to change their breath, easy roar lasting a solid twenty to thirty seconds, indeed strong and powerful.

Since Garen had lost his Soul Energy detection ability to explore around, he could only observe these huge creatures visually.

He suddenly thought of a problem.

There was an insurmountable relationship between the High-Dimensional Universe and the Low-Dimensional Universe. Just like characters of a comic, they had completely incomparable differences. However, the red light of talent and power could bring him directly from a low dimension to a high dimension. He could not imagine what kind of being that existed could have such an ability. It was no longer just controlling the rules of time and space, but the direct promotion of the essence of life beyond the level of a Low-Dimension Universe. Such means were much more terrifying than an ordinary person turning into a God.

But after a simulation played in Garen’s mind, he seemed to have another more absurd guess.

According to the formation of Mother Stream, he could simulate a possibility of the origin of the Black Hole.

“Could it be that I myself am a creature from the High-Dimensional Universe and the red light is just something that takes me to Low-Dimensional Universe and experiences transmigrating, so that’s why creatures there don’t kill me. If I die, I’ll just continue to reincarnate endlessly. But now that I’ve entered another High-Dimensional Universe, naturally, I’ve completely lost the ability to do so.”

Garen was more and more aware that his assumption might be true.

“If I’m a creature of the High-Dimensional Universe, that explains why I’ve never met anyone from the same world as myself at Lighthouse. At the same time, it explains a lot of unexplainable things. The red light is just obviously something that helps me cross the barrier, nothing else about it. I’m just entirely adapting to the rules of this world all by myself.”

“It’s time. Get ready to land.” White Dragon Cocoreila’s voice pulled him back to reality.

A row of White Dragons had already flown to a huge circular flat surface. It was the top of a mountain peak, just as if someone had used a knife to cut the peak of the mountain to create such a huge platform.

In the middle of the circular platform was a sharp black metal needle that looked like a sundial timer.

There were dozens of White Dragons who were on the platform already, along with their dragon whelps. Cocoreila had also brought Garen and the other Dragon Whelps down, then searched for a place before kneeling down. After that, there were still several White Dragons that came swooping down, standing or kneeling down silently on the platform.

Garen was getting surer of his own assumption, but his current crisis was not whether he was a High-Dimensional Creature, because of no matter what his origin was. Facing this world, he still had only one identity — Alien Soul.

As more and more White Dragons landed, Cocoreila placed her Earth Dragon Whelps on the platform which she carried in her mouth and waited quietly.

“Don’t move around. If you get too close to the other White Dragons, they will kill you,” she warned.

Only then did Garen remembered that even if the White Dragon Clan lived together in groups for survival, their cruel and selfish nature could never be covered up. After all, they were still the evil Colorful Dragon Clan and they were extremely vigilant about everything.

Mou…!

At this time, almost all of the White Dragons have arrived already. The circular platform was densely packed with over twenty adult dragons and hundreds of Dragon Whelps. All the adult dragons had their long necks bent downward, bowing down on the ground as they let off gentle humming sound.

An enormous White Dragon that was over ten meters in size descended slowly, landing at the center of the circular platform, right beside the long needle.

It had a white staff in one of its claws that was above his head and gently settled on the ground, standing with its two hind legs just like a human.

“May the great Tiamat bless us.” This White Dragon was obviously not young anymore. He raised the white staff into the air and a white mist appeared on the top of the staff. Whistling sounds of winds could be heard as if there were white snowflakes floating about in the mist.

A text-like symbol emerged, suspending right above the mist as it shimmered a white fluorescent shade. From far away, the symbol resembled a five-headed flying dragon. It was just an outline of it with extremely simple lines.

Thump.

A shimmering ripple that was like a heartbeat started spreading from the symbol and instantly diffused into the entire white circular surface area.

Garen’s heart almost jumped out of his chest. He felt an intense pressure that suddenly fell onto the top of his head as if some horrifying creature was watching them as if a giant was watching them like ants on the ground.

But he could clearly feel that no surge of energy was passing through their bodies, the elder White Dragon’s action just now was just merely calling for the attention of God.

“Danger!” Garen felt extremely uneasy.

He seemed to have a sort of illusion as if his deepest darkest secrets were looked into by a great existence.

The feeling was making him very uncomfortable. It was like being stripped naked in front of a crowd and standing on stage with countless spotlights shining on his little junior…

Although the metaphor was completely ridiculous, it was nevertheless extremely appropriate as to Garen’s current feelings.

“No!! No!! Roar!!”

Right at that moment, a loud voice thundered as a Dragon Whelp soared into the sky. Flapping its wings as it flew into the distance, its body emitted a strong Soul Energy Force.

Garen’s heart skipped a beat. That level of Soul Energy Force was a Void Creature!! They even came to this world!? How was this possible!?

Even though his Soul Energy was unable to escape his body, he could still feel the level of the Void Creature parasitized in the Dragon Whelp’s body.

“That’s at least three Soul Rings!” He swiftly registered the level of the Void Creature that just escaped. His intuition was telling him that this fellow had probably followed the void that he entered when he came to this world.

All of a sudden, the elder White Dragon’s staff in the center moved and a white Light Beam shot out, striking accurately at the Void Creature that was trying to escape.

Hiss…

A subtle sizzling sound of burning meat could be head. The White Dragon that was parasitized by a Void Creature was instantly bound by the shot of white Light Beam, tied together as if bounded by ropes and thrown into midair.

With a swing, it directly pierced into the sharp metal needle in the middle of the circular board, instantly becoming a skewer.

Roar!!

“No!! How can I die here!?”

The Void Creature roared loudly in Void Language, but to no avail, the metal needle had penetrated his chest and blood was trickling down the needle. At the same time, the majestic gaze on top showed a look of satisfaction.

Frightened, Garen listened to the Void Creature howling as it struggled, becoming weaker and weaker. The Soul Rings of the Void Creature began to explode one by one, but the tremendous force generated was all completely suppressed by the gaze above their heads. Just like the hold of a feather, it seemed effortless.

Three Soul Rings!!!

If it was well utilized, that horrifying existence was not much different from him. Even in the Endor Civilization, it was still considered the Middle Demon Lord Level! The tyrannical existence that was able to rule several planets was actually here, skewered like a prey that was hunted down.

“Next family.” A loud rumble rang once again in Draconic Language.

Garen then only realized that the Void Creature was discovered through the one-to-one inspection as something abnormal was noticed.

He wandered around and peeped out from the gap by the side of Cocoreila’s body. He saw the other corner of the circular board, and there stood a white arched stone door. White Dragons were carrying along their Dragon Whelps through the stone door. Clearly, that was the tool used to detect Alien Souls.

Chapter 1254: Threat 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“That thing is able to detect Void Creatures, it’s highly likely to be able to detect me! What should I do?!” Garen thought frantically. As a Demon Lord based on Soul Rings, even the Void Creature with three Soul Rings was completely vulnerable under the attack, so there was no way he could make it through! Even if he resisted it, it was just the equivalent of a mixture of cheese and eggs. It would be meaningless!

On the circular board, families of White Dragons began to pass through the white door along with the Dragon Whelps. Waiting further behind the dragons, Garen watched the line in front of him get shorter and shorter. As the circular board began to turn, the white door was getting closer to him already.

“Pass.”

An Elder White Dragon that was guarded by the white door casted a glance toward the few White Dragon families that were behind.

“Hurry up,” he urged impatiently.

A White Dragon family walked toward the white door.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a figure shot out from this family and fled in the distance. Even if Garen was not a practitioner of Soul Energy, he could still clearly feel the Soul Energy that broke out this time around.

This was also a Three-Soul-Ring-Void-Creature and three of his Soul Rings instantly exploded at the same time. The force that blasted out was so immense, his speed surpassed the Elder White Dragon’s in a blink of an eye, reaching a point that no creature could ever keep pace with.

“Idiot.” The Elder Dragon that had a staff in his hand barely raised his eyes. Not even moving, he just watched as the Dragon Whelp flee.

Chi!

The symbol at the top of his staff once again shot out a beam of white light. Same as the last time, it tied the Void Creature together and pulled it back in an instant. Soon enough, the black needle on the circular board pierced right through it.

“In the eyes of the great Tiamat, all guises and lurkings shall be exposed,” the Elder Dragon spoke loudly in a Draconic Language that sounded close to singing.

All the other White Dragons piously bowed their heads to show respect. Even though some of them were of selfish dragon races who would not actually fully believe in Tiamat, they still showed respect on the surface as it was as effortless as lifting a finger for them White Dragons. After all, the only one who was truly protecting them all was still Tiamat.

The group continued to move forward.

Garen watched as the white door got closer and closer. His heart was almost at the edge of his throat already.

“What should I do!?” His brain had never worked this fast as he tried to find a way to deal with the current situation.

One by one, the White Dragon families walked into the white stone door and exit from the other side, quietly waiting at the other side of the circular board.

“It’s your turn, hurry up,” the White Dragon who was guarding the door cast a cold glance at Cocoreila.

“Yes, respected Dragon Guard,” Cocoreila responded reverently, then led the way into the white door and stepped out from the other end with her Dragon Whelps bouncing along behind her.

Garen gritted his teeth and jumped in.

Chi!!

A bright white Light Beam instantly lit up the sky.

With a bang, the entire circular board shook slightly. Garen’s sight was blinded by the white light before him.

“It’s over!” A chill washed over his head as the Soul Rings in his entire body began to shake violently. As a Demon Lord, his dignity as a whole did not allow him to be killed without the slightest resistance!

“You dare to run!” Before his sight faded, he could vaguely hear the roars of the Elder Dragon.

The white light passed far in front before his eyes over ten meters from him and landed on one of the White Dragon Whelps that was attempting to sneak out the circular board.

All of a sudden, the white flame ignited and the Dragon Whelp howled in pain. It was just a blink of an eye before it burned into white ash and was blown away by the wind, disappearing into the snow.

Garen was sweating all over as he stood in the middle of the white stone door.

“Stupid, what are you still doing here? Scram!” The Dragon gave him a tail, causing Garen to almost flip over.

Instead of being angry, he was happy.

He was actually fine!!!?

“Sure enough, it worked!” Garen let out a sigh of relief from the bottom of his heart as he looked at the Soul Ring deep in his soul.

On the other hand, he would turn into a native of this world completely.

In order to escape the crisis earlier on, he simply combined his Soul Ring with his body thoroughly. A combination as such was equivalent to the Demon Lord giving up his ability of reincarnation, merging himself completely within the shell of this creature.

If creatures die and Demon Lords die, Demon Lords would no longer have the right to simply transmigrate between worlds anymore.

This method was not something all Demon Lords knew, but an imprisonment law that Garen had learned from Shadow Dragon some time ago. It was said that such an imprisonment would imprison himself into this current body.

This was also the point he was confused about.

If the rules of the Shadow Dragon could be used, perhaps the other upper laws would be usable as well?

Garen had gotten through the crisis. Looking at the Dragon Guard that just pulled his tail, he climbed back to Cocoreila’s side quietly and waited as he began to simulate the other things he had just realized.

But unfortunately, body simulation practiced a lot of other things. Except for a couple of Living Secret Techniques, the others had to be modified before using due to the different laws.

“But this means that everything I’ve learned can be used, they’re all actually significant. They just require some slight modifications,” Garen’s crisis had passed, and so he felt brighter now.

“So it is very likely that this High-Dimensional Universe is able to accommodate all the laws of the Low-Dimensional Universe, but just because the laws here are more comprehensive and upper-leveled, creatures of a Low-Dimensional Universe may be incomplete. With that, this means that all the knowledge I’ve gained is not useless. I just need to perfect everything according to the rules here!”

Garen felt comfortable.

Between High-Dimensional and Low-Dimensional Universes, he originally guessed that there was just one difference in dimension. But now, the difference in gap did not seem that high anymore, perhaps only just half a dimension.

The Gods of this world represented the highest powers. They may be able to use High-Dimensional enslaved creatures, but they could not simply adjust space-time. According to his inherited memories, there were also come Gods who were able to travel through different space-time.

“This type of connection seems a bit like advanced space-time, but more powerful than an advanced universe,” Garen began to analyze indiscriminately.

After all, he really was almost caught and nearly became a skewer. This experience was something he never wanted have again. If he was to die in a frontal battle on a battlefield, he was just afraid of this powerless feeling that he could not understand.

“Alright, all families inspection has ended. You can all return now.” The Elder Dragon standing at the center ordered.

Then only did all the White Dragons heaved a sigh of relief. Fluttering their wings, they began to fly back to their nests along with their little ones.

Cocoreila was the same as well. Once again, she carried the three small Earth Dragons in her mouth as Garen and the other five Dragon Whelps followed behind. However, she was not heading back to the original nest, but she flew away from the snowy peak and toward the other white mountains in the distance.

“Mother, where are we going?” A Dragon Whelp asked innocently. It was the most courageous one who asked, the Dragon Whelp who was born the strongest. This fellow wanted to fight the second he was born, clearly, he had an active personality.

“We’re going to our original home. This is the Elder’s Peak, it’s not our home.” Cocoreila answered in a gentle tone. As she had three small Earth Dragons in her mouth, her speech was not clear at all.

“What about our father?” Another Dragon Whelp asked.

“I don’t know. We White Dragons have too many fathers already, I didn’t find out who my father was either. Lavido and I just broke up last year so perhaps you can call him Father,” Cocoreila answered quite hesitantly.

Garen rolled his eyes.

White Dragons’ marriages and relationships were not just complicated in general. Due to low fertility, one mother dragon may simultaneously mate with more than ten male dragons until she gets pregnant. Therefore, these White Dragons that were born would not usually know who their father is.

“Can I have milk?” A Dragon Whelp asked aloud.

“Go back and eat,” Cocoreila roared in response, “We’re still flying.”

She was flying slowly as she still had to take care of the Dragon Whelps.

But soon, she heard a groan. A Dragon Whelp, regardless of her consent, had rushed to her abdomen and started to suck on her teat.

White Dragons actually needed milk.

Garen learned a new point of view toward the world once again.

The group of Dragon Whelps instantly began to compete for the teats as there were only three of them so they had to take turns.

As for Garen, he was just rolling his eyes by the side. To ask him to compete for a teat with the group of brats, you could just forget about it. According to his inherited memories, although one could choose to drink one’s mother’s milk, a Dragon Whelp could always opt for meat directly.

The white snowy peaks moved underneath them slowly. No birds dated to invade this area as it was the dragon’s territory. A dragon’s prestige was enough to scare away any creature below Level Four, even weaker ones would be scared to the point they degrade.

Therefore, a large number of social creatures did not dare to invade the dragon race’s place of residence.

After Garen got through his crisis, he had begun to consider using his talent and powers to quickly improve his strength. This world was too dangerous.

He just used the laws of imprisonment to fuse himself into this body, but his soul was still too powerful for the body. If he was to encounter a soul-wise grandmaster, not to mention a God, just a human Necromancer or a high-ranked Wizard who was involved with the studies of souls, they would easily notice his abnormality or that something was off about him.

It was obvious that the Elder Dragon earlier on merely relied on the staff to use magic. As for why the Gods did not notice his abnormality, it was perhaps just a rough alarm system.

Garen suspected that the scan might have just been a mechanism of intimidation. It seemed that the Will of the Gods were watching over them but in reality, the Gods were probably not leisurely watching the White Dragon Clan’s baptism one by one. Although Tiamat was not loved by many of the good dragons, she was still respected by many dragon races. Her believers were broad. There were White Dragon Clans not only at the main plane but countless planes as well, it was practically impossible to actually attract the attention of the Gods.

“The strong incompatibility of my soul and flesh has to be solved as soon as possible! I’m still a hidden ticking time bomb staying here! I might be discovered any time!” Garen’s heart quickened at the thought of it. Unlike other places, the powerhouses who were experts in the studies of souls were too many over here. There was even a Soul God!

Once discovered as an Alien Soul, he may face a situation that was worse than death. Even possibly becoming experimental material to be dissected was considered a light case.

Moreover, the White Dragons still had to go through another baptism when they grow up. By that time, he may face such troubles. What if the Gods really did look around occasionally…

This time he got away because of pure luck, but not necessarily next time.

Garen quickly made up his mind.

In his inherited memories, the custom of the White Dragon Clan was to accept the newborn baptism of Tiamat when they reach the age of ten. This adult baptism was most likely to involve souls, so the chances of being discovered then would be much greater!

If this incompatibility problem was not solved, he would be discovered sooner or later!

“In ten years, this problem must be solved!”

Chapter 1255: Trouble 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The hideout was located on a faraway snowy peak at Elder’s Peak.

The snowy peak was not too high, probably just half length of Elder’s Peak at most. Large green forests surrounded them and occasionally, a few yellow trees could be seen. Huge flocks of Earth Dragons were roaming nearby. Some of these Earth Dragons were the deformed White Dragons whereas some were hybrids of Earth Dragons and other creatures. More or less, they still had the blood of a dragon.

Cocoreila brought Garen and the other Dragon Whelps to start a life here. She had thrown the three Earth Dragons off the mountain peak, leaving them to fend for themselves.

She brought the remaining five little guys into a dragon den and settled down, surrounded by the ice.

A dragon den was just like a bee’s hive. There were many huge hollows, and each of them was enough for a Dragon Whelp to live inside quietly. It acted just like a single room.

Life inside a dragon den was boring and tedious. Every ten days, Cocoreila would bring back a prey she had hunted down. Sometimes it was a giant creature which was enough for everyone to eat for a few days, sometimes it was tiny animals. Sometimes, there were still distant families of Earth Dragons.

There was no fire, so a White Dragon’s way of eating was to freeze the meat with chilled air and then chew it up. It was just like eating biscuits, crunchy and a bit fishy, but still very fresh. As for the Dragon Whelps, they have been eating such things besides the first few days when they still had milk.

Soon enough, Garen started to like this way of eating.

He lived in a small hole on the left side. All he had to do every day was just eat and sleep, move his body around after waking up, and just continue eating.

On the other hand, the other Dragon Whelps were different from him. They enjoyed messing around and fighting each other.

Furthermore, it was not just the playful kind, but real actual fights. White Dragon Mother Cocoreila, however, did not pay much attention to the Dragon Whelps’ fights. From her perspective, it was a method of training for them to hunt prey. The inherited memories clearly stated it already.

As for Garen who never participated in any of the fights, he was being antisocial in the eyes of the others. After all, there was no other dragon who was willing to get in contact with him as well.

And so, time passed day in and day out. Garen constantly searched for things and treasure that were able to improve his body’s qualities. The physique of the White Dragons in this world was too strong already.

As a Dragon Whelp, his body qualities had increased an average of ten points in just less than two months’ time!

Strength, agility, physique. This three aspects had had an average steady growth from the original one point to an average of over ten points. It was simply horrifying.

Garen still had not used his Soul Energy to nourish his body as he had already found a better use for it.

********************

Boom!

“Saone, you’ve lost! You must give your portion of meat today to me!” In the dragon den, two Dragon Whelps panted as they loosened their grip on each other. Both of them were bruised and scarred everywhere, apparently the aftermath of a fight.

On the side, two other Dragon Whelps observed silently whereas Cocoreila had gone out to hunt again. Since the Dragon Whelps were still growing, they required a huge amount of meat, hence why she had to keep hunting in order to meet the needs of the five Dragon Whelps.

“Alright, alright. I’ve let you go easy today, I wasn’t in the best condition!” Saone was the Dragon Whelp with the biggest head, but surprisingly, he could not fight against Satwo. As for Sathree and Safour, and Garen who was named as Safive, nobody could beat him, except for Garen who had never fought against him.

“Not the best condition again, how many times have you not been in your best state already? Haha…” Satwo laughed, his blue draconic eyes settling on Sathree and Safour who were standing by the side. The two little guys were immediately scared and shrunk back.

Satwo smiled in satisfaction. Apparently, he was extremely satisfied with his intimidation effect. He had finally established the first step as the leading authority among his brothers and sisters.

“After the newborn baptism, we shall begin our lives independently. Mother will no longer take care of us, and we shall have to do our own hunting by then. I propose that all five of us, brothers and sisters, should live together before we grow up.”

He said loudly, “When we are weak, we have to live in groups! This is knowledge engraved in our blood!”

“I agree.” Sathree was the first to reconcile. He was already scared of being beaten up by Satwo. It was alright if everyone’s physique was almost the same but Satwo’s muscles were too solid, and so he had a larger explosive power. If they fought one on one, even Saone with such a gigantic head could be easily flipped over. This added to the fear they had of Satwo.

“I think we should conquer the Earth Dragon creature,” suggested Saone.

“We can’t beat them.” Satwo shook his head, “I’ve sneaked down the day before and tried already, even the weakest dragon is still stronger than me.”

They were still Dragon Whelps, and even Saone who was the biggest in size was just almost as big as a wolf. It was practically impossible for them to beat those strong Earth Dragons.

As for Cocoreila, besides providing them with food, she had nothing else to do with them. Feelings in a White Dragon family was very indifferent. After a longer period of time, they would even drive others of the same kind out as they were competitors.

White Dragons were generally selfish, and Cocoreila was particularly prominent in this area. She was currently completely exhausted by the serious burden of raising five Dragon Whelps, and so she was gradually disliking these little things who get everything without working for it.

This kind of situation was not uncommon at all. A White Dragon’s fertility was not weak at all, being able to give birth after another decade to a considerable number of Dragon Whelps. That was why many Dragon Whelps were likely to be driven out of the dragon den and forced to survive alone.

Because of such dangers, Saone and the other dragons also began to think about their future lives carefully.

However, they were still two months old after all. Even if they had inherited knowledge, their minds were still not mature enough.

The four little dragons gathered together and began to discuss the arrangements for the future.

At the entrance of his small hole, Garen squatted down as he stared at his brothers and sisters below. He had been observing these Dragon Whelps for the past couple of days already and their average physique was estimated to be approximately ten points. Saone was the strongest one among all, reaching twelve points whereas Satwo was the fastest, reaching thirteen points.

The level was about there already. The world of dragon race was still indeed powerful, and they were now just ordinary whelps, which was almost equivalent to ten times of an ordinary human’s strength.

However, Garen was still using the basic human standard unit data of the previous worlds as he was still unclear of the human qualities of this world.

He crouched before the entrance of his hole and yawned.

He had a look at his current physical attributes.

‘Safive – Strength 13, agility 13, physique 11, intelligence 17. Potential 0%. Soul Limit 170.’

Safive was a name simply given by Cocorerila. The White Dragon Clan was declining more and more and if there were not a matter of a threat of survival, perhaps an organizational system like a clan would not even appear at all.

It did not matter to Garen anyway. His sole purpose of coming to this world was no any other reason than investigating the source of Mother Stream’s exhaustion. At the same time, if he could find a better road of change, he would straight away transfer as well. This world was clearly brand new and full of vitality for him.

Although dangerous, benefits also existed at the same time.

“So this is the results after two months of training.” Garen shook his head silently, “Just a little stronger than they are. Seems like the human form of training methods are not really effective for the dragon race…”

For the past two months, he had been exercising according to the way of practicing Secret Techniques. However, perhaps it was the incomplete rules, the results were not much, just slightly better than these Dragon Whelps who used the traditional way.

“Well, it’s still better than nothing. Let’s look at talent then…”

Garen settled his gaze on his own accumulated Soul Energy. The four Soul Rings, to be exact, were actually three complete perfect Soul Rings and a half Soul Ring, which generated two months’ worth of Soul Energy, all of which were accumulated by him. But not all were used directly on his body.

That was because he had discovered that after entering this world, his talents and powers seemed to have some subtle changes. They were now able to absorb his own Soul Energy to strengthen his body.

“Since when did this start?” Garen tried to recall and it seemed to have started since he completely fused his Soul Ring into his body.

“Since I can absorb Soul Energy now, I’ll have a look at the conversion efficiency of my Soul Energy into potential points.”

Garen squatted down and looked at the four Dragon Whelps below who were in the middle of a discussion as he slowly started to maneuver his accumulated Soul Energy, moving them toward the position of his talent and powers.

His talent and powers were located right in his eyes, or perhaps where his eyes were.

A tremendous surge of Soul Energy poured into his eyes rapidly.

Without blinking, Garen kept his gaze at his potential points.

Swoosh!

Sure enough, his potential points began to rise quickly, 20%… 50%… 110%… 150%…

The numbers jumped sharply.

His Soul Energy consumption was also alarmingly big.

After ten minutes, all his accumulated Soul Energy had completely entered the position of his talent, and fully converted into potential points.

“521%. That’s still okay.” Garen looked at his own data, a five-point attribute point could be used. It had only been two months’ time so it was pretty good already.

“Although the stronger the body, the more difficult it is to upgrade later, but at least I can still pass through my weak youth stage quickly.”

Garen looked at the Dragon Whelps below and added the five-point attribute point fairly to his strength and speed with zero hesitation. Cocoreila had become increasingly impatient with raising them so they were likely to be chased out of the dragon den to live independently at any time. Maybe they might be even eaten by dangerous creatures before they even live to their newborn baptism. For now, he should prioritize his own survival skills to protect himself.

Hunting was the only way to protect one’s growth and development.

After the addition, Garen looked at his attributes.

‘Safive — Strength 16, agility 15, physique 11, intelligence 17. Potential 21%. Soul Limit 170’

Swoosh!

Garen waved his claw, making a sharp whistling sound.

The laws of this world were extremely abnormal. Such physical qualities were not as strong as it was in other worlds but it was already suppressed here. Even Air Slash could not be used at all.

Garen continued crouching reluctantly as he waited for Cocoreila to return with food.

The sky gradually darkened and soon, it was nighttime. The sky turned dark already.

The dragon den was empty, only a few pieces of gem equipment that were collected by the White Dragon shimmered faintly.

Garen had heard Cocoreila introduce it once. This luminous equipment was a solidified Level-0 trickery lighting system. Trickery was a sort of spellcraft that intrigued him, that urged him to want to understand this power system. But obviously, the Adult White Dragon was not concern about this aspect. The Dragon Race was naturally immune to all spellcraft below Level Four, so far apart from the Level-Five Great Wizards. The other low-ranked Wizards were not even able to break them at all.

So that was not worth paying attention whatsoever.

Even the scales of the Young Whelps now were immune to Level-One spellcraft.

“Why isn’t Mother back yet?” Saone asked in a hushed tone, “Usually she’s back by this time already.”

“Maybe she was caught in the middle of something,” Satwo guessed.

“There are no creatures around that can actually threaten Mother though,” Safour did not like to talk much, but it seemed that his intelligence in analysis was better.”

“Just wait for a minute, maybe she’ll come back in a moment,” Saone suggested.

And so, the other Dragon Whelps continued waiting.

According to his inherited memories, family relationship between White Dragons as it is gave off serious insecurity.

Time passed quickly and a few of the Dragon Whelps took a nap and woke up once again. By the time they realized it, the sky was already bright again…

But mother dragon was still not back.

“Mother’s still not back,” Satwo said in disappointment.

“Maybe there’s too much food from this hunt and she’s trying to figure out how to get them back,” Sathree responded in a hushed tone.

“Yes, it happened the last time too,” Saone regained his confidence. “Satwo, let’s go play wrestling!”

Satwo agreed happily and the two Dragon Whelps began to mess around.

As for Safour, who was more intelligent, got somewhat worried. He stood at the side of the cave and looked out from time to time, hoping to see their mother’s huge figure.

Garen was still crouched in his own cave. He had already realized that something was wrong and that Cocoreila had probably abandoned them.

This was not uncommon at all in the Colorful Dragon Clans. Among Colorful Dragons, White Dragons were the weakest, but their fertility was the strongest. In addition to their extremely selfish nature, many mothers of White Dragons would abandon their whelps at the dragon eggs stage. There were also those who only abandon their whelps after the eggs were hatched, it was nothing unusual at all.

Hu…

He sighed.

From the treasures that were decreasing day by day in the dragon den, he had already been aware of it. Cocoreila obviously planned this earlier on already, transferring the treasures out bit by bit from the dragon den. Now she may have completely abandoned this few Dragon Whelps of hers.

Relative to the Earth Dragon creatures and other dangerous beasts in the outside world, including humans, Dragon Whelps were fragile. Once they were discovered, especially by human beings, getting caught to become a contracted beast was considered a good case as so often would they be slaughtered and broken down into various materials to be made into spellcraft objects.

That was because besides special groups of creatures, human beings rarely domesticated dragons of Colorful Dragon Clans, especially the most selfish White Dragons.

Fortunately, this place was not far away from the White Dragon Clan. They were still under the protection of the White Dragon Clan so they would not be in much danger. They could survive by hunting for themselves.

“Let’s wait for a while more,” Saone’s voice was heard again from below.

Garen got up and returned to his hole to rest.

In a blink of an eye, two days passed already and Cocoreila had yet to return.

Even Sathree who had always believed in their Mother was shaken by now.

“We’ve been abandoned,” Safour was almost sure of his own speculation.

The other three Dragon Whelps remained silent.

Chapter 1256: Trouble 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen had just finished training and was just about to lie down and take a break.

He had temporarily reformed a set of common combat techniques that was suitable for Dragon Whelps. There was no specific name to it, just a simple exercise that trained different body combat skills.

At his level, even if he had a different body, his melee ability of the same stage would still be the strongest. He was confident that even if the four Dragons Whelps outside combined forces, he could easily deal with them without even using his abnormal physical qualities.

Although they had simple fighting techniques in their inherited memories, but knowledge was still knowledge. After all, one must put in the effort to train in order to convert it into one’s instinct.

Just as he sat down, he saw Saone and the other Dragon Whelps were squeezing their way into his hole.

“Safive, we’re going out to hunt, do you want to come along?” Satwo had clearly established his position as the leader, standing at the forefront as he yelled.

“Hunt?” Garen stood up, “What are you planning to kill?”

“I don’t know, but we have to go out and search for something to eat,” Satwo answered with a look of confusion. Clearly, he did not know what to kill as well.

None of the creatures that Mother had hunted were ones they could realistically deal with.

“If we don’t go out, we’ll starve to death here.” Safour seemed to be more sensible, “Either way, we can only go out.”

Garen certainly understood this. Now that Cocoreila’s Draconic Aura was still here, no ferocious Earth Dragon creatures or any other powerful creatures would dare to invade the surroundings. They were still safe, but they still had to leave this place as soon as possible.

It was just the matter of where to go and how. These were the things that should be carefully considered.

They just did not dare to live in mountain caves as this anymore. These places were often visited by fierce birds, they could not possibly take care of themselves.

After slight contemplation, Garen then agreed to go out altogether.

The group of Dragon Whelps fluttered their wings and flew out of the dragon den swiftly. They knew that it was unlikely of them would return anymore.

Under Garen’s directions, the five Dragon Whelps flew into the layers of clouds, using the clouds to cover their bodies. The nearby region was the White Dragon’s domain so it was unlikely that they would encounter other ferocious birds, hence it was safe for them.

For Garen, it did not matter to him where he goes. Either way, he just needed time so that he could use his Soul Energy to constantly transform his attribute points to strengthen his body. The efficiency of converting Soul Energy was not bad at all, requiring not much of consumption. Furthermore, it was different from before. His Soul Energy used to be evenly spread throughout his body, but after being converted into attribute points, Garen could control his preferred attributes.

As for the leadership authority of the several Dragon Whelps, he was too lazy to bother. It was just nothing in his eyes.

Large green forests loomed beneath the clouds and without realization, the group of Dragon Whelps had flown in the direction of a colder region. Garen remembered that this was the direction of the White Dragon Clan Elder’s Peak.

Roar!!

All of a sudden, a loud roar of a dragon sounded from below.

A white shadow rushed into the sky, crashing right into the Dragon Whelps, causing them to fall apart from each other.

“Get out of my domain.” This was an Adult White Dragon. Rising from the snowy peak below, he was now hovering in the air, bellowing right in front of the group of Dragon Whelps that were broken apart.

The five Dragon Whelps, including Garen, was knocked senseless by the immense airstreams.

Garen kept his mind calm and collected. As he stabilized his body, he tried to figure out the value of this Adult White Dragon.

“Strength and speed should be at least thirty points and above! Below forty points!” He quickly came up with a slightly accurate data.

Too strong…!

Garen then looked at his own value. His strongest attribute was only seventeen points of intelligence. Just a mere struck of the airstream and he had lost balance already.

His eyelids twitched for a bit. Garen and the other four Dragon Whelps could only turn around and leave, they could no longer stay her any bit longer. The Adult White Dragon behind them roared loudly once more before flying back to his snowy peak. Garen clearly sensed the death glare shot behind them. He knew that if they met an Adult White Dragon in the wild, they would all become slaves of the dragon or perhaps food.

If it was not because of the fact that White Dragons liked killing each other, with their fertility, they could have long dominated the Colorful Dragon Clan.

Returning along the same path was basically impossible.

“What should we do now?” Saone asked.

“We are going to hunt,” Satwo answered firmly.

“But what can we hunt?” Safour also issued a question. “What can we possibly hunt?”

“We’re too weak,” Sathree felt helpless and disheartened once again.

“No, we can go and have a look in the forest, perhaps we can find something to eat,” Garen spoke up. He did not want to mess around with these brats anymore. The appearance of the White Dragon had made him realize that this world was no less dangerous than any other places, and perhaps even more dangerous.

“Forest?” Satwo looked at Garen, “Safive, have you been to the forest? There are Elves there, and giant bears. We’re not their opponents at all.”

“You don’t just casually encounter giant bears and Elves in all forests…” Garen was completely speechless. The dragon race inherited memories only shown dangerous attempts into the mind, but not much of the specific details. They mentioned the forest, but they only let the dragons be aware of the dangerous creatures in it.

Therefore, Dragon Whelps would not know that there were weak creatures as well in the forest.

“I’ve realized that Safive is more certain of his own judgment,” Safour seemed to observe Garen’s difference.

“So what? I’m the boss!” Satwo waved his claws.

“Alright, alright. You’re the boss. But we’re heading to the forest now,” Garen nodded casually.

“Yes, we’re going to the forest,” Satwo repeated. This was their only choice. In the case that all dragons had no plans or ideas, this was the only path they could choose.

As they flew in an unfamiliar direction, the surrounding temperature was getting warmer and warmer.

Large hawks and birds gradually began to appear below them.

“We have to go down, there will be a lot of powerful birds here that we can’t deal with,” Garen suggested. He had noticed a giant eagle earlier on that had wings about ten meters big and its strength and speed were estimated to be twenty points and above. It was terrible.

“Alright, let’s go down,” Satwo immediately accepted Garen’s suggestion.

The group of Dragon Whelps descended quickly, finding a gap in the dark green forest below.

Several deer that were drinking water quickly ran away.

“Food!” At the side of the deer, Satwo yelled and pounced forward. However, he immediately tripped over a branch of a tree at the side and fell to the ground.

The other Dragon Whelps by the side broke into laughter.

Garen, however, walked aside alone and observed the woods around him.

He immediately saw footprints at the edge of the creek. The footprints have yet disappeared and from the looks of it, it was a human footprint.

“Human…” His vigilance was immediately heightened. He was a human being himself. From his inherited memories, he knew the how precious dragon skin was for human beings to be used as materials. From there, he also knew that if he ever encountered a group of human beings, he would surely become a moving treasure in the eyes of the other party. Once the news spread out, it would definitely attract more humans.

“This is troublesome. There seem to be human activities around here… So close to White Dragon Clan,” An idea popped into Garen’s mind.

Howl!

A leopard who was drinking at the creek looked up and snarled at the Dragon Whelps, obviously unhappy that the Dragon Whelps were interrupting him drinking water.

“But we are the great dragon race!” Saone was furious that a mere small leopard actually dared to provoke its dignity.

It fluttered its wings and flew toward the leopard, squirting out a mouthful of Chill.

With a pounce, the leopard easily dodged the white Chill, but Saone was quicker than him. Innate qualities of the dragon race were basically impossible for this ordinary leopard to overcome. After a while, Saone threw himself forward and pressed onto its head as it struggled on the ground.

“That’s too easy, haha!” Saone laughed. Its strength was way stronger than this grownup leopard, pinning it down effortlessly. “How should we eat this?”

“Let’s freeze it first!” The Dragon Whelps rushed forward. If it was not because of their young age and still did not have a Draconic Aura, the leopard would not have probably bumped into them and had straight away fled.

After the first prey, there would be the second one, and soon enough, a wild boar appeared in their field of vision.

The wild boar was decked in a thick yellow rock armor. Almost as tall as a human, it looked mighty powerful.

Facing the wild boar head on, the Dragon Whelps were unable to cope with its strength at all. After breaking multiple huge trees, the Dragon Whelps joined forces to fly around the wild boar in an attempt of making it dizzy. The wild boar indeed lost its balance and Satwo sped up immediately, crushing the head of the wild boar with its claws.

And that was another meal. The Dragon Whelps divided the food together and Satwo was awarded the huge head.

However, apart from Garen who was on his toes the entire time, nobody else noticed that in the woods not far behind, a group of humans wearing light armor were silently moving in their direction.

“It’s Dragon Whelps…” An old man dressed in a close-fitting long robe squatted down and examined the remaining bones of the leopard. “This leopard was a Level Three Lightning Leopard and its speed is already extremely fast, but it was still killed.”

He paused, “From speed, strength and the claw marks, it should be the works of Dragon Whelps. The White Dragon Clan’s just nearby, Adult White Dragons wouldn’t simply eat their prey on the spot. Moreover, there should be more than one Dragon Whelp, and they would make a bunch of good materials.”

“Your Excellency, should we search for the dragon den first, or kill these Dragon Whelps first?” A man in green armor with Greatswords in both his hands whispered.

“Our priority is to kill an Adult White Dragon, and the rest shall be discussed later on. But then again, it is rare to encounter Dragon Whelps that are so far away from their group…” The elder Wizard sank into deep thought, “How about this, Karel.”

“Here, Your Excellency Sara.” A scrawny old man in a black robe walked out from the troop. His hand held a cypress staff that had a skill on its top that looked eerie and terrifying.

“You can bring this two White Silvers over and get rid of this nest of Dragon Whelps. You can take sixty percent of the materials,” the elder Wizard commanded.

“As you wish, Your Excellency.” the creepy old man smiled.

“Be careful of the appearance of Adult White Dragons. These Dragon Whelps are just Level Four, be careful of their ice spits, they’re actually just slightly stronger than Level-Four beasts,” the elder Wizard said.

“I’m already a Level-Five Great Wizard, Your Excellency,” the creepy old man said confidently.

“Go then.”

Chapter 1257: Stable 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“We must leave this place.”

Garen got up and said to the Dragon Whelps who were drinking water. He did not want to leave alone. He was still too weak by himself and needed these Dragon Whelps to move around with him, not just for power, but as a cover for his identity. Once his abnormality was discovered, problems were likely to arise and he would be easily noticed.

“Why do we have to leave?” Satwo asked.

“There are humans here,” Garen whispered. “If they’re moving around this area, they obviously have some sort of purpose.”

“Humans? We can kill them straight away. They’re just food,” Saone thought otherwise.

“We may be able to kill them in the future, but not right now.” Garen shook his head. “Are you guys moving?”

“No, there is water source here. Where there’s water, animals are bound to come by. Therefore, if we stay here, we’ll be able to find good food,” Safour said with a witty tone.

“As long as there’s endless food, we will continue to advance!” Sathree exclaimed loudly.

“As long as we advance, we’ll be able to go find Mother!” Saone continued.

“And as long as we’re able to find Mother, we’ll all be safe!” Satwo waved his claws.

Bang!

A huge claw that was clenched into a fist landed on his eyes.

Instantly, Satwo stumbled backward. Before he could figure out what was going on, he saw Garen flinging another punch towards him.

“No! You…”

Bang!

Both of his eyes were completely bruised.

Saone was furious that he actually dared to hit the boss! He rushed forward and tried to entangle Garen into close combat but it was pointless.

Garen took a step back and simply kicked his leg causing his knee to land right on Saone’s abdomen.

Oh!

Both Saone and Satwo fell on their butts. Their heads were spinning and they were completely stunned.

“Now I’m the boss,” Garen walked to the front of both dragons and waved his claws.

“Alright… Alright, you’re the boss,” Saone was convinced right away.

There was still a look of dissatisfaction in Satwo’s eyes, but from the strength and speed of Garen’s movements, he was obviously no match for Garen. With a huff, he gave in reluctantly.

“Now, we’re leaving this place,” Garen confirmed his authority as the leader and proposed decisively to leave.

Sathree and Safour were shocked by Garen’s sudden burst of powers.

The group of Dragon Whelps sorted out the leopard meat cubes and brought them one by one, tied them up with large leaf vines from the trees before flying away wobbly into the distance.

Roar!

Suddenly, a low rumble was heard from the forest below.

Something dark darted out from the woods. It seemed to be a gigantic, black wild boar.

The wild boar was covered with a black iron armor, rushing straight towards the group of Dragon Whelps. It had blood-red eyes and it reeked badly.

“Rise!” Garen shouted.

The wild boar was at least twice their size, rushing over like a car. He did not want to fight against this fellow.

All the Dragon Whelps immediately increased their heights but a beam of grey-white light shot out from the back of the wild boar, hitting Saone’s hind legs.

“Ahhh!” Saone howled in pain.

The ray was actually able to break through the dragon skin’s magic defense. Although they were only Dragon Whelps now, their epidermis was still able to immunize Level-One magic and even a certain resistance towards some Level-Two spellcraft. However, looking at Saone right now, the ray was clearly far more than just a Level-Two spellcraft.

After struggling for a while, Saone completely lost the ability to flap his wings and fell from the sky.

The other Dragon Whelps were shocked. At this moment, the selfish nature of White Dragons was truly manifested. All the Dragon Whelps ignored Saone who had fallen and flew away frantically.

Garen cast a glance towards Saone who was below him. The gigantic wild boar had its head up waiting for it to fall and there was a creepy old guy in a grey robe wandering beside the wild boar.

“Human…” Garen’s heart shook. His strength and speed were incomparable to Saone. Moreover, Saone’s body was temporarily frozen as he continued falling. Before he touched the ground, Garen once again fluttered his wings and fiercely squirted a mouthful of Chill towards the old fellow.

When the white Chill rushed to the old man, it seemed to be blocked by a transparent barrier.

The old man smiled and extended his right hand. A Void Shadow of a white skeletal hand could be seen around his entire palm, wrapping his palm within it. Looking from afar, it seemed as if his entire arm was just skeletal.

The skeletal arm pierced through the screen and grabbed onto Saone who was trying to escape.

Garen who was in the sky immediately felt the intense threat and darkness from the white skeletal arm. It felt as if he was standing at the cliff of an abyss, the cold feeling surged straight into his mind.

Garen could feel his hair standing on end and his Soul Ring instinctively judged his reaction. This old man was indeed very strong! Definitely not something he could deal with right now!

Without hesitation, Garen turned around and fled. Soon enough, Garen caught up with Satwo and Sathree who were in front of him and they quickly left the place. As for Saone, the odds were against him.

The old man below hesitated as he looked at the fleeing White Dragon Whelps.

“There’s actually more than one. That’s unfortunate, they’d make such good material.”

Grabbing Saone in his hand, his sharp but bent fingertips pierced through the Dragon Whelp’s skin.

Saone screamed in pain, wailing loudly as he felt the excruciating pain. White blood flowed from the wound and dripped on the ground, covering the small meadow with a white layer of frost.

After being caught by this old Wizard, he could not fight back at all.

********************

Garen followed the Dragon Whelps as they flew and soon enough, everyone was back together except Saone who was nowhere to be seen.

The group of dragons flew along their original path, staying silent the entire time.

“Saone… is he going to die?” Satwo whispered. No creatures could actually stay calm the first time they faced death.

“The outside world is too dangerous…” With his head bent, Safour spoke as his body trembled.

This was also the first time Garen felt that this world was not just generally dangerous. Before that, there was a God’s inspection, and now he had just encountered an old man who looked strong and abnormal. Besides knowing some human combat techniques himself, his other strengths could only be used after the completion of the laws. However, it would take too much time to complete the laws and he could not even guarantee his own safety right now.

“There are only two options,” Garen said in a low tone.

“What two options?” Satwo asked quickly. He found that among them, Garen was the most assertive and most knowledgeable.

Sathree and Safour immediately looked at him as well.

“Humans have appeared in our surroundings and obviously they’re not here to just hang around leisurely. Look at the man’s strength just now, there’s no way he was here just to deal with us Dragon Whelps. If we want to be safe, we have to get far away from this place. We should find the White Dragon Clan Elder’s Peak and tell them about our findings. There’s a specialized Dragon Whelp Breeding Institute in the clan, we can go in and learn to fight.”

Garen carefully explained his plan.

“I’m planning to go to the clan’s breeding institute, what about you guys?”

The other Dragon Whelps were as clueless as headless flies. Saone had just died right before their eyes and they were frightened to the point where they had lost their definite views. They simply listened to Garen and set off in the direction of the clan.

******************

After they safely arrived at the White Dragon Clan, Garen explained their situation to the White Dragon guard and they obtained the entry permit.

It was evident that the White Dragons had long known that humans were nearing by and did not refuse the Dragon Whelps who came into hiding. Besides Garen and his group of Dragon Whelps, there were other White Dragons who had brought along their Dragon Whelps to seek shelter nearby the clan’s Elder’s Peak.

Due to the disappearance of their mother, Cocoreila, Garen and the other Dragon Whelps had arranged to enter the breeding institute, as he wished for.

The White Dragon Clan’s Dragon Whelp Breeding Institute was an organization set up for Dragon Whelps who had lost their parents or families because they did not bother about their Dragon Whelps. There were over fifty Elder White Dragons in the entire race and five of them were in charge of looking after the Dragon Whelps. There were also many dragon beasts and Earth Dragons around who were managed by the White Dragons as a safety precaution.

Inside the institution, the Dragon Whelps were taught how to fight, how to hunt, and what creatures to look out for that were threats to them. They were also taught about the environment needed to advance, the conditions, and the storage of miscellaneous food.

What attracted Garen’s interest was the practice of spellcraft.

When they were selecting their classes, Garen chose the Arcane Art Course without hesitation instead of the Actual Combat Course that most White Dragons would choose.

For White Dragons, as long as they stepped into adulthood, they would have dragon scales that would immunize all spellcraft below Level Four and their powerful Draconic Aura would be equivalent to a no-loss Level-Three spellcraft energy field that was able to control large groups of Earth Dragons as well as dragons. Moreover, they would have several Ice-type spellcraft of Level-Six Ice Mirror Art and two kinds of Frost Breath.

Every Wizard that faced an Elder White Dragon with such strong constitution and terrifying powers had the ability to reduce or even exempt the effects of the spells that were Level Four and above. With the swipe of a tail, the force could actually go up to a Level Six creature’s top strength. No spellcraft screen or Wizard’s armor could possibly resist such a strong force. The instantaneous burst of power would be as much as a Level Five lethal spell.

This kind of horrific talent was why the White Dragons, even some of the dragon race, rarely focused on learning Spellcraft. Only those Elder Dragon whose lives were too long would choose to practice Spellcraft because they were too bored.

“Are you really sure that you’re choosing Spellcraft Course? Don’t blame me for not reminding you that the most suitable path for us dragon race is to first improve our melee ability and only choose Spellcraft when we can protect ourselves because by that time, we’ll have sufficient time to practice Accumulation,” the young dragon that was in charge of registration reminded. “Also, we won’t be responsible for your meals. In the process of learning, all of you will learn to hunt stronger preys and through this process, elementary Spellcraft is completely useless for dragons.”

Garen nodded as a sign that he understood.

“I understand.”

“No… You don’t.” The young dragon shook her head, her long slender snake-like neck made her as beautiful as a white swan. Clearly, this was a female dragon.

“Even though we are from the dragon race and we have a vast amount of spirit power, this doesn’t mean that we can advance quickly. Like humans, we need at least ten years or so to reach the standards of Level Four, and this is if you’re talented. If you don’t have talent, it’ll take at least sixty or seventy years. As for Level Four Spellcraft, it’ll only cause a small damage to Adult Dragons. It’s very weak!” She emphasized once more.

“I understand.” Garen had known about this already. “That’s why I’ve also signed up for Combat Course.”

Stunned, the young dragon stared at Garen carefully.

“Alright then, since you’ve already made your decision.” With a few strokes, she wrote down Garen’s name on the paper. Not Safive, but Garen.

Ever since they got away from Cocoreila, Garen had changed back to his original name.

“We’ll conduct recruitment applications every once in a while to enter different environments to train Actual Combat. If you die, don’t blame me for not informing you,” the young dragon said in a low tone.

Garen smiled.

“May I have your name?” This was the first time he had encountered such a kind-hearted fellow in the White Dragon Race.

Chapter 1258: Stable 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Ola. The name’s Ola. We don’t have many dragons inside the spellcrafting course as we have only about a dozen Dragon Whelps. While our classes are flexible, our examinations are held on a timely basis. You’ll be informed on a monthly basis on the stone inside the Elder’s Peak,” Ola explained. “We need to receive something in return for passing down our knowledge and techniques to you guys. In this world, knowledge, and techniques are not to be passed down for free. Hence, you’ll need to work for the clan in exchange for them.”

“What’s the job about?” Garen understood the concept behind. The selfish White Dragon Clan would not give them anything without a reason.

“Battle.” Ola’s explanation was clear and simple. “With the humans or other living beings. This is to expand our territories. If you accept the terms, please press your claw here.” He placed a leather paper in front of Garen.

Garen then went through the contract written in Draconic Language.

Then, he pressed his claw onto it. Henceforth, his life was bound by the clan until he turned into an adult.

This was unavoidable. Despite being much stronger than typical living creatures, the hatred he could attract was far more than the typical living creatures. Without the clan’s protection, he would not be able to go anywhere more than ten kilometers.

Rumor had it that the humans had decided to build a colony nearby the clan’s location and they seemed to be planning a fight with the clan to the death.

Garen flew out of the registration office after dismissing himself from Ola. He went directly towards the combat course for registration. He then returned to the emergency assembly point where he noticed Satwo and the other two dragons already there waiting for him. Since they had only registered for one course, they were much faster than Garen.

“The instructor is Instructor Dragon. There will be an inquiry day every three days and we can go and inquire about anything related to combat. However, we only have half a day to ask the questions. Then, we will have a monthly examination.” Safour’s question was extremely concise and clear.

“Rumor has it that those humans that had killed Saone had decided to stay and not leave the area. This is too dangerous. They’re not even scared of the clan!” Satwo shouted.

A group of Dragon Whelps was chattering noisily between a stone crevice in the snowy peak.

Adult White Dragons and many Dragon Whelps could occasionally be seen flying past the gap of the snowy peak. They were just a group of inconspicuous members.

“We must work hard,” Safour said. “Let’s ignore the humans. I’ve already asked and I found out that less than five out of a hundred Dragon Whelps can reach adulthood safely. Most of them would either be caught and slaughtered, not strong enough or careless before reaching adulthood. We don’t have a guardian since our mother is no longer around.”

What he said was the truth. Garen and the rest were a group of fragile beings without the protection from their kin. The Elder’s Peak would not protect them unless they were nearby the Elder’s Peak. This was impossible as they were required to finish their missions in exchange for knowledge. However, they had to leave the proximity to complete their mission. It was an infinite cycle.

Garen understood the situation best as he had even inquired regarding the overall situation of the humans stationed outside. They were a group of powerful Wizards from the nearby Deladia Empire. Their leader was a Level Seven Great Wizard named Gushan. Since his arrival, he had already gotten into a conflict with a White Dragon’s family and he almost killed an adult White Dragon without going all out.

Despite this incident, the White Dragon Clan did not dare to wage war against him as Gushan was being backed by the enormous Deidala Empire. Rumor had it that this human race empire had quite a few Level Seven Great Wizards in their arsenal, dozens of them. They even had an even higher ranked Eternal Blazer. Only the top Wizards who were Level Eight and above could be crowned as the Eternal Blazer. Only the Ancient Dragons from the Dragon Clan could face against such existence, which strength was better than the Level Seven Great Wizards by leaps and bounds.

Hence, the clan could only hold their grudge even when one of the Adult White Dragons was almost killed. The innate selfish personality of the White Dragons did not allow them to put their lives on the line unless they benefited from it. In addition, the Deidala Empire was simply an existence that they could not fight against.

This clan was not under the care of an Ancient Dragon and what they had were just a few old Dragon Priests. The Evil Dragon Goddess Tiamat would never show herself when they fought against the humans as she once had her wings both wounded by the human’s God of War.

*************

Time flew as spring passed in a blink of an eye and the scorching hot summer arrived.

Garen had started gaining knowledge and techniques from both of the courses that he attended.

The combat course syllables were very easy and hardly consumed his energy. His main focus was the arcane art course as he had placed all of his attention it.

There were at least ten other Dragon Whelps that were as obsessed as him towards Spellcraft as they sat together in a valley somewhere in the snowy peak.

Garen was sitting on the right as he listened to the teenage dragon’s lecture quietly.

It was out of his expectation that Safour had enrolled in the same arcane art course as him. However, Safour had to give up on the combat course as he was not as energetic as Garen. The former was sitting on a stool carved from ice behind the latter as he listened intently to the lecture.

Despite the blizzard howling outside, it did not affect the teenage dragon’s boisterous voice.

“Level 0 Spellcraft is also known as Level 0 Trickery. Its application is very narrow. Other than performances, its general use is to determine the quality of a Wizard’s Spirit Power. However, it is the very foundation of every Spellcraft, hence, it is a step that we have to take,” the teenage dragon said loudly.

“While there are a total of fifty-six types of traditional Level 0 Trickery, we only need to be able to use ten types to fully master the basic energy manipulation for all types. These would be your foundation after selecting the sect in the future.”

The teenage dragon reached out its claw as a small ball of light lit up above it.

“This is an Illumination Spell.” He started wavering its arm but the ball of light remained stationary as it was grasped within the latter’s palm. “I used the snowball I have condensed as an illuminating object. Then, I cast the Illumination Spell on it and this is the end result.”

The Dragon Whelps had witnessed many objects that had been cast with Illumination Spell by their own family members. They were very calm and quiet as it was a given that they were not surprised by such a small trick.

Then, the teenage dragon started explaining the means to regulate the Spirit Power as he cast a simple Illumination Spell.

Garen soon understood the concept of Spellcraft as he listened attentively to the explanation.

In essence, Spellcraft used the basis of Spirit Power to draw the subtle energy from the universe. The latter could be categorized into different types which would result in a variety of simple and complex derivative alterations. Hence, this would naturally form Spellcraft Systems of different types and levels.

It was equivalent to a chemical chain reaction. When a Wizard wished for a specific chemical reaction, he would then required to follow the sequence as they put it the specified material.

The same could be said about Spellcraft. The final form of the Spellcraft was an end result of reactions. In order to create the desired end result, one would need to focus on their Spirit Power to balance and guide different types of energies to collide, fuse and react together. A complicated reaction would occur, achieving the final effect of Spellcraft.

The variety of energies in the air would be equivalent to the different ingredients required for a chemical reaction. The role of the Spirit Power was to control how the ingredients were introduced, such as the number of ingredients required, the methods of mixing and leading them together.

“… Hence, we need to focus once we release a spell. As it is a channeling process, it will be hard to continue channeling once the process is interrupted or you’ve missed the time to react,” the teenage dragon explained the theory behind Spellcraft.

“What is Spirit Power?” A Dragon Whelp stood up and asked loudly.

“Spirit Power is the amount of your concentration.” The teenage dragon smiled, revealing his white sharp fangs. “You’re placing all of your Spirit Power onto me as you’re paying full attention to my lecture. Since you’re paying attention to me with all of your senses, the moment I released an enhanced Illimunation Spell…”

Pew!

Suddenly, a blinding ball of light exploded from the teenage dragon’s hand.

Wow!~

An alarming cry was hard.

It seemed that the enhanced Illuminating Spell had considered the Dragon Whelps’ endurance. Despite the consideration, the group of Dragon Whelps was blinded by it as they screamed.

Garen managed to evade the ambushing attack.

“Alright let’s take a rest. Everyone is free to do their own things and we will continue when the hourglass is two thirds through.” The teenage dragon then took out a golden hourglass and placed it on the snowy floor. Then, the black fine sands started to flow from the top to the bottom.

Garen and the other Dragon Whelps rubbed their eyes as the blinding flash was very impressive.

Garen sat alone on the stool and started to recall the situation around here recently since he was bored.

The clan and the Deidala Empire had seemed to come to an agreement as the adult dragons were no longer being attacked. The people from the Deidala Empire had, in fact, stopped their attacks on the Dragon Whelps as well. Instead, they had started building something deep inside the forest.

According to Ola, There were wars occurring at the border of Deidala Empire as two major empires decided to invade the Deidala Empire at the same time. It was very likely that they might come to an agreement with the high ranking elder dragons of the Elder’s Peak, where the White Dragon Clan might assist the Deidala Empire by participating in the war while they received protection from the Empire in return.

He pondered as he glanced at the Dragon Whelps around him. He wondered how many Dragon Whelps would survive from this war.

The Dragon Whelps from the White Dragon Clan was never valuable as the White Dragons were too good at breeding once they were matured. In addition to that, it would require many years for the Dragon Whelps to mature and the price was simply too much.

“How troublesome… To improve and reach equilibrium with the soul within ten years is too difficult. I need to think of a plan or else this world’s mystery is the only path I can take.”

Garen started frowning unconsciously.

“Garen! Garen!” Safour, who was behind Garen, patted on the latter’s wings.

“What’s wrong?”

“Satwo has delivered our food to us,” Safour whispered.

Garen suddenly understood the situation.

He did not have enough time to go out and hunt for his own food lately as the two courses had consumed most of his time. At times like this, Satwo, who was already impressed with Garen had decided to share a portion of his food with Garen. It was the same case for Sathree as well.

These two Dragon Whelps felt Garen had his own definite views of his own. He was extremely calm even when they encountered a powerful Wizard back then. Their impressions towards him had changed since then.

Garen and Safour stood up as they walked to the entrance of the valley. There, they saw frozen food on the ground which was placed by Satwo and Sathree. They stared at Garen and Safour from afar before turning around and flying away into the distance.

Both of them walked towards the food and started to gobble them up quickly. Safour, on the other hand, basked under Garen’s glory as he ate along.

Garen had become the leader of this group of Dragon Whelps as he had gained both mental and physical recognition of the other Dragon Whelps.

Although the White Dragons were selfish, they would still listen to the stronger ones as such was the law of nature.

“Let’s eat up,” Garen took huge bites after bites as he munched on the raw meat as he quietly thought about other stuff.

Chapter 1259: Mission 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He had been in the clan for some time. However, he could not find a better way to increase his attribute points at a faster pace other than the most primitive way which was to nourish it with his Soul Energy.

Garen quickly finished the meats before going back to the class. The content of the Arcane Art Courses was not much as it required the dragon whelps to train on their own most of the time.

Hence, the class was dismissed rather quickly.

After Garen bade goodbye to Safour, he went towards the Combat Course. Coincidentally, both courses did not clash against one another as one was in the morning whereas the other was during the afternoon.

The Combat Courses was much more lively than Arcane Art Course. Although it was one of more than ten Combat Courses, it already had at least twenty dragon whelps.

Similarly, the class was held inside a cold and windy ice valley. There was a huge disc-shaped platform at the center. The platform was also known as the Battle Arena and it was surrounded by many stools that could be used for resting. There were also a few dragon caves which had unknown purposes. These caves had many icy blue stalagmites by the entrances and they had been used as decorations by the White Dragons as they gave off blue illumination. These stalagmites were very valuable towards the humans as they contained nourishment that could enhance their bodies. This was because it had fused with the dragon’s aura for a long period of time.

Garen mixed himself among a few Dragon Whelps as he flew into the ice valley in low profile. He looked around and realized that the teacher had yet to arrive. However, there were quite a number of Dragon Whelps who had already arrived. Some of them were flying and fooling around in a corner while some were sitting quietly as they ate with their heads down. There were also some chattering among themselves in groups.

“Hey Garen!” A light blue-scaled Dragon Whelp flew over and greeted him.

“Leona? Is there anything you need?” Garen gave her a cold shoulder.

“Can’t I find you to play together if nothing is going on?” Dragon Whelp Leona said unhappily. “Come and see the Snow Dragon I’ve built!”

She then happily pointed at the Snow Dragon nearby. However, Garen viewed it as a carrot no matter how he looked at it.

“Ugly…” He commented on it casually.

“What do you mean ugly!?” Leona was unsatisfied with his comment.

“It is ugly. I never argue with other dragons,” Garen said casually as he went to his seat.

There were three Dragon Whelps pushing and yelling at a weak and small Dragon Whelp near his seat.

Garen ignored them as he sat down. The stools and tables here were mimicked from the humans. Although the designs were simple, it was solidly built.

It was not the first time he saw Dragon Whelps bullying other Dragon Whelps. However, as long as he was not involved in it, he would not bother speaking to these kids. These Dragon Whelps did not dare mess with him because of his firm muscles and lustrous scales. It was the reason why he had a peaceful life thus far.

Leona flew towards him and sat in front of him as he sat down. They had been designated as partners in the Combat Course as Garen was obviously the best in terms of physical attributes during the Combat Course’s trial. It was the higher up’s intention to train Leona together with Garen as Leona was, in fact, the daughter of the clan’s Elder Dragon. Hence, it was normal for her to have special privileges.

Despite Garen wanting to ignore this little girl, he had to put up a perfunctory act with her as he did not dare be hostile towards her.

“Garen, do you know? Sister Ola is about to have sex with Uncle Cartel,” Leona came over and whispered to Garen.

“…” Garen stared at her speechlessly. “What are you trying to say?”

It was a given that a little female Dragon Whelp did not know what embarrassment was as this was a concept applicable only towards the humans. It was nothing out of the norm for the White Dragon Clan which encourages breeding.

“I plan to go and peek on them. Do you want to join me?” She said furtively.

“No.” Garen rejected her immediately. “I have a lot of things to do. There’s also work and practices from the Arcane Art Courses.”

“Aren’t you curious?” Leona whispered.

“Not even the slightest,” Garen urged Leona to turned her head back to the front as the teenage dragon teacher was about to start his lecture. The instructors here were all part-timers hired at the last second. They were all young dragons that had experienced fighting against powerful foes as each of them had records of killing Level Seven creatures.

The lecture had commenced. There were not a lot of theories and explanation as many of the White Dragon’s battle techniques were inherited. As long as the Dragon Whelps were able to tap into it and practice the techniques, they would soon be able to use them naturally.

The Dragon Clan was born with a powerful body. When matured, their strength and speed would be equivalent to the human’s Level Seven Great Knight. One would be known as the White Silver at that level. Rumor had it that the White Silver Knights in the human tribe possessed a high prestige, where they would able to perform guardian duties to an Earl in his territories.

Hence, what the dragon whelps required to learn was how to utilize their already powerful physical characteristics. Furthermore, one of the main things the Dragon Whelps needed to master was a technique called Draconic Aura.

The Draconic Aura was a natural skill of the Dragon Clan where it could oppress the others. Its potency would naturally increase as the dragons aged. However, the Dragon Clan had invented a training method for the Draconic Aura to further enhance its effectiveness. It was similar to a human training their body and techniques in order to achieve the life force of a Knight.

The class started quickly and similarly to the Arcane Art Class where they were only teaching the foundation, the courses here were all basic foundation syllables.

However, there was an old White Dragon in silver armor on the platform. Although its wing looked rather relaxed, the dragon’s gaze gave off a powerful coercion. That was a Draconic Aura which was much stronger than the average adult dragon.

As the Dragon Whelps sat down and turned down their volume, he started speaking.

“I am Baesman. I believe everyone here knows me since you’ve been here for some time. However, today is different as I will officially pass down the techniques of master Draconic Aura. I will also officially announce the overall job description, the dates, and the details of your missions.”

His mighty voice in Draconic Language kept reverberating within the ice valley.

“The Draconic Aura Techniques!” Garen was excited as he could finally get in touch with the world’s skill system. Despite the Arcane Arts Courses teaching them the basics and knowledge of Spellcraft, Arcane Technique, and the effects of different types of Spellcraft, they had not taught him the training methods. On the other hand, the Combat Courses was earlier in this aspect.

He was not the only one that was excited as the other Dragon Whelps felt the same as well.

Leona was the only one that had uninterest written all over her face. It seemed that she had known of such a thing and had learned it a long time ago.

Garen stared at her and found out the reason why this person had such tremendous strength during basic training. He was nowhere near this female Dragon Whelp’s strength even though he had added points into his strength attribute.

The Dragon Whelps in the course started buzzing among themselves.

Roar!!

Baesman, who was on the platform roared loudly. The intense dragon roar’s reverberation turned into shockwaves as it shocked the Dragon Whelps to the point where they utterly routed. Some of them were so scared that their heads were tilted on the ground and they lost all the strength in their limbs.

“I, Baesman Raghasa Rossavizi… hate living beings making a ruckus in front of me!” The instructor started to move its wings aggressively as he screeched. A frightening sensation of coercion was released from his body. It was similar to being pressured by the atmosphere as the Dragon Whelps did not dare to speak due to the coercion.

Garen was shocked that he was under its effect as he could not breathe properly. He was ecstatic as the skill system was completely new to him.

However, he realized that Leona, who was sitting in front of him had given off a faint pressure to neutralize the majority of the Draconic Aura’s pressure.

There were a few other Dragon Whelps among the rest who gave off the same Draconic Aura similar to Leona’s. The only difference was its strength.

Garen held himself together with brute force to prevent himself from falling down to the snowy ground.

The surrounding became quiet.

Then, the dragon instructor continued its lecture.

“The theory behind the Draconic Aura practice is very simple. What we need to do is simply feel the Draconic Aura that we release naturally. Then, we will try to grasp it and ultimately control it so that we can use it freely as a weapon whenever we want.”

The dragon instructor moved its heavy body around as it walked, giving off a thumping noise with each step he took.

“This weapon will follow you forever! It will remain within your skeletons even after death. Your skeletons will carry along the Draconic Aura so that low-level beings will not be able to get close to you! This is the nobility that we dragons are born with!” The dragon instructor said excitedly as he raised his heads up like a snake.

“You can use the Draconic Aura for other reasons rather than just being a weapon. We can keep it within us and use it as a tool to enhance our physical bodies. It will make us stronger and tougher! Our scales will become more solid and we will have sharper claws.”

“Now, I will introduce you to the discovery of Draconic Aura.”

Baesman then started to explain the existence of the Draconic Aura.

The Dragon Clan was indeed a powerful tribe.

This was the first impression Garen had after listening to the lecture.

The Draconic Aura was actually a natural and powerful Energy Field produced by the Dragon Clan. The dragons were able to produce an external Energy Field that could mentally oppress living beings at all times.

All of this originated from the Dragon Heart’s heartbeat. The Dragon’s Heart was extremely powerful as its rhythm required the movement of numerous myocardium. These muscular heart tissues contained many little beings that gave off electric excitation. They gathered together to form a powerful electricity which ultimately caused electric excitation from the remaining body’s muscles. This energy would naturally spread out and influence the natural surrounding. This was the basic theory behind the Draconic Aura.

Naturally, there were other complicated processes involved, but the most important thing was the electricity within the Dragon’s Heart as it was the leading source of energy.

Instead of having a brain, dragons had Dragon Crystals. The Dragon Crystal and Dragon’s Heart were located in the brain and body respectively. These two were the basic organs that maintained a huge dragon’s physiological activities. Naturally, the electricity produced from a Dragon’s Heart would be extremely powerful as it was the powerhouse of the dragon’s huge body.

Learning the basic of Draconic Aura was not the only main focus of the Combat Course. They also had to learn the anatomy of a dragon and the methods to quickly kill a giant dragon. Furthermore, they had to learn how to kill off a powerful human as well as normal humans who were the main enemies of the White Dragon Clan.

Although the syllables of the anatomy lessons were just scratching the surface, it was detailed enough that there was mention about the dragon’s muscles and fibers.

Garen managed to learn in detail without using his powerful Soul Ring. He was able to quickly understand the contents with his body’s high intelligence. He had seventeen intelligent points the moment he was born. The source of this development was his powerful soul and the nourishment he obtained while he was inside the egg.

The discovery of Draconic Aura was simpler than the rest as instructor Baesman taught a simple technique.

All one required to do was to push the snowflakes away and avoid them from landing on one’s body.

In order to achieve this, all he required to do was to follow the prescribed imagination process. When the mind produced a ripple, he then had to focus and imagine that there was nothing above his head. In other words, it was basically imagination and concentration. All he had to do was to discover and activate it through a special process as the Draconic Aura was an innate skill to all dragons.

Chapter 1260: Mission 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen tried a few times. Initially, it was ineffective. However, his soul was simply too powerful and he was able to vaguely sense the minute trajectory of the snowflakes above his head after a few trials.

The change was so minute that if Garen would not have been able to detect it if he were not paying a close attention. His Draconic Aura was currently not strong enough to influence the external objects. This was the only effect he was able to produce as of now after he gathered all of his Draconic Aura.

“Alright. It’s time to hand out your missions.” Baesman, who had just finished explaining the basics started speaking up once more.

“You’ll have to give in order to receive. Your mission is to head to the ice forest in the south and hunt for the Giant Frost Iguanas. The heart and eyeballs from the Giant Frost Iguanas are very valuable in breeding the Black Teeth Wolves as they could greatly increase their fertility rate.”

The Black Teeth Wolves were the White Dragon Clan’s livestock similar to how humans raising pigs.

“The Giant Frost Iguana typically ranges from Level Three to Five and they’re best for you to train yourselves. Naturally, you’ll have to retreat when you encounter the Elder Giant Iguana. Since we treat them as a source of food, they would definitely view us as a threat. The Elder Giant Iguana is a Level Six living being. You’ll die if you don’t run away from it.”

He then started to point out the Giant Frost Iguana’s weakness, behavior, and its abilities.

As Garen listened attentively, the lecture soon reached to an end.

All of them returned back to their quarters to sleep to get some rest before continuing the lecture the next day.

Garen’s dwelled together with Satwo and the others in a cave located at the foot of the snowy peak. It was originally a bear cave. However, it had been deserted for a long time and it seemed to have been scared off as the White Dragon Clan arrived. As the foot of the mountain had a high temperature of twenty plus degree Celsius, it was rather uncomfortable to the White Dragons which preferred a cool environment. It was also not safe enough, which was the reason why no dragons came to this area. Only Garen and the other orphaned dragons would come here as they had no other place to go.

He kept alternating attending classes and resting, leading a peaceful life as a month passed in a blink of an eye.

Garen then had accumulated a few Attribute Points.

Garen decided to put in all of his accumulated Attribute Points before it was time for him to start his mission.

The dragon was laying down deep inside the cave. Garen started to observe his own Attributes and found that he had grasped the basics of Draconic Aura. While he could use his Attribute Points to increase the Draconic Aura’s level, he did not wish to rush it as this skill required a long time to master. It would catch a lot of attention if he were to improve too much within a short period of time. He would be easily discovered by those with powerful spellcraft capabilities. Everything would be over if they found out that their soul was abnormal.

Since he was not able to add the points to his skills, he could only add them to his physical attributes. It was very cost effective for him to add them to his Physical Attributes in the early stages.

Coincidentally, Safour had gone to the Arcane Art Courses to discuss the content of the missions with a few other Dragon Whelps and found out that they had to go together.

Satwo and Sathree had gone out to hunt earlier and were already on their way.

Garen was the only one left inside the cave and would participate in hunting the Giant Frost Iguana the next day.

“I can be immune towards diseases and even a lot of Spellcraft if I have a strong Vitality and Strength. Furthermore, I will have the ability to evade fast and dangerous spells as well. I might even be able to avoid being locked by the Caster as well. The latter would not be able to injure me even if he had a high-level spell. I will be able to increase the Arcane Art’s learning pace if I were to increase my intelligence. Although I have yet to officially learn Meditation, it is still very useful.”

Garen decided to increase his physical attributes instead of intelligence after hesitating for a while. One would not be able to learn Spellcraft in a short amount of time. This was especially true for the Dragon Clan, which possessed a powerful physical body.

“I’ll enhance my speed, strength, and agility equally. I had the high-speed development similar to every other Dragon Whelp when I was born. However, it only lasted for about two months and the situation wouldn’t reappear now that everything has calmed down. I have accumulated about five points worth of Attribute Points for the past two months. Since I have a mission to fulfill and since the Giant Frost Iguana is not fast but powerful, I will just add them into Strength for now.”

It would be better for him to finish the hunting missions earlier as this meant that he would obtain more rewards. Garen had also planned to breed a few Black Teeth Wolves so that he would not rely entirely on hunting nearby the area around it was too dangerous. Satwo and the others might be captured and killed off by the humans if they were not careful.

He could breed them within a certain area inside his own cave. He would have to wait it out and see the circumstance in terms of breeding the wolves’ offspring. If it was not feasible, he could use them to exchange for other items such as books related to Arcane Arts.

Garen’s learning pace far surpassed any other Dragon Whelp and since he had to follow the other Dragon Whelps’ pace in class, he felt that he had wasted a lot of time and talent.

Garen looked at his own Status Pane after decided the path he wanted to take.

‘Safive – Strength 16, Agility 15, Vitality 11, Intelligence 17. Potential 527%. Soul Limit 170’

He had placed all of his Attribute Points into Strength without any hesitation.

His Strength instantly rose from 16 to 21.

He could clearly hear the sound of his muscles tightening up. It sounded like a spring and even more like a reinforced bar being tightened.

He felt his limbs becoming firmer and heavier as the muscle density had increased.

He then whipped out his claws and attacked the ground inside the cave. A clear dragon claw mark could be seen as it was at least ten centimeters deep.

This was an end result of Garen’s casual strike.

“A fully grown White Dragon’s Strength is approximately between 30 to 40 points. I still have a long way to go…” Garen sighed softly as he eased his tightened muscles.

Although he was able to produce such power with 21 points of Strength, the adult dragons would be even more powerful since they had at least 20 more points than him. According to Garen’s analysis, it was not just Strength as the remaining three Attributes of an adult dragon were between 30 to 40 points.

They were incredibly powerful as Garen might not be able to break an adult dragon’s defense even if he had 30 points of Strength. This had yet to account for their incredible regenerative abilities.

This was under the assumption that his opponent decided to let him attack him without fighting back using any high-level spells. It might cost him his life if his Vitality was not high enough when he was hit by the spells.

After a detailed comparison, Garen understood that the difference in strength between him and the matured White Dragon was still incredibly far apart.

“However, it requires a Dragon Whelp at least fifty years to mature. This means that I will have an additional enhancement from my Attribute Points other than growing strong naturally. This means I will most likely be able to surpass a matured white dragon in less than fifty years,” Garen estimated in his heart.

After adding his Attribute Points, he stood up and walked out of the cave.

The area outside the cave was covered in a layer of white frost, coincidentally forming the shape of a fan as it froze the cave’s surrounding area. Since it was a cave inhabited by the White Dragons, the temperature was naturally lowered.

The forest surrounding it was still filled with greeneries. As there was a faint Draconic Aura and the White Dragon Clan’s coercion, one would not be able to see any dangerous living being nearby. However, there were only a few harmless and small beings hiding about here and there.

“Hey~!” A Dragon Whelp flew towards Garen from afar as she shouted at him. “Garen. It’s time to move out.”

It was Leona. She was slim, graceful and even her scales were much more lustrous and purer than a typical White Dragon. She looked like a White Crystal Dragon and was extremely beautiful.

However, as Leona flew, two Dragon Whelps appeared behind her and both were clearly male dragons.

Leona landed in front of Garen as she put her wings away.

“It’s time to go hunting. It’s my first time going out for a hunt. Are you scared!?” She screamed out of excitement.

“What’s there to be afraid of?” Garen did not like speaking to her. However, the more he acted so, Leona would try to speak to him even more. She had said that being cool and cruel is a necessary trait for a White Dragon! She had very strong intuition and seemed to have inherited a portion of the elder’s Classification talent. She could probably vaguely sense that Garen was much stronger than the rest of the Dragon Whelps.

The strong ones would often receive a different opinion from the rest.

“Are you really not afraid? The Giant Frost Iguanas has an innate spell called Ice Armor!” Leona said loudly. “They are much stronger than us and it would be dangerous if we were hit by them.”

“Can they fly?” Garen turned around as he walked towards the cave.

“Uh, no…”

“Then there’s nothing to worry about. We can fly,” Garen said casually.

“However, we won’t be able to achieve anything right? How are we supposed to hunt?” Leona was puzzled.

“He’s just a coward.” The two Dragon Whelps flying behind her landed as the muscular one shouted. “Listen to me Leona. If it were me, I would blow the Giant Frost Iguana up into the sky with my breath!”

He patted his chest.

“You? Forget about it. It’s still possible if it were Boris.” Leona looked at the other Dragon Whelp who was slightly more well proportioned.

Boris the Dragon Whelp looked at Garen calmly and it was obvious that he was rather unhappy with Garen’s impoliteness.

“Is he really the one you must team up with? Although I don’t know if he knows how to fight, no one will like his attitude.”

“Garen is born with this cold personality. He’s not as unfriendly as you think he is,” Leona defended him.

“If we form into a small team of three, we will definitely be able to kill the Giant Frost Iguana if we strictly follow the battle strategy. I have already thought about the procedures and it doesn’t matter if he’s required,” Boris said coldly. He was also a direct descendant of an Elder Dragon. He was slightly unhappy that there were still a few Dragon Whelps who dared disrespect him.

He had feelings towards Leona even though the latter’s elder was slightly weaker. However, he would be able to produce excellent offspring if she were to become his partner purely for reproduction.

“Leona, I don’t like you getting along closely with that Garen guy,” Boris said softly.

“Boris, Garen is my partner and my friend!” Leona was discontented.

Although Boris was discontented as well, he did not show it.

“How about this. He can join us but his loot will depend on how well he performs. If he performs badly, don’t blame me that I decided to give him nothing.”

“Great!” Leona was instantly happy upon hearing it.

Garen was speechless as he stayed inside the cave. He had heard of the name Boris before, who was a few years older than him. He should be at the age to use his Draconic Aura to train his body and he seemed to have taken a liking towards Leona.

The Dragon Whelp Nurturing Center did not nurture Dragon Whelps that had just hatched and Garen was considered to be the youngest of them all. On the other hand, Boris was the earliest batch and had been around a few years longer than Garen.

He wanted to ignore these kids but he would have attracted a lot of attention if he were to hunt too many of them alone. It was not a bad idea for him to take cover in this small team. Since Leona was naive and the higher up definitely had their intentions when they decided to place her together with him.

Chapter 1261: Giant Iguana 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

His body’s equally strong qualities were noticed when they were testing his standard level. Garen was revealing these things vaguely so that he would be taken seriously by the others despite not having the most valuable assets.

“They probably want me to focus on protecting Leona,” he pondered.

A series of chaotic noises echoed from the outside of the cave.

Garen prostrated himself on the ground and began practicing his Draconic Aura and Condensation skills alone.

This was a lengthy process but the one thing that the Dragon Clan did not lack was time.

The current strength of the average Dragon Whelp was about eighteen points. Garen was not worried about being unable to finish this Quest at all because his strength had already greatly surpassed the average Dragon Whelp.

After waiting for a while inside the cave, it appeared that Leona and the others had finished their discussion outside.

Only then did they enter the cave.

“Garen Garen!” Leona yelled while flying into the cave. “We’ve finished discussing. You’ll be one of the two main attackers. What do you think? Do you agree or not?”

“Main attacker?” Garen stood up. “I don’t mind but what’ll you guys be doing?”

Boris opened his mouth immediately.

“Leona and I both have specially made Enchanted Necklaces that can release Long-range Attack Spells. Don’t worry, we won’t disappoint you.” Although he was furious at Garen for ignoring him and returning to the cave alone, he remained courteous to him on the surface because he needed to assure Leona of his demeanor.

“What Attack Spells?” Garen revealed a surprised expression faintly.

Boris instantly raised his claws and pointed at the necklace in front of his chest in a somewhat proud manner. It was a chain of white pearls that had been strung into a necklace with a rare cerulean gem that hung below. It was extraordinarily dazzling and crystal-clear.

“Can you see it, Sleepyhead? My father prepared this outstanding item for me. It can release Level Five Dragonfire Spells three times a day.”

“Wow, that’s so cool?! My ring can only use Dragonheal Spells three times daily.” Garen did not react but Leona who stood on the sidelines was unusually excited now.

Level Five Spellcrafting. Although they could only use it three times a day, it was enough to guarantee their safety. Moreover, it was very likely that they had other similar Spellcrafting Equipment.

These were types of Enchanted Equipment that could only be specially made by Casters and Wizards. They required Enchantment and would consume costly materials as well as a large amount of Spirit Power and energy before they could contact Weave to release and enchant a spell. It was pretty good that both of these Dragon Whelps had obtained two pieces of Level Five Enchanted Equipment. These items could only be specially created by Level Six Wizards and Casters that could afford to consume a lot of energy. A single Enchantment could cause a Wizard to consume at least one of their Casting levels. In other words, a Level Six Caster who was on the borderline of having their rank promoted would drop immediately instead if they tried to Enchant a piece of equipment like this. Moreover, they would deteriorate and return to their previous state when they had just entered Level Six. This was a waste of Spirit Power.

“They’ve really spent a huge sum of money,” Garen pondered. The White Dragon Clan had declined terribly. There were merely five or six Elder Dragons who were Casters that were Level Five or above. However, they instantly brought out two pieces of Enchanted Equipment. It was very likely that these items were collected articles that were seized from the humans.

“We don’t have to fear anything now that we have these two pieces of equipment.” Boris was a Dragon Whelp to the core. There was still a limit to his maturity in the end. Hence, being unable to stop himself from taking his strongest trump card out and flaunting it was a very normal thing for him to do.

After confirming that they had their own defensive forces, only then did Garen truly decide to join this unit. Perhaps it was the other way around. After all, he and Leona were already partners in the same group that had to move together while Boris and the other dragon had rushed over to join them voluntarily.

The group of dragons prepared to check the items that they had brought respectively. There were no Space Dimensional Pockets. Items like that were seized from the humans by the White Dragon Clan. However, they could not use it because they did not possess human Spirit Powers. The Space Equipment would collapse and lose its effectiveness completely if they opened it forcibly. Moreover, the White Dragons like themselves did not have the craftsmen to create these playthings.

They finished checking the map and the various tools and items that they would use in their daily lives. The four Dragon Whelps formed a team and flew towards the mountain valley where according to the map was where the Giant Ice Iguana was located.

They chose to go there during the night to take advantage of the night sky that would make it unlikely for the other creatures to discover them. The distance between the Giant Ice Iguana and the White Dragon Clan was somewhat far. They needed to thread across an even longer distance. Even though there were roads that were cleaned up by White Dragons that frequently came and left, there were still certain Earth Dragons that were scattered everywhere because they were too used to Draconic Auras. Most of these Earth Dragons had low intellect and were very likely to attack Dragon Whelps that were just passing by.

When night came and the purple moonlight was covered by the black night sky, Leona and the group flew straight towards the location that was indicated on the map. There was a long continuous stretch of black forests in a rising and falling mountain range below them. The deep sound of large beasts that were fast asleep could be occasionally heard. There were multiple continuous bursts over a period of time.

Garen flew in the middle of the team. Meanwhile, a young fellow named Saszt flew in front. He was the muscular Dragon Whelp who had followed Boris. This boy’s boastful tone was very apparent but he loved following Boris’s orders. Meanwhile, Leona flew at the back beside Boris. However, her gaze was always swaying across Garen’s body.

Garen had impeccable physical fitness. Moreover, he was more well-proportioned and muscular compared to the average Dragon Whelp. This was a strong but also beautiful combination. It was no wonder Leona was gazing at him so fervently.

Boris and Leona who were beside him had spoken a few times. However, it seemed completely ineffective because it could not prevent her unabashed gaze. He was forced to give up helplessly. Meanwhile, his own gaze that was lingering on Garen became even more unsatisfied.

Garen could not be bothered with these bratty childish matters. He was currently lowering his head and looking down at the vast terrain below.

The pitch-black mountain range rose and fell from higher to lower altitudes continuously. Spots of bright white light that were swaying here and there could be seen occasionally. They floated around endlessly but no one knew what they were.

Drawn-out wolf howls could also be heard now and then from afar.

The group of dragons flew forward for over half an hour. Soon, they could see faint vortex-like phosphorescence that was blinking on one of the higher mountain peaks in front of them. The green phosphorescence formed a gigantic vortex that was spinning on the side of the mountain peak slowly. Under the illumination of the purple moon, it gave off a dreamlike sense of beauty.

“What’s that?” asked Saszt softly while flying in front.

“That’s the Thunder Snake Clan,” answered Boris instantly.

“The Thunder Snake Clan, huh? I’ve heard my grandfather mention it before,” Leona nodded as well. “They’re a rare race of living creatures that depend on us for shelter to live. There were Manticores last time as well but it’s unfortunate that they’ve all fled. Currently, there’s only one Thunder Snake left.”

“It won’t be troublesome if we fly over there, right?” Garen was concerned about the others.

“No, although the dependent relationship has lightened recently during these past few years, it’s unlikely for them to attack us spontaneously,” said Boris logically. He was clearly emulating the attitude of a certain Adult Dragon.

They flew past the Thunder Snake Clan from above. Garen observed the light green phosphorescent vortex. There were numerous moth-like insects inside the vortex that were blinking with light. Light green fluorescence was spreading all over their entire bodies faintly. This phosphorescent vortex was clearly created by these light green moths.

“Come and look quickly. It’s Beyber and the others!” Leona suddenly yelled while pointing towards the distant sky.

“Beyber? Where? I’ll definitely give him a good show after coming out this time!” The moment he heard this name, Boris who was pretending to be calm all this while flared up. He glanced over fiercely in the direction where Leona was pointing before actually seeing a little team of Dragon Whelps that were similarly flying past the borders of the Thunder Snake mountain now.

The fellow that was leading these few Dragon Whelps was named Beyber and he was always fighting with Boris. Neither of them was afraid of the other because they both belonged to the Elder’s bloodline. However, Boris was still slightly weaker in the end because he was beaten up more frequently.

There was a congenital black birthmark patch on Beyber’s right wing. Hence, he was very easily recognizable. He also had an extremely muscular physique.

He had obviously noticed Boris and the others here. He grinned while charging over from afar while faintly harboring some malicious intentions.

“That guy! He’s provoking me!!” Boris burned with rage and positioned himself as if he was about to rush over. However, he was immediately held back tightly by Saszt.

“Don’t, Boris! The swelling on your backside had just subsided so you can’t get hurt again! Our quest will be delayed if you get injured again now!” Saszt clearly did not know what to say to save Boris’s face.

“Saszt!! When have I been unable to defeat that bastard?!”

Boris’s flushed suddenly. This was the first time Garen discovered the states of White Dragons when they blushed.

“It was the day before. You were single-handedly beaten up by Beyber. I saw it with my own eyes. I’m doing this for your own good!!” There was a loyal expression on Saszt’s face while he hugged him closely without loosening his claws at all.

Oh!

When he saw Leona’s surprised gaze that was tinged with faint disdain, Boris was itching to find a crack to burrow through. Saszt’s strength was indeed great. Otherwise, there would have been nothing that he could have said to get this idiot to cooperate with him!

However, it was too late to regret it now.

“Don’t go and suffer another beating! Boris!!” Saszt yelled. Boris and the other dragons who were far away heard him as well. They could not help but roar with laughter.

“Pfft…” Leona could not stop herself from laughing either.

Garen shook his head silently when he saw the face of Boris the dragon that was flushed to the point where it turned purple. Boris knew that the image of himself in Leona’s heart was already completely damaged.

However, he had searched for this partner and encountered him on his own.

Boris raised his head and let out a drawn-out cry. He watched Beyber and the other dragons fly away into the distance while guffawing. As his own strength was insufficient to break free from Saszt, he could only roar madly in grief.

“Let’s go. Stop roaring,” urged Garen.

“That’s right. If there’s something wrong, we’ll go to the Hunting Area and settle it with them there!” Leona could not help but cheer Boris up.

The group of dragons experienced a lot of difficulty in calming down Boris’ emotions after encountering this minor incident. Boris scolded Saszt angrily before continuing to fly towards the Hunting Area listlessly.

Along the way, they passed through a little grey human campsite that was below them. Numerous human warriors walked in and out of the tents at times and they could even occasionally see a Wizard walking out of the tents.

“Those are the powerhouses of the Deladia Empire’s alliance. They’ve already united with our White Dragon Clan to form an alliance of Wizards.”

Boris was the one who explained. Since Garen did not laugh at him earlier, he had revised his impression of him and viewed him in a much better light now.

“Powerhouses of the alliance? How was the alliance act formed?” asked Garen.

“Rumor has it that it was formed through the dragon race’s Alliance Oath Spell. They pay us compensation so we respond when they summon us and come forward to support them. These Summoning Spells are unique. However, they’re only suitable for Adult White Dragons. We are currently not qualified yet,” Boris shook his head.

“Are these summon-type spells? I’ve heard that summon-type spells can be used to summon doors to other worlds where we can hunt down powerful creatures from different space-time dimensions to either enslave or engage in combat with them, is that so?” Garen did not have the information from the relevant books. Instead, he could faintly remember these contents from his inherited memories.

“Yes, it’s like that. Spells like these are listed in the stack of books that my grandfather collected. However, certain editions are incomplete. Since they weren’t very useful towards us White Dragons, no one really valued them highly. Many of these books were accidentally ruined because they weren’t preserved or taken care of properly,” said Leona regretfully. “Why? Do you want to learn Summoning Spells, Garen? If you wanted to do that, we might as well enslave the subordinate Earth Dragons and Dragon Beasts. We’d probably need at least Level Five or Level Six Summoning Spells to summon creatures like Dragon Beasts. It wouldn’t be that useful.”

“That’s true as well,” Garen nodded understandably. Actually, he was merely planning to try and see if he could open his initial main door to the Space-Time Universe. However, when he thought about the terrifyingly powerful beings that existed when he Transmigrated to this world, he knew in his heart that this was highly unlikely. The desire for mere advanced level Spellcrafting to achieve such a high degree was a wild fantasy indeed.

“My grandfather has dispatched two Dragon Guards to assist Deladia with defending the Wizard Tower. He can probably obtain complete Spellcrafting information in exchange. However, it will probably be very expensive. If you want it, you can go and contact those two ‘big brother’ Dragon Guards,” said Leona quietly.

“Yes, I know. Thank you very much,” Garen made a mental note.

Chapter 1262: Giant Iguana 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When the group of Dragons passed through the human campsite below them from above, there were people on the ground who raised their heads and stared. However, they did not display any frightened looks because they were clearly used to this.

The Dragon Whelps’ hunting period was limited to one month. Therefore, numerous Dragon Whelps had obviously passed through this area already within the past few days.

They continued flying forward before a vast white snowy peak appeared in the distance. The top was covered in white snow while the bottom part was a long stretch of the light green and yellow mountain body. The entire snowy peak was unusually pure which gave off a simple and clean atmosphere.

The sun had currently exposed its head in the east slowly. It illuminated a large part of the sky while the halo of the purple moon was gradually covered by it.

Leona and the group of Dragon Whelps arranged themselves in a square formation while flying straight towards the snowy peak. The morning sunlight reflected across their bodies and illuminated faint golden-red glows.

A flock of gigantic wild geese swept past them from below at high speed. These wild geese were Level Two creatures that seemed as though they had sensed the auras of the Dragon Whelps. Hence, they accelerated suddenly and fled speedily.

In the wild, other than Earth Dragons, Dragon Beasts, and a few other advanced level creatures, most of the other creatures were not rivals of the Dragon Whelps.

“This is the Hunting Area. We’ve already arrived at the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range. Be careful, everyone. We’re not the only ones here. We may also encounter some advanced level Demonic Beasts nearby who came to hunt as well,” Boris reminded them loudly.

Garen flew in the middle of the team. He lowered his head and looked downwards. He could see a few little people who were moving slowly in the forest from afar. They seemed as if they were stumbling terribly.

As flying creatures, White Dragons naturally possessed extremely powerful sight. He narrowed his pupils quickly and stared below before noticing that the sparse black dots in the dark parts of the forest were actually humans that were walking slowly.

They wore tattered clothes and their faces were dull while their skin was dark purple. They were clearly not living people but they shared one characteristic with them.

That similar quality was their abdomens. All of their internal organs were clearly displayed in a manner that allowed people to see the black intestines and other organs that were coiled up inside. Their organs were wrapped up by a transparent membrane layer.

“Those are Walking Corpses. They’re monsters that were naturally produced by the poisonous gas here and their remaining energy before they died,” explained Boris in a quiet voice while approaching Garen.

“Walking Corpses?” Garen glanced at him briefly. This fellow’s posture seemed to indicate that he wanted to get closer to Garen.

“That’s right, they can’t be fully killed and they can revive themselves quickly after dying. Too many of the corpses in this forest were preserved in these zombified states because of the poisonous gas. Therefore, they couldn’t rot at all,” Boris nodded. He turned around and glanced at Leona once he had finished speaking. “It seems like you dislike Leona, huh?” he asked in a very quiet voice.

“Why would I want to like her?” asked Garen in response. Despite being rather smart, this fellow could only tell that he did not like Leona now… Weren’t his actions obvious enough?

Boris’s mood improved instantly. He patted Garen’s shoulder.

“If there’s anything that you need help with, you can come and look for either me or Saszt.”

“Just don’t come and bother me,” replied Garen indifferently.

Boris’s next words were suddenly caught in his mouth before his face began to turn red again at once…

Garen could not be bothered to save Boris’s face.

All the Adult Dragons of the White Dragon Clan were selfish. Within a short while, Dragon Whelps would be chased out of the nest and forced to become independent on their own. The affections between them were very apathetic and they only respected and paid attention to power. Adult White Dragons could not interfere in the matters regarding the nurturing of Dragon Whelps. Those who did would be naturally eliminated.

Therefore, acting in a perfunctory manner towards Boris was unimportant to him.

“Alright… Alright…” Boris tried his best to swallow his anger. “The Hunting Area is at the snowy peak in front. As the main attackers, you and Saszt will move forward and fight in a little while. No problem, right? Leona and I will perform long-range attacks.”

“Okay.” Garen had no qualms about this. He wanted to briefly observe the Ice Iguana first anyway.

The group of Dragon Whelps flew into the mountain range where the snowy peak was located quickly. Numerous shrouds of strong and weak densely-packed auras were constantly permeating and spreading throughout the inside of this area. Some of them soared into the sky as they were unimaginably powerful.

When they looked over from afar, they could easily see more than ten Giant Ice Iguanas of various sizes that were moving and strolling around in the snow. These creatures had low intelligence but possessed powerful physical bodies and Spirit Power. Their flesh also possessed extremely strong fertility increment functions.

Giant Ice Iguanas possessed four muscular legs. Their entire bodies were greyish-black but were wrapped in a layer of powdery snowy white dust on the outside. They looked like enlarged versions of lizards that were dragging long tails.

The only difference between them and the lizards was the dark blue notch in the middle of their foreheads.

The smallest of these Giant Ice Iguanas was as tall as an adult human. It was normal for the length of its body to be anywhere from five to eight meters long. At a glance, Garen could see that the largest one was a “super” Giant Iguana that was at least fifteen meters long. These Giant Iguanas had bodies that were fully dark green and covered in coarse scales. Their heads were surrounded by a circle of black-green fins. The shrouds of tyrannical auras were released by them.

The Dragon Whelps’ vision greatly surpassed that of the Giant Ice Iguanas. Therefore, they could see the other party while the Giant Ice Iguanas were unable to see them.

“The visions of Giant Ice Iguanas can only reach more than ten meters. Moreover, it’s very blurry as well. They use smells to detect their enemies. Thus, we have to be careful.” Boris was well-prepared with all kinds of information.

“I’ll go down and check it out first!” Saszt charged downwards alone before waiting for his instructions. He was aiming precisely at the smallest Giant Iguana.

He had just approached a range of fewer than twenty meters away. However, the Giant Iguana was already prepared. It swung its grey-black tail violently and drew it towards Saszt to counter him.

Saszt did not withdraw at all either. Since his strength was his advantage, he did not dodge at all but lowered his head firmly and struck it instead.

Bang!

The powdery snow on the snow-covered ground flew upwards before being scattered everywhere. Meanwhile, Saszt actually resisted the Giant Iguana’s swinging tail determinedly.

This was a smaller-sized Giant Iguana that was only five meters long but as tall as a human. Nonetheless, they were already considered as big guys to these Dragon Whelps. Although the intelligence levels of Giant Ice Iguanas were not impressive, they were indeed large and would not simply yield to the Dragon Race.

Saszt’s mind relaxed immediately after he had probed and discovered the upper limit of his opponent’s strength. Then, he fought and grappled with the Giant Iguana. He used his claws to attempt to scratch the Giant Iguana’s neck with all his might. Meanwhile, the Giant Iguana had wound its tongue around Saszt’s neck desperately which made it impossible for him to move forward at all.

Both of them rolled around on the snowy ground.

Leona and Boris who were watching covered their faces unconsciously and remained silent.

“He’s forgotten everything that we learned in the Combat Course…” said Boris helplessly.

Garen stood on the side and watched for a while. It did not seem like Saszt was in any danger because this little Giant Iguana had clearly come out to hunt alone which made it less risky for Saszt. Its strength was almost on par with Saszt at about nineteen points, more or less.

“Garen, go forward and help him!” Boris yelled.

Garen had no choice but to step forward. He aimed precisely for the Giant Iguana’s neck and prepared to hurt it before using his claw.

There was a banging noise.

The bone of the Giant Iguana’s neck broke off precisely when it was struck. Garen did not even have to waste a sliver of additional strength before the creature was instantly killed by him.

When the same strength was used by a person who had undergone training and one who had yet to experience those same exercises, the difference between the combat powers of those two individuals was actually very great.

Garen and Saszt were both Level Four Dragon Whelps. They possessed the same types of various Dragon Whelp abilities but Garen’s were stronger than Saszt’s in more ways than one.

Boris and Leona also felt that Garen’s previous clawing motion was very beautiful. However, they were unable to see the entire situation earlier. Therefore, they merely felt that Garen was able to solve this battle instantly because Saszt was already coiled around the Giant Iguana. They did not think that it was significantly amazing because they could have definitely done it themselves as well.

Saszt only crawled out from under the Giant Iguana’s belly while panting after the creature was finished off.

“You should’ve came earlier. That scared me. That fellow’s tongue was harder than the scales of the Elders, even to me. If any other dragon had been in my place, they would have been strangled and killed by him at the very first instance!!” Saszt could not help but start boasting after only saying a few words.

Garen shrugged because he could not be bothered with saying much.

“Alright, stop wasting time. Dig out its eyes and Crystal Core quickly because the smell of its blood will attract other creatures over,” Boris had a learned look on his face. As an old scholar of the Nurturing Center, this was naturally not his first hunt.

The four dragons gouged out the items and left quickly. Not long after, they could hear a weird croaking noise echoing behind them faintly. It seemed as though a strange creature had discovered the corpse.

Leona placed the eyeballs and Crystal Core into a little oval shaped can that she had brought.

“This is a preservation bottle that ensures that it won’t go bad for a short period of time. It can maintain its freshness for a period of two months and is excellent to be used during quests.”

After that, they encountered another Giant Iguana. It was slightly bigger than the previous one but not to a large extent. It had yet to break through to Level Four.

Compared to the previous Giant Iguana, this one was clearly more vigilant. It released its protective Ice Armor and covered its body immediately after seeing them. It formed a large sparkling white translucent armor instantly that protected the front half of its body. However, the back half of its body was not shielded. Nonetheless, since the Giant Iguana’s turning speed was very fast, there was clearly not a possibility that it would give Garen and the other dragons a chance to attack its tail.

Without wasting any time, Saszt charged forward and continued attacking. Since he had already said so earlier, Garen rushed forward as well.

This time, this Giant Iguana’s strength was much greater than the previous one. The Giant Iguana moved its head forward and attempted to collide it against the two dragons violently.

Garen moved aside but Saszt was unable to dodge it at all. His wing was scratched before an additional cut appeared in his scales suddenly.

“We’ll lift it together,” said Garen loudly. He had yet to display his 21 points of strength but had merely exhibited 19 points of strength which were at the same level as Saszt. He did this to avoid bringing attention to himself.

“Alright.”

Both dragons had just agreed before the Giant Iguana retracted its tail and swung it at them again.

The dull whooshing noise of wind could be heard when its tail fanned out a clearly twisted airstream that whipped towards the two dragons.

Saszt used all his strength to arch forward while Garen lifted both of his claws forward.

Bang!

They blocked it steadily!

The combined strength of both dragons was greater than the Giant Iguana’s strength. The Giant Iguana roared. It lowered its head and opened its mouth before its red tongue wound itself around Saszt while its tail swung itself towards Garen for the third time.

“Dragonfire Spell!”

At the moment, Leona roared loudly behind them.

Flames that were shaped like a single dragon exploded from her claws. They were accompanied by countless red stars that flew down and struck the Giant Iguana’s tail rapidly.

It appeared that both Leona and Boris had circled the Giant Iguana and arrived behind at its backside suddenly.

This was the combat tactic that they were referring to earlier.

The Giant Iguana’s Ice Armor could only protect the top half of its body while its lower half was at a loss. Hence, it was much easier for the dragons when they used one of their stronger members to attract the Giant Iguana’s attention while the others attacked it from behind.

Chapter 1263: Hunt 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The red Dragonfire Spell crashed against the bottom half of the Giant Iguana’s tail violently. The surrounding icy snow-covered ground melted while water vapor rose and turned into shrouds of white mist that diffused everywhere.

Garen and Saszt stepped backward frantically before hearing a pained yell immediately. The Giant Iguana in front of them finally burst forth in a frantic struggle. It released all of its strength and rolled on the snowy ground with all of its might.

However, the Dragonfire Spell was a Level Five Spell and could not be easily extinguished. The spell stuck to the bottom half of the Giant Iguana’s tail determinedly like a maggot in a skeleton. It burned endlessly before the scent of flesh could be faintly smelled in the air where it was wafting.

Garen and Saszt took a few more steps backward hurriedly.

They could gradually see that the Giant Iguana’s endless struggles had slowed down more and more. Finally, there was a brief banging noise when it crashed on the ground. Its entire body was burnt black which made it somewhat impossible to see its initial state.

“Tch tch, what great power! This is truly Level Five Spellcraft!” Saszt praised. He stepped forward and shifted it slowly while trying to see its entire burnt state.

“Don’t burn the Crystal Core and eyeballs.” He was slightly worried.

“The eyeballs certainly can’t be used anymore,” answered Boris helplessly. “Fortunately, it’s less likely that the Crystal Core will be so easily burnt and destroyed. The Crystal Core won’t be damaged so easily because it’s located in the hardest part of the Demonic Beast’s body.”

Garen followed him and walked over as well. He suddenly felt a large shroud of burning air currents surging towards his face in a slightly scorching manner. Luckily, the Dragonfire Spell would extinguish once the Giant Iguana had died.

He turned the Giant Iguana’s corpse over gently before quickly finding the Crystal Core in the Giant Iguana’s forehead that was about to be burned soon.

“Such high temperatures.” His own body temperature would maintain itself at around less than negative twenty degrees at all times. Hence, a shroud of white gas drifted out faintly when he touched the Crystal Core.

“How’s the Crystal Core? Garen?” asked Leona and Boris loudly when they rushed over from behind him.

“Yes, how’s the Crystal Core? Since this Giant Iguana was so fierce, I’m sure that the Crystal Core would be better.”

They walked closer towards Garen but saw that he was standing before the Giant Iguana alone and looking somewhat dazed.

“Garen?” Leona reached her claw out and shook it in front of his face.

“Uhh, I’m fine. I was just spacing out.” Garen returned to his senses. A hint of a sincere smile that came from his heart appeared on his face.

“Spacing out? You were spacing out even when you were collecting your spoils of war?” Leona could not understand him.

However, when she saw the Crystal Core, that round pale blue crystal that was already slightly blackened from the smoke in Garen’s hand, her attention was immediately shifted over there.

“Haha, we got another one. It’s actually much better than the previous one that we got in front too.”

The three Dragon Whelps gathered together and began celebrating joyfully.

After Garen had given them the Crystal Core, he walked towards the side and continued pondering on his own as if he had encountered an issue.

The issue that he had just discovered was actually an unexpected pleasant surprise.

The Crystal Core that was obtained from the Giant Iguana actually gave him a few slivers of potential aura.

It was not Soul Energy but merely potential energy that was similar to what he had experienced in the Totem World previously. The Giant Iguana’s Crystal Core clearly possessed the ability to increase his potential value.

His potential value had already increased by 1% when he was absorbing it previously within a short span of time. If he had finished absorbing the Crystal Core fully and obtained another three of these Crystal Cores of the same level, he would receive an additional Attribute Point.

“This is an unexpected surprise. I initially assumed that I could only accumulate it slowly throughout a long period of time, but now I see that I can walk on another path.”

However, this was considered normal when he thought about it. After all, the laws of this world were far more entirely comprehensive in comparison to the previous worlds that he had experienced. The presence of sightings from the Totem World that appeared here were normal as well.

“The Crystal Core and eyeballs are the two most important parts of a Giant Iguana. I don’t think that they would agree if I wanted to divide the Crystal Core on my own. The best method would be to go at it alone.” An idea formed in Garen’s mind. He was uncertain of his own position now. However, Level Four Giant Iguanas would probably not be an issue.

In the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range, Level Four Giant Iguanas were simply as abundant as ants in an anthill. There were everywhere and as long as you did not go to the densest areas, you would usually not encounter Level Five Giant Iguanas or even Level Six Elder Giant Iguanas.

Once the group of Dragon Whelps had kept their belongings, they continued on their journey and found another Level Four Giant Iguana. They used the same attack method and killed another one easily.

Since Boris’s Dragonfire Spell was the only one that could quickly injure and kill Giant Iguanas while Leona’s Enchantment was not the killing or wounding type but the healing kind instead, the group was forced to stop here temporarily. As the Dragonfire Spell could only be used three times a day, they decided to leave the last use in case they needed to defend themselves at any time.

Fiery Blaze Mountain Range was a long continuous mountain range that resembled a centipede. They were currently at the “tail” part of the “centipede”. If they walked forward, they would easily encounter many more Giant Iguanas. The Giant Ice Iguanas that could be seriously handled by the White Dragon Clan’s hunting formations were naturally not lacking in strength. The lowest leveled Giant Iguanas were Level Four at least. It was rumored that there were also beings that possessed higher intelligence among the Elder Giant Iguanas. The powers of these existences were unknown but their higher intelligence levels meant that they could find various other practice methods to improve themselves.

Once the group of Dragon Whelps had finished their work, they began looking for a place where to could set up camp and hide.

They had already entered the deeper part of the mountain range to hunt. As they would probably require a longer period of time if they were to leave and go outside again now, it was better for them to find a good cave to rest temporarily. In order to complete their quest this time, each Dragon Whelp needed to hunt five Level Four Giant Iguanas and obtain either their Crystal Cores or eyeballs. They could also acquire the Crystal Cores of two Level Five Giant Iguanas instead.

Since they had currently obtained the Crystal Cores of three Level Four Giant Iguanas upon entering this area, they had already completed the quest of one Dragon Whelp.

Moreover, they were fortunate to not have encountered the disturbances of any other Giant Iguanas when they were hunting.

They found a random place in a corner before the four Dragon Whelps dug a hole and burrowed inside it quickly. Next, they sealed the cave to prevent their auras from leaking out and attracting other high leveled Giant Iguanas. It was important to note that if they were hunting Giant Iguanas, the Giant Iguanas themselves would hunt them as well if they encountered them.

Inside the hole, Garen sat in one place alone while quietly eating the Giant Iguana’s flesh that was roasted and cooked-through. This was a better piece of breast meat that they had randomly sliced off earlier. They had kept it as food supplies.

“This location is not bad. It’s more secluded because it’s at the bottom of a snowy cliff. Moreover, this place can be our temporary base because it’s below a wind gap.” Boris was relatively more experienced than the others.

The Dragon Whelps’ mutual body temperatures caused the temperature of the entire cave to stabilize at around negative twenty degrees.

Leona stood on one side and continuously flipped the Crystal Core and eyeballs that they had obtained in her hand while not worrying that they were dirty. Instead, there was a greedy look on her face.

Meanwhile, Saszt was constantly replaying the events of the daytime battle in his head. He appeared more confident once he had fused these memories with the Giant Iguana’s weaknesses that his tutor had mentioned previously.

It was currently already night-time outside now. The wind and snow mingled while the sound of violent whistling could be heard outside through the cave’s ventilation hole.

“I’m going out for a while,” Garen got up and walked towards the outside of the cave.

“Where are you going to go when it’s already so late, Garen?” asked Leona frantically. During the daytime, Garen’s performance was merely strictly according to the rules and not as excellent as she had imagined. Meanwhile, the Dragonfire Spell in Boris’s hand was excessively powerful. He could kill one Giant Iguana with each attack, rendering them completely helpless. This caused her attention to be mainly focused on Boris now.

“I’m going to make a few rounds in our surroundings. Don’t worry, all of you should rest first. I’m just going to take a walk because I can’t sleep,” Garen answered flatly.

“It’s very dangerous at night,” said Boris in a concerned manner.

“It’s fine.” Garen had already started to push open the camouflaged snow wall as he spoke. He burrowed out of the hole in the snow that he had spread open. Next, he quickly resealed and restuffed the stone wall that was used as a door.

During the night, the natural purple moon had cast a hazy purple halo that penetrated through the snowstorm.

An abundance of snowflakes that were only the size of fingernails cascaded down sideways when they were blown by the wind. They fell on Garen’s body and face and allowed him to clearly feel their fine striking strength.

He turned around his surroundings. He was currently standing at the foot of one of the cliffs. There was nothing but a stretch of pure whiteness before him. He could only see a distance of more than ten meters. Despite the illumination of the purple moon’s halo and the natural Darkvision that White Dragons possessed, he could only see darkness any further than that.

He had merely stood at the cave entrance for less than half a minute but he could already feel both of his legs sinking downwards slightly. A part of his legs was already submerged in the falling snowflakes.

“Weather like this is advantageous to Giant Iguanas. No wonder they’ve lived here permanently throughout the years. It’s fine when there aren’t any snowstorms during the day. Nonetheless, the current night-time period is probably the time when they’re most active.”

Garen lifted his legs and walked forward gently one step at a time. He walked towards the flat area within the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range according to the directions in his memory.

Under this heavy snow, every single trace of battle such as the corpses and skeletons that remained would quickly be buried in the whirling snowstorm.

Garen did not dare to fly at all. Flying in this sort of weather where he could not see his way clearly would cause him to lose his sense of direction. It was the same everywhere. In the event that he fell headfirst into a herd of Giant Iguanas…

He could only inch his way forward while stepping in both deep and shallow areas. He orientated himself in one precise direction. He was too afraid to change his direction rashly because it was likely that he would lose his way back.

An enormous silhouette appeared in the whistling snowstorm quickly.

A Giant Iguana!

Garen focused and held his breath suddenly before lightening his footsteps.

He had never attempted to challenge a Level Four Giant Iguana on his own. Coincidentally, it was time for him to try it now.

The Giant Iguana had clearly noticed him earlier. The surface of its entire body was already covered in the Ice Armor in advance. This was a Level Four Innate Spell that possessed above-average defensive abilities.

Pfoo, pfoo, pfoo!

The Giant Iguana charged towards Garen directly in a somewhat annoyed manner.

The most common attack moves of these creatures included swaying their tails, headbutts, and biting or tearing. Coupled with their extremely thick armored skin and Innate Spells, these three moves were enough to render most middle-level creatures helpless.

Garen stared at the Giant Iguana carefully. His experience during the daytime battle had already allowed him to understand the Level Four Giant Iguana’s data more thoroughly.

“Since its speed is around fourteen points, I can dodge it easily. Its strength should be somewhere between nineteen to twenty-five points.”

He watched the Giant Iguana charge directly at himself. He could not block the impulse of this charging approach even if their strength was the same.

He shook his wings rapidly and swerved towards the right.

However, the Giant Iguana’s tail twisted towards him head-on immediately. The combo moves that this creature was accustomed to using was occurring again.

Garen lowered his body. Since he was as agile as a human, he could easily evade the violent tail that was whipping towards him.

This Giant Iguana’s body was almost seven meters long and it was not lacking in strength. From the sound of the whistling wind that blew past his face, Garen guessed that his opponent’s strength was at least twenty-two points.

“It’s unfortunate that its speed is too slow.” Garen rushed forwards once he had evaded its tail. Coincidentally, there was a gap in the Giant Iguana’s defenses at that moment when it was unable to turn around and attack in time. Garen clawed the Giant Iguana’s backside then.

The strength of his claw and the Giant Iguana’s own power were not much different but his own speed was much quicker. As the average Dragon Whelp could surpass the speed of this Giant Iguana, there was no way for it to hide at all.

Garen stabbed his claw into the Giant Iguana’s backside violently.

An intense earth-shattering pained roar erupted.

Garen could only hear a thunderous noise in his ears instantly when he tried to remove his claw determinedly.

The tail swished back and forth and thrashed towards him at this moment.

It would simply be a joke if Garen were to be hit by this straightforward attack method.

He shook his wings gently and flew upwards before evading the creature’s tail easily once again. Once he had reached this level, unless the difference between the attributes of both parties was far too great, opponents that did not possess close combat grades or realms that were strong enough could never defeat Garen directly.

The Giant Iguana’s body was seven to eight meters long while Garen’s current Dragon Whelp self had only matured to a petite body of more than a meter long. Since he could not endure too many strikes, he had to be extra careful.

Chapter 1264: Hunt 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Shh!

Garen struck the Giant Iguana’s backside with his claw again.

As the top half of this Giant Iguana’s body was covered by an Ice Armor, Garen would need to attack one area at least two to three times continuously before he could break its defenses. However, this was not the case for its buttocks and the areas behind.

The Giant Iguana’s cumbersome body made it more troublesome for him to turn towards Garen. Garen managed to successfully strike him multiple times continuously as he attacked its backside.

Red blood flowed out of its buttocks continuously and trickled on the snow-covered ground before it froze into ice speedily.

The Giant Iguana’s pained roars became quieter while the movements of its entire body began slowing down gradually as well.

Finally, after over ten minutes, the Level Four Giant Iguana lowered its head and smashed it against the ground when it was completely exhausted. It could only sigh while crawling on the ground. The Ice Armor on its body scattered.

Garen walked over and smashed his claw against the creature’s forehead. Since it did not break open completely the first time, he replenished his energy briefly before scratching and cracking the surface armor and sticking his claw inside to dig out the Crystal Core. Next, he used both of his claws to gouge out its eyeballs quickly.

The eyeballs froze into balls quickly once they had left the Giant Iguana’s body. Moreover, these eyeballs would only last for a maximum duration of ten days without a specialized storage method.

“This wasn’t as simple as when we had Boris’ Dragonfire Spell.” Garen only felt the true power of the Dragonfire Spell now because it could destroy a Giant Iguana instantly.

He took the Crystal Core and felt it carefully. Indeed, he could actually feel the subtle potential aura that was constantly seeping out of the Crystal Core and burrowing into his skin. The potential value at the bottom of his field of vision was also beginning to increase slowly.

“I need to carry this with me at all times.” He rubbed the Crystal Core against the powdery snow and got rid of the traces of blood. However, he became dispirited instantly when he remembered that White Dragons were not accustomed to wearing clothes and had no way of carrying many items. The important items that they carried with them this time were placed in the large leather sack that Leona wore on her body.

“This is somewhat troublesome…” He pondered and simply threw it into his mouth. There was a cracking noise when his teeth clenched down firmly on the Crystal Core and broke it into pieces. Moreover, he had almost damaged his teeth instead as well.

“So hard!” Level Four Crystal Cores were already so hard. If this were a Level Five Crystal Core, he would not have been able to bite it at all.

“It’s truly troublesome.” Garen could feel the broken pieces of the Crystal Core that he had bitten. The potential value inside was currently surging into his body rapidly while his mind was slightly consoled.

However, he could feel his teeth faintly cracking. He would certainly not do this again next time.

He thought that this would not be an issue because he had assumed that a dragon’s teeth were the strongest parts of their bodies. He had never expected that they would break into pieces instead. Therefore, these were not minor losses.

He swallowed the Crystal Core in one mouthful. Garen glanced at the corpse on the ground before continuing to move forward.

Another black silhouette appeared in front of him quickly. One more Giant Iguana had appeared. However, this Giant Iguana was clearly much larger than the previous one. It was over ten meters long. A disdainful look flowed out of the Giant Iguana’s eyes when it saw that Garen was tiny in comparison.

Garen’s heart tightened before he retreated hurriedly.

“This excellent fellow… is definitely Level Five!” Its body was incomparable to a mere Level Four.

However, this Giant Iguana was clearly not prepared to let him go. Its body that was twelve meters long could apparently run at a speed that was faster than the previous Giant Iguana. The trampling of its four heavy limbs kicked up large amounts of snow.

By looking at its strength, Garen knew that his opponent was definitely more powerful than himself.

“I can’t fight recklessly!” He shook his wings and dodged towards the left.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a grey shadow swept over violently. The speed of this fellow’s tail was at least three times faster than the previous Giant Iguana.

Garen was terribly shocked and hit until he could not react in time. The Giant Iguanas that he had encountered in the daytime could hardly move their tails this quickly.

Bang!

His inaccurate estimation of his enemy’s speed caused him to be violently struck by its swaying tail.

Garen could only feel as if his entire body was painfully hit by the front of a train before his whole dragon body flew backward instantly like a rubber ball. Cracking noises echoed from his body immediately, indicating an unknown number of broken bones.

Its possessed at least twenty-three points of strength! Moreover, its speed was terribly fast!

Garen’s mind was in a state of shock. How would he fight it?

He endured the pain and flapped his wings while flying towards his right swiftly.

He recalled all of the various skills that he possessed. Most of them were unusable because they were restricted by certain laws while the few types that were usable were mostly used by human bodies. Therefore, it was impossible for him to use them with his current White Dragon body. The only one that he could employ was a set of attack and one-hit kill moves that he had reformed with much difficulty during the past duration of time.

“I haven’t tried out its effects yet so this is a good opportunity to test it out.” When he was hit this time, Garen exhausted a lot of his energy in order to use the appropriate defenses. However, since his own strength was great as well, he did not lose any mobility.

Any other Dragon Whelp that had been in his place would probably be useless at this moment.

After flying more than ten meters away, Garen relied on flapping his wings to buffer the unloaded strength. When he descended once again, he could see that the Giant Iguana was continuing to charge towards him.

The speed of this fellow’s tail was faster than usual. Moreover, it had currently surpassed him terribly. As he could not see clearly at all, Garen was constantly vigilant about the whipping tail.

Ice Pressure Blade.

Garen crouched down suddenly while raising both of his claws upwards. His body coincidentally burrowed into the uncovered space near the Giant Iguana’s abdomen while his sharp claws scratched precisely and dangerously across the Giant Iguana’s abdomen firmly.

The Giant Iguana could not swing its tail towards this area no matter how hard it tried.

Garen’s claws vibrated at top speed endlessly. He used a strange frequency to adjust his fine arc before slicing the grain of the Giant Iguana’s abdominal armored skin.

Shh!

The slicing motion made a single noise.

The Giant Iguana let out a frenzied, pained roar. It accelerated and charged forward but ended up helping Garen increase his friction and cutting strength.

A crashing noise erupted before a large cut appeared at the back of its abdomen when it was sliced open immediately. The areas that were covered by the Ice Armor were only inflicted with damage on the armor itself. However, a huge wound that was over three meters long had appeared white-grey in his white-grey stomach near its abdomen that was not covered by the Ice Armor.

Garen rolled away from the side of the Giant Iguana’s body. Since the Giant Iguana was chaotically whipping its tail around in pain this time, there was no way for it to determine the direction that Garen had rolled towards.

Garen had just rolled away and had yet to get up from the snow-covered ground when he heard a fierce quake that was spreading out furiously in the direction of the Giant Iguana.

Bang!!

Large amounts of powdery snow were formed into a substantial shock wave that was sent flying because of the vibrations. This affected Garen as well who flew away when he was mixed in the snow.

He could not help but spit out a mouthful of blood in mid-air.

The four limbs of the Level Five Giant Iguana stomped on the ground violently and formed intense shock waves. These ripples were not force field ripples but were closer to elemental attacks.

“Level Five’s Earthquake…” Garen recalled the Giant Iguana’s skill. He had never expected that its power would be so great. However, it was useless now. Even if he had known about this skill earlier, he would still have to resist it firmly now. Regardless of how he dodged it, the only way that he could fully counter this Earthquake skill was to immediately fill the space around the skill user within a ten-meter radius with this type of low-frequency violent vibration waves.

Garen was badly injured now.

He had never expected that one Level Five Giant Iguana would be so difficult to handle.

However, the other party had belittled him as well. If his opponent had attacked at full throttle from the start and whipped its tail to increase its Earthquake skill directly, Garen would not have stood a single chance. He could have only fled with critical injuries then.

Hence, it was different now.

Garen flapped his wings determinedly and stayed far away from the Giant Iguana. Although he was badly injured, he exerted his legs and wings simultaneously. The Giant Iguana could not catch up to his speed.

Moreover, the key point was that the Giant Iguana’s belly was sliced open while its intestines had spilled on the ground. Since its intelligence was somewhat lower and it was provoked to the point of blind fury, it simply murderously pursued Garen with all of its might. Meanwhile, it trampled all over its own intestines on the ground and smashed them into a pulp. More of its blood flowed out before the surrounding snowy ground was completely dyed red by its blood.

The dragon and Giant Iguana chased each other for several minutes before the Giant Iguana finally collapsed on the ground and stopped moving completely.

Its gigantic body lurched forward because of the drive before it dragged out a clear mark behind it.

Garen’s entire body was covered in wounds while an unknown number of bones in his body were broken.

His vitality was only slightly stronger than the average Dragon Whelps but his upgraded strength was more significant than that. However, even if this was the case, he could barely break through the Giant Iguana’s skin when he fused his strength with the Ice Pressure Blade skill. Hence, the difference between their power was far too great.

If this Giant Iguana had not been careless, it would probably be impossible for Garen to kill it even if he wanted to do so.

When he saw the Giant Iguana collapse, he dragged his own heavily injured body over and rushed there frantically.

He could already faintly hear the sound of the movements of other Giant Iguanas that indicated that they were approaching despite the surrounding snowstorm.

“I must hurry or else the spoils of battle may not necessarily be mine.” Garen ran over quickly before digging his claw into the Giant Iguana’s forehead firmly.

There was a puffing noise when his claw was apparently unable to break through its defenses but was only able to inflict a small wound instead.

The sound of footsteps around him indicated that they were closer now. Garen became slightly more panicked and clawed at it firmly again.

The little wound instantly expanded slightly before the white skull underneath was revealed.

However, the Giant Iguana was not completely dead yet. It let out a pained roar again but it was much weaker this time.

Roar!

Suddenly, within a distance that was very near, another similar Giant Iguana’s roar echoed in response. The sound of footsteps that were coming from many others that were approaching around it stopped suddenly. They were clearly deterred by this low roar.

By listening to the noise that indicated the weight of the creature, Garen could immediately determine that the approaching Giant Iguana that had roared earlier would definitely not be weaker than the fellow that he had just gotten rid of painstakingly.

There would be no time left if he did not leave now!

He clawed at it furiously one last time before smashing its skull open. He dug the Crystal Core out with the smashed bones as well.

He turned around and fled before he could even take the eyeballs in time. He flapped his wings and flew off immediately.

At this moment, a tail that was as quick as lightning whipped behind him hurriedly. Despite clearly being unable to reach him because of the distance, the gigantic tail actually managed to sweep up a large patch of snow.

The snow crashed towards Garen in an earth-shattering manner as if it was a steel whip when it was acted upon by the tremendous force.

The Ice Pressure Blade that Garen had only recently learned was supposed to increase the attack abilities of his claws. However, it was useless in the defensive aspects.

He could only resist firmly.

Pfoo…

A large amount of snow fell on his body violently.

Garen could only feel as if his entire body was being pierced by needles before his whole dragon body was sent flying backward brutally. He did not know how far he rolled. He rolled and flew dizzily in the snowstorm in mid-air for more than ten seconds before dropping on the ground quickly.

It seemed as though he was directly flung on to the top of a cliff by the tail. The end of the cliff was in front of him while a boundless dark snowstorm was on the other side.

Garen held the Crystal Core determinedly before looking at his own state briefly. He laughed bitterly at once.

The situation was somewhat tragic now.

‘Safive — Strength 21(5), Agility 15(4), Vitality 11(4), Intelligence 17. Potential 48%. Soul Limit 170’

Level 1 Draconic Aura. Level 1 Arcane Art Basics.

All of his attributes had deteriorated to these temporary states and were almost weaker by one level.

“Now I’ll just have to see if this Level Five Crystal Core was worth this risk or not.” Garen only felt the dangers of the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range now. No wonder the Adult White Dragons gave Leona and Boris Level Five Enchanted Equipment and were very uneasy this whole time. They also made it compulsory for them to form groups.

When he looked at it now, if he had formed a group and made sure that all of the other Dragon Whelps were of the same standard as himself, he might have been able to barely challenge the Level Five Giant Iguana. However, the movements of battle would bring numerous uncertain dangers. Just like earlier…

Chapter 1265: Opportunity 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He had attracted a similar Level Five Giant Iguana immediately. If he had left slightly later, he would probably lose all hope of seeing the sun tomorrow.

Garen laid his back on the icy floor. The pain was coursing throughout his entire body. These injuries would probably take a few days to heal.

He pinched the Level Five Crystal Core and placed it in front of himself to take a look.

The subtle potential aura was currently surging outwards continuously and burrowing into his skin.

“According to this speed, I probably need three days before I can absorb the potential aura inside completely. The total amount is probably equivalent to one attribute point or a potential value of 100%.” Garen made these calculations mentally.

Since his Energy Machine Imprint had collapsed, he could only perform calculations on his own. Reconstructing the Energy Machine would require a rebuilding period which made it very troublesome. It was fortunate that this world could contain a type of strength such as Willpower.

Aside from Willpower, there were other types of Secret Technique strength that could be contained as well. However, the strength of most Secret Techniques was indeed slightly weaker in comparison to the grades of the forces in this world. Moreover, he did not come here this time to reconstruct his Secret Technique but to discover the reason behind the Depletion of the Mother Stream. If it was possible, he did not want to die with the Mother Stream. On the contrary, he wanted to alter the other systems instead.

He rested on the ice for a few minutes. Garen felt his body somewhat heal slightly. Only then did he crawl up slowly. He rubbed the Crystal Core against the snow-covered ground and cleaned it before placing it in his mouth in one go and swallowing it directly into his belly.

This Crystal Core was merely the size of a walnut. It was insignificant to a Dragon Whelp that possessed stronger devouring abilities.

Garen felt slightly safer once he had swallowed the Crystal Core. However, his stomach felt somewhat uncomfortable now.

“It looks like I can’t swallow it directly next time… I need to think of another way.”

He scanned his surroundings and vaguely estimated the direction he had flown. Next, there was a snapping noise as he flapped his wings and flew down towards the snowy cliff to return to his original path.

The snowstorm whooshed and whistled. Garen hid in the snowy night. Currently, he could not afford to provoke even one Level Four Giant Iguana because his speed had decreased too much. His strength and vitality had also deteriorated terribly. He was completely at wit’s end now and could only turn circles and make a detour.

It was fortunate that his intelligence was very high. Although his memory was not as good as usual, his brain’s sense of direction was also pretty amazing. He could find his way around in the snowy night while hiding as well as locate the place where his little group had hidden once again.

The snowstorm had lessened slightly. When Garen was standing at the entrance of the cave that was used as their hiding spot, the sky had already turned brighter.

He rolled on the snowy ground a few times to cover the traces of blood and wounds on his body in a layer of ice. Next, he smelled himself carefully to ensure that the scent of blood did not linger on his body. He also found some delicate white fern-like plants that were growing beside the cracks in the rocks. These non-poisonous plants produced strong sweet scents. After crushing it, Garen rubbed it all over his body multiple times.

Only then did he push the snow wall open before walking into the cave.

The three remaining Dragon Whelps were still snoring and sleeping soundly inside. Other than Boris who had sensed him entering and opened his eyes to glance at him blurrily, the other two did not respond at all. Saszt had even drooled all over the floor. His saliva had frozen into ice on both sides and fixed his large mouth on the floor, making him look very silly.

Garen resealed the hole in the snow properly while feeling as if this expedition had been truly somewhat risky.

He crouched down once again and crawled into an empty corner before falling asleep gradually. He felt the coldness that was constantly emitted from the potential aura before dozing off into dreamland slowly.

On the second day, after sleeping for twelve full hours, the four Dragon Whelps crawled up slowly and yawned continuously.

Boris pushed the snow wall open firmly before a gust of cold wind blew in from the outside. The four Dragon Whelps crawled out one after another. The layers of snow on the outside had almost buried the cave entrance.

They climbed a few steps upwards along the layers of snow. Garen yawned while his entire body ached. His entire body was terribly weak. Yesterday’s critical injuries had finally displayed their formidable effects.

He glanced at the state of his current attributes.

‘Safive — Strength 21(7), Agility 15(7), Vitality 11(6), Intelligence 12. Potential 68%. Soul Limit 170’

Level 1 Draconic Aura. Level 1 Arcane Art Basics.

“They’ve been restored slightly. However, I don’t think that I can catch up to the values of average Dragon Whelps.” Garen was helpless. It looked like he needed to hold back today.

“Garen, why do you look so dispirited?” Leona slapped Garen firmly from behind and almost knocked him down.

The area that she had hit was now aching with a fiery pain.

Garen was helpless.

“No reason. I encountered a Giant Iguana when I went out for a stroll last night. I ran in circles everywhere for a long distance before finally returning. I’ve exhausted a lot of energy.”

“You encountered a Giant Iguana? Oh my god, you’re so brave,” Leona sighed in shock.

Garen chatted with Leona while thinking about what he would do today. It was fortunate that although he was injured, the sharpness of his claws was not affected. Basic coordination would probably not be an issue.

During the second day of hunting, they encountered another new Level Four Giant Iguana quickly.

This fellow was taking large chomps out of a White Dragon Whelp’s corpse on the ground and chewing it.

When Garen and the group of dragons saw this scene, Saszt could not stop himself from charging over immediately. The battle began at once.

Naturally, the Level Four Giant Iguana was not their opponent when the Four Dragon Whelps could coordinate with each other skillfully. Saszt became the main supporting strength body while Garen followed from behind and used the Ice Pressure Blade to increase the strength of his claws and killing power. They managed to injure the Giant Iguana’s skin and although they could not kill it because of its Ice Armor, they could enrage it effectively.

Garen had clearly grasped the way the Level Four Giant Iguana moved. Although their speed was slower and their strength was much weaker, Garen was not afraid because Saszt was here to support him significantly. When he noticed that the pieces of the Giant Iguana’s muscles were moving, he could determine its attack direction. Hence, his own speed had decelerated greatly. Nonetheless, they could still dodge many of the Giant Iguana’s oncoming attacks easily as Saszt was there to keep things in check and ward it off.

Therefore, the distribution of work here was very obvious. Saszt was mainly responsible for moving forward and providing the bulk of strength while Garen would spare some time to take revenge on the Giant Iguana. Meanwhile, Boris and Leona executed the Dragonfire Spells behind them.

They cooperated skillfully to take one Giant Iguana down. Saszt had suffered some light injuries while his muscles were faintly exhausted. After all, this was the first time that he had acted as the main attacking dragon. As Garen was fighting alongside him previously, the pressure this time was naturally greater.

Garen allowed the Giant Iguana to scratch and hurt his shoulder on purpose as well so that he could look as beaten up as Saszt.

Boris came forward to dig the Crystal Core out before giving it to Leona and placing it with the rest so that she could keep track.

“Come come come, I’ll heal your wounds.”

Leona could only watch from the sidelines all this while. Now that both Saszt and Garen were hurt, she instantly felt as if she could use her abilities now. She rushed forward happily.

This was the result that Garen wanted. He stood next to Saszt.

Leona raised her hand before them while a pure white water flowed out and gathered there. The fluid floated in the air before quickly condensing into a ball of water that looked as if it was milk that had gathered in one place.

Bleurgh.

A large mouth spread open in the surface of the milk ball before it exerted all of its strength and vomited some translucent light white sticky liquid. This sticky liquid dispersed into numerous little water droplets that flew towards Garen and Saszt continuously.

“It looks so gross…” Saszt’s entire body felt uneasy.

“Don’t worry, don’t worry. This is merely a fixed process of this spell. It’s not as if a real creature is vomiting this out…” Leona whispered as if she was slightly out of breath.

Garen felt a psychological block as well. However, he could only endure it to heal his wounds as soon as possible.

Among the sticky water droplets that flew out, almost one-third of them flew towards Saszt quickly while the remaining majority flew on to Garen’s body.

Most of these water droplets covered the surface of his body before burrowing inside through the cracks of his dragon scales and penetrating into his skin.

Garen instantly felt as if his entire body had cooled down, making him extremely comfortable. The aching areas received some effective relief.

This sensation lasted for several minutes before disappearing quickly.

“How miraculous! My injuries are actually healed!” yelled Saszt beside him in a happily surprised tone.

Meanwhile, Garen glanced at his statistics.

‘Safive — Strength 21(11), Agility 15(12), Vitality 11(11), Intelligence 17. Potential 69%. Soul Limit 170

Level 1 Draconic Aura. Level 1 Arcane Art Basics.’

“Its effects are pretty good. It restored an average of four points throughout my attributes during this one time. It can probably restore everything fully if I use it another few times.” However, Garen knew that it was better not to reveal the fact that he had left to hunt alone without informing the others. Anyway, Leona had the Dragonheal Spell that could be used thrice in a day. Since he was always getting injured, he could heal himself quickly as long as he used it in the future. Meanwhile, he had also gained a deeper understanding of Level Four Giant Iguanas. Hence, it would not be a major issue because Saszt would be there to support him as well.

This group of Dragon Whelps would not provoke Level Five Giant Iguanas anymore.

“Come over and look, you guys. This Dragon Whelp’s corpse really looks like Burdock from the third class.” Boris was investigating a Dragon Whelp’s corpse on the side. Only half of its corpse remained because the rest had been chewed up.

The other Dragon Whelps gathered over there. They looked at the corpse of the Dragon Whelp that was gnawed beyond recognition.

Leona was slightly afraid while Saszt was burning with fury as his fighting spirit increased. Only Boris and Garen remained calm.

“It was probably killed by a Level Five Giant Iguana. We need to be careful after this because there may be Level Five Giant Iguanas nearby. Don’t act rashly,” Boris whispered.

The three remaining dragons nodded.

After that, the group of Dragon Whelps continued hunting. They did not venture any deeper into the mountain range but wandered around the nearby area instead. They were looking for Level Four Giant Iguanas in particular to practice their skills. However, it seemed like they were not as lucky on the second day because they had only encountered one lone Level Four Giant Iguana. The others that they encountered were either in packs of three or four or were Level Five Giant Iguanas instead.

If it was not for the White Dragon Whelps excellent vision, the situation would have truly become tragic once they approached the Giant Iguanas.

They had merely hunted one Level Four Giant Iguana before the daytime scenery turned dimmed. Boris continued leading the other three dragons in search of a hiding spot. He had hunted here before so he knew the location of the safest hiding spots.

This time, they found a precipice in the middle of a cliff before they dug out a cave with all their might and burrowed inside. It would definitely be impossible for Giant Iguanas to discover them in terrains like this because they could not fly.

Garen did not dare to sneak out and hunt alone this time anymore. Instead, he was waiting for the Crystal Core inside his stomach to be absorbed completely. He would obtain one new attribute point because of this. Moreover, when he added it to his vitality, it would speed up the healing process of his bodily wounds.

********************

Inside a deep cave in the depths of the icy snow

Darkness, coldness, and chills that were as sharp as knife edges spun slowly in the depths of the cave endlessly like an enormous twisting whirlpool.

On both sides of the cave, numerous sets of imposing knight’s armor were positioned upright in a crouching stance with one knee on the ground. These sets of black knight’s armor were empty on the inside while they held broad and heavy knight’s swords with both of their hands. The edges of their swords pierced into the ground deeply. Seemingly countless strange symbols were engraved into their sheets of armor in a densely-packed manner. These symbols resembled tadpoles that were constantly swimming around. They were unimaginably strange and were all releasing faint auras of death.

“It’s like… there’s a kind of smell…” Suddenly, a gloomy voice echoed from the depths of the cave. It sounded like an old man that was about the die as the voice was hinted with an air of exhaustion and decay.

After a short period of silence, the voice sounded again.

“It’s a powerful soul… A powerful Aberrated Soul. It smells good… Smells so good…” Greed and longing were indirectly revealed in the voice.

“Baschin.”

Pfoo…

Among the sets of knight’s armor that were kneeling on one knee on both sides of the cave, moss green flames were ignited in the eyes of the helmet’s one of these armors.

He stood up and drew his giant sword out of the ground before taking long strides towards the path in the center of the cave. He faced the interior of the cave as if he was waiting for orders.

“Master, I await your instructions.”

Chapter 1266: Opportunity 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“Go bring that soul back here,” The voice spoke.

All of a sudden, a black thread shot forth inside the cave. This black thread quickly wove itself into a round ring in mid-air, and then the center of the ring slowly split apart, forming a mirror inside.

The surface of the mirror was as bright as new, and it slowly began to reflect a line of white Dragon Whelps. There were four of them, hiding inside a cave and chatting idly.

The green flames in the Knight’s eyes flickered for a moment, and then they instantly locked onto one of the Dragon Whelps.

This white dragon was well-proportioned, with strong muscles and scales that seemed brighter and cleaner than the other white dragons.

It bowed toward the depths of the cave and then turned around and walked out of the cave, clattering as it went. There was an extremely complex golden screen turning slowly at the mouth of the cave, blocking off all the threats that might walk out of the cave.

But the Knight seemed to be completely oblivious to it, walking straight toward the golden screen at the mouth of the cave.

As soon as the Knight walked into it, the translucent screen lit up with a whoosh, and a large cloud of black smoke was absorbed out of its armor.

The Black Knight walked out determinedly and managed to get past this golden screen eventually. Its foot stomped hard into the deep layer of snow outside.

Once it walked out, however, half of the many tadpole-like glyphs on its armor vanished, leaving only a small portion, and even those gave off an impression of aged fragility, as though it could fall apart at any time.

The Knight paid that no heed at all and just stood at the cave entrance, figuring out the direction. Then, it strode boldly in one direction. After a few steps, it actually began to fly.

Roar!!

A Giant Frost Iguana Elder rushed straight at it, racing at the Knight from underneath the snow. It was probably because the Knight had intruded into its territory. But when it saw the glyphs all over the Knight’s body, the Elder Giant Iguana’s pupils dilated abruptly.

“An Undead! Agony Knight!! Forgive me!!” It screeched in terror, an armor of ice instantly enveloping its entire body. This was Level Six Ice Armor, but at the same time it actually turned around and ran outward, showing no intention to resist whatsoever.

But before it got very far, a bolt of black light shot down from the sky. It was a spinning black Greatsword, the terrifying weapon three whole meters long, emanating large clouds of black smoke from all over its body as it spun rapidly downward.

Psst.

As easily as slicing through tofu, the black smoke Greatsword cut through the Elder Giant Iguana’s neck. And then it spun once above the snowy ground, before returning to the Knight’s hand in mid-air.

The Giant Iguana Elder’s large head rolled onto the floor, the thick Level Six armor had put up no resistance whatsoever. Without any chance of fighting back, a Level Six Giant Iguana Elder was killed by the Black Knight, just like that.

“A boring, insignificant soul…” The Knight gripped the Greatsword, and the black smoke from the blade seemed to pull something out from the Elder Giant Iguana’s body. The black smoke was a lot thicker than when it first came out and was currently flowing ceaselessly into the cracks in the Knight’s armor.

After killing the Giant Iguana, the Knight did not even look at the corpse beneath it. It just flew in the direction it had decided on.

It did not move very quickly, but wherever it went, all the Giant Iguanas avoided it in terror. No living creature dared to stand in its way.

In fact, some Giant Iguanas actually got onto their knees and began to kowtow at it.

*********************

On the third day, Garen finally finished absorbing that Level Five Crystal Core before leaving.

As he expected, the Crystal Core he had risked his life to obtain gave him one Attribute Point.

And after a night’s rest, his injuries had healed slightly and his average fitness returned to half its original value. Add that to his killing move, Ice Pressure Blade, and his combat power was about equivalent to Saszt’s now.

After departing on the third day, the four Dragon Whelps moved at a significantly faster speed. They were pretty lucky this time, since they met two Level Four Giant Iguanas consecutively, both of which had gone astray from the pack. They were easily finished off with a few Dragonfire Spells.

Boris also tried to attack some Level Four Giant Iguanas head-on, but unfortunately, once it was weakened by the Level Four Ice Armor, the power of the Dragonfire Spell was not strong enough to harm the Giant Iguana’s tough hide. Under these snowy conditions, the Level Four Ice Armor demonstrated its full power, whereas the Dragonfire Spell was drastically weakened. The increase on one side and decrease on the other meant that head-on Dragonfire Spells were practically useless.

The Giant Iguana soon released its Ice Armor again.

They could release their Ice Armor five times a day. It was a spell they were born with, so it did not consume too much of their power.

The group of Dragon Whelps kept moving from one location to another. Going through a long and narrow tunnel in the icy valley, they finally encountered another team of Dragon Whelps for the first time.

“Leona? Boris!” Outside the tunnel, the four Dragon Whelps stood together, discussing something. When they saw another group of Dragon Whelps walk out of the tunnel, the sturdiest-looking Dragon Whelp instantly started yelling.

“Toni!? How lucky, to think we’d meet you first!” Boris was instantly overjoyed, and he ran up to meet them.

“Toni, what are you guys doing here?” Leona asked as well. Clearly, she knew this Dragon Whelp.

“The way ahead is blocked,” said Toni, depressed. “I’m waiting for other teams to catch up, maybe we can gather together and eat these few Giant Iguanas.”

She looked left and right, and then approached Leona, whispering into her ear.

“There are two more Dragon Whelp teams around, but they’re all hiding now.”

“If there are so many Dragon Whelps here, we don’t necessarily have to take this path, do we? Are you waiting for something in there?” Garen asked in a soft voice.

Toni instantly looked at Garen, surprised. This one reacted really quickly, he could guess the truth even with so little to go on. He was almost on par with the cunning humans!

“Impressive!” She expressed admiration at Garen’s reaction. “There’s an Ice Stalagmite in there…”

“Whoa!” Boris and Leona gasped in unison.

The Ice Stalagmite was one of the rare and precious resources to come from this land of ice and snow. To Frost-type Creatures, that was a true treasure of the earth. A complete Ice Stalagmite could provide enough Frost Power to increase one’s power by one whole level. It worked on all Frost-type Creatures that were Level Six or below.

This was also the second reason the white dragons let their Dragon Whelps come here to hunt. They wanted the young ones to fight among each other, until only the strongest were left standing in their fight for the Ice Stalagmite. Only then could they truly become passable warriors.

“Looks like those Giant Iguanas are here to fight for the Ice Stalagmite as well,” said Garen softly.

“Yep. Two Level Fives, Four Level Fours. They’re split into two groups and standing off against each other now, but it’ll be any time now. There are at least Dragon Whelp Teams, including us, and we’re no match for them in a head-on fight. If both sides are left weakened after the fight, though, things might be different.” Clearly, it was not Toni’s first hunt either, her tone was very experienced and assured.

Garen had also noticed that the aura coming from Toni was stronger than Boris’. Looking at the shape of her muscles, he guessed that she was at least equivalent to Saszt in level. If she also had equipment fixed with Level Five Spells, she would truly be formidable.

Toni led the other dragons, including Leona and Boris, into the circle they had decided on before, and everyone banded into a temporary team. All of them were quietly awaiting any changes from up ahead.

It seemed as though Garen’s team was the last one, no more Dragon Whelps came after them.

The other two Dragon Whelp Teams never showed up, nobody knew what they were planning.

Bam!!

All of a sudden, there was a large explosion of snow from up ahead, sending the snow flying everywhere.

Roar!

There was a tremendous, explosive roar from a Giant Iguana. This was followed by several more consecutive roars.

There were a bang and a dull thud. The Giant Iguanas on each side had evidently started fighting.

Garen hid in the circle of Dragon Whelps, listening to the sounds from up ahead. Since he had fought a Level Five Giant Iguana hands-on, he could tell almost immediately. The first roar had probably come from a Level Five Giant Iguana.

Not only did Level Five Giant Iguanas have Level Five Ice Armor, they also had a powerful non-discriminatory attack, Earthquake. They were also much faster and stronger than regular Giant Iguanas. That made them extremely powerful.

There were so many Giant Iguanas in front of them, killing each other. There were two Level Five Giant Iguana Crystal Cores right there, if he could get his hands on them, it would help him greatly!

“I just have to be careful.”

He glanced at Leona and the other dragons. She was discussing something softly with Boris and Toni.

He knew how powerful Level Five Giant Iguanas were, so he understood how improbable it would be to kill Level Five Giant Iguanas with this group of Dragon Whelps. The only way would be to exhaust themselves using Level Five Spells, putting their own lives on the line.

But the Dragon Whelps would never be so coordinated, nobody would be willing to go there and be grievously injured from the swipe of a tail. It would be very dangerous to sustain serious injuries in a place like this.

Even Leona’s Dragonheal Spell could only heal three Dragon Whelps at once, and it could only heal light injuries at that. After all, the Dragon Race’s Magic Defense was too high, even Dragon Whelps would have their spell efficiency reduced by one level. This reduction applied to both positive and negative spells.

“But if I want to get those two Level Five Crystal Cores, it’d be a bit troublesome with so many Dragon Whelps around…” Garen added the recently-obtained Attribute Point to his Vitality without hesitation.

Instantly, he felt a cool comforting sensation flow out of his brain and spread to the rest of his body. He watched his status go from injured to barely injured, on the brink of recovery.

Looks like even if it was a whole potential point, it still was not as easy to completely heal a body as powerful as a dragon’s as compared to when he was a human. Once the foundations were strong enough, the power needed to recover would naturally increase as well.

Well, at least he had regained his combat power. Garen bent down.

Boom!

All of a sudden, there was an intense jolt from up ahead. Garen could immediately tell that it was probably the Level Five Giant Iguana’s Earthquake. And it was not just one either, both Giant Iguanas had used it at the same time.

As the Giant Iguanas wailed out, a Dragon Whelp from a hidden Dragon Whelp Team nearby could not help but fly up to see the situation. The Giant Iguanas could not see far anyway, so they were not worried at all.

“They broke the Ice Stalagmite!?” the Dragon Whelp roared loudly as soon as it glanced over.

The Ice Stalagmite was broken?!

Just then, Garen abruptly felt an immense potential aura surge out of the snowy area ahead of him.

“This potential aura!!!” His heart pounded madly. This potential aura was more than ten times that of a Level Five Crystal Core, if he could just get his hands on it!

Green light rose in his eyes. No matter what, he needed to get that Ice Stalagmite!!

Chapter 1267: Agony Knight 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“As for these little ones, as long as I’m a little more careful, they shouldn’t be too much of a problem.”

Garen’s heart was decided, and he left the team quietly, walking toward another corner. All the Dragon Whelps were distracted by the forces coming from the intense battle, so no dragon actually noticed his departure.

Following the wall of snow, Garen slowly walked to a crevice and listened to the commotion outside.

If he wanted to get the Ice Stalagmite, his current abilities were not quite enough, so he needed to use some other methods as well.

Garen walked around the site of the battle once. There was a team with a few Dragon Whelps hiding nearby, and he could feel their gazes burning into his back when he moved to certain areas. Some of those gazes clearly carried a warning.

He was unperturbed, continuing to search and remember the lay of the land around here.

A simple but somewhat brutal plan formed in his mind.

“Whatever, I just have to make sure Leona and the rest dodge it.”

Garen considered this simple plan over and over again, and finally decided to make his move.

*******************

Deep within the snowstorm.

Outside the tunnel, it looked as though two circles, one large and the other one small, were huddled against each other.

In the first circle, there were several Giant Iguanas killing each other around a sharp and broken stone. In the second circle behind it, there were many Dragon Whelps lying in wait.

The whole thing looked like a skewer of candied haws.

One Dragon Whelp, on the other hand, flew out of the tunnel, upward and outward. Bracing against the wind and the snow, it landed on top of the candied haws’ circular mountain.

The snowstorm was extremely dense here, so he could not see anything clearly at all. But Garen relied on his powerful memory and computational power to quickly find a spot above one of the hiding teams.

He carefully imprinted this spot into his memory, and then went in search of other spots.

*****************

“Eh? Where did Garen go?” Leona noticed someone was missing from his team and was instantly confused.

“I saw him go out by himself, but I don’t know what he went to do,” replied Saszt honestly.

“I keep feeling as though Garen’s a little mysterious. I don’t know if it’s just me, but he seems to like being a lone dragon,” said Boris unhappily.

“I think so too, a little.” Leona nodded in agreement.

“He’s just one Dragon Whelp, ignore him for now,” said Toni nonchalantly. “It’s fine for us to work together like this, right? If there are no problems, shall we just settle with this?”

“Sure. Once the battle starts, clear off the other Dragon Whelps first,” agreed Boris.

“Then it’s decided.”

The two sides formed a temporary alliance.

The other Dragon Whelps did not have Enchantments, so they had no speaking rights here. They could not leave these leaders and operate on their own as Garen could. Without a Level Five offensive spell, they could not kill a Level Four Giant Iguana. Instead, they would be hunted down and killed.

******************

“Hmph, it seems that Toni got some support, whad’we do?” Inside another dug-out cave, several Dragon Whelps gathered together and discussed in whispers.

“It’s fine, we just stay in here no matter what, and only go out once they’ve more or less settled their fight with the Giant Iguanas. They can have those few Crystal Cores, our true aim is the Ice Stalagmite!”

A Dragon Whelp with slightly red skin said softly.

“Can we really do that?”

“Of course, with my Magic Equipment, there won’t be any problems whatsoever!” said the reddish Dragon Whelp confidently. “Then we’ll catch them all in one fell swoop! Heh heh heh… If they’re seriously injured, we can demand that they hand over all the Crystal Cores.”

“Deth, you’re a genius!” The other Dragon Whelps began to gasp in admiration.

“Good, as long as you guys get it. You won’t regret following me!” Deth was extremely pleased with himself.

*********************

Garen lay sprawled on a very high cliff. Looking down, he saw that everything was completely white. He could not see or hear anything, the wails of the snowstorm drowning out the sounds from the Giant Iguana battle below.

He could not see or hear anything from up here.

But it was fine, Garen had already determined his location using his own sense of direction and memory. The Giant Iguana battlefield was directly beneath him.

Unlike the other Dragon Whelps, his intelligence far surpassed theirs.

The development of a White Dragon’s brain was not particularly advanced, and so it was naturally no match for his seventeen points.

He calculated the process slightly.

Garen began to use his claws to cut through the hard ground with his Ice Pressure Blade.

He smashed and stabbed at the ground, and with each cut he carved out deep slashes. He had already memorized the lay and path of the land here.

Soon enough, he had dug a gaping hole out of this elephant-sized snowy cliff, such that it could fall at any minute.

He could only accomplish this because he had the Ice Pressure Blade, an extremely high-sharpness claw technique.

Without hesitation, Garen flew upward and then smashed his body down hard.

Ka-chak.

The entire snowy cliff emitted a crisp sound, and whatever remained of the final link snapped instantly.

Amidst the howling of the snowstorm, that little cracking was not particularly ear-piercing or clear; instead, it was completely drowned out. Garen saw the entire elephant-sized snowy cliff roll down, rumbling as it went.

Not long later, barroom!

There was an enormous rumble, and he abruptly heard loud howls of agony coming from below. It seemed like he had managed to hit a Giant Iguana!

Garen tried to distinguish them carefully, but he could not tell which Iguana had been hit. Well, as long as he managed to hit one and break the stalemate, he considered it a success.

A battle must have erupted down there.

Garen quickly moved to where the other Dragon Whelps were hiding.

Using the same moves as before, he began to cut up other large chunks of ice. Sometimes he would meet rock, and then he would cut through that easily as well. Dragon claws had always been sharp and deadly. Add that to his special technique, and the degree of sharpness increased exponentially.

There was another rumble, and yet another chunk of ice went rolling down.

This time, he did not hear any sounds from the Dragon Whelps, probably because the snowstorm was too intense. Regardless, Garen knew with certainty that he had caught the Iguanas’ attention.

This Dragon Whelp hiding spot was the closest one, so once a Dragon Whelp was injured, the smell of blood would be as clear as a lighthouse in the dark of the night to the Giant Iguanas and their acute sense of smell.

And then, once they discover that there was an ambush lying in wait, they would definitely finish off the hiding ones first.

He had carefully calculated it all, this spot just happened to be the nearest to the Giant Iguanas, so even if there was no smell of blood, it would still give the Giant Iguanas a sense of threat, forcing them to speed up the battle.

Garen did not linger and continued walking to the third position he had marked.

Only he could wander around like this in such a heavy snowstorm. The other Dragon Whelps did not have such a sense of direction and memory, and would easily get lost in the storm if they were not careful.

The third chunk went down as well.

Watching the broken cliff roll down, Garen noticed that this one seemed to be off-target. The storm had suddenly intensified, blowing it off-course.

“But it’s fine, I can grab the Iguana’s attention too by creating a commotion.”

He was not bothered at all. He did not touch the fourth chunk, however, because that was where Leona and the others were hiding.

Walking back the way he came, Garen patted down his claws, and all the traces he left behind were completely buried by the snowstorm.

******************

Roar!

A Level Five Giant Iguana was hit in the back by a giant broken cliff. As a result, it was pressed onto the ground and could only roar out furiously as it stayed there, completely sprawled.

The other Level Five Giant Iguana was being surrounded by the four remaining Level Four ones. Hide, blood, and flesh was sent flying on both sides as they wrestled with and tore away at each other.

Two of the Level Four Giant Iguanas had large gashes clawed out of their sides, and the blood froze as soon as it began to flow, forming red ice crystals. Meanwhile, the only Level Five Giant Iguana had been blinded in one eye, and there was a deep scratch on one side of its neck. One of its back legs had also gone limp, so all in all, it made a pitiful sight.

Bam!

It made one last effort and used its final Earthquake, jolting away the four Level Four Giant Iguanas around it, but also finishing up the last of its power.

The four Level Four Giant Iguanas were also completely exhausted by this point and riddled with wounds. If it were not for the chunk of a snowy cliff that fell down suddenly from above, taking out one of the Level Five Giant Iguanas, the weaker ones probably would have no other choice than to turn tail and run.

Looking at the broken Ice Stalagmite a little off the center of the area, the remaining Giant Iguanas roared happily, as though chasing away the Level Five Giant Iguanas.

Battles between Giant Iguanas did not usually end in death.

Helplessly, the Level Five Giant Iguana helped its companion push away the broken cliff, and the two of them prepared to leave, one after the other, heads lowered dejectedly. Their Ice Armor had also been used up during the fight, so if they did not leave now, they might attract the unwanted attention of other Giant Iguanas.

Just then, a wave of huge tremors came from the direction of the only exit.

The few Giant Iguanas were instantly alert.

“Goooo!!” Immediately after that, they saw a group of white Dragon Whelps rush out. They were only as tall as half a man each, but greed sparkled in their eyes.

There were more than ten Dragon Whelps in total, and they all made a mad rush for the Ice Stalagmite in the middle.

The Dragon Whelps went to the injury-riddled Level Five Giant Iguanas, the rings and necklaces on their arms twinkling with a rainbow-colored light. These were clearly Enchanted items, affixed with high-level spells.

“If a large boulder hadn’t suddenly fallen from above, we could’ve totally waited a bit longer before making our move!” said Boris exasperatedly. He looked at the Giant Iguana ahead of him and shuddered slightly in his heart. That was still a Level Five Giant Iguana, after all!

“What are you scared of, it doesn’t have any more Natural Spells left! Right now is precisely when it’s weakest,” said another Dragon Whelp on the other side loudly. It was Deth, who had originally planned to lie in wait and scavenge the final spoils. Now, however, he was a complete mess, having clearly been wounded by the broken cliff as well. As such, he had a stomach full of pent-up anger.

He was already chased out here by that cliff, so if he still refused to fight along with everyone else, the other Dragon Whelps would not be foolish enough to wait. Instead, they would make the first move. That was why he had to abandon his plan and make his own move ahead of schedule.

Even so, anyone would be slightly intimidated when facing a Level Five Giant Iguana like that.

“I’ll hold ’em up!” A powerfully-built Dragon Whelp rushed out abruptly. Aiming its claws at the Giant Iguana’s eyes fearlessly.

Whoosh!

A giant tail swiped at him mercilessly with lightning speed, as though hitting a rubber ball, and sent the Dragon Whelp flying. White blood sprayed instantly. They did not need to see it to know that this Dragon Whelp was seriously injured.

It did not have as strong a Will as Garen, and fainted before it even hit the ground. It could not even reduce its speed, and so it crashed hard into a rock-solid wall of ice nearby, leaving cracks all over the surface. Many of its bones broke, and it seemed that this Dragon Whelp would not survive.

If it had reduced its momentum in mid-air, it might have been able to reduce the damage from the crash. But it had immediately fallen unconscious, so not only could it not mitigate the damage, it could not even tense up its muscles to resist the impact. Hence, the damage it received was much worse than it would have been usually.

“Don’t go up to it! Use Spellcraft!” Having witnessed that, Boris knew that a head-on attack would not work, so they could only use Enchantments.

If they attacked from the front, they would be killed instantly. The other Dragon Whelps knew that without him having to say it.

Chapter 1268: Suffering Knight 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen tiptoed back to the place where Leona and the others were, but realized that all the Dragon Whelps had gone out to grab a share of the spoils.

He was in no hurry, either. It would be even better if he could just pick up his share after they had finished fighting.

He hid alone in the corner and listened to the endless barrage of loud wails and explosions inside, knowing that this was the Spellcraft explosions from the Enchanted Equipment.

Time ticked by, and soon enough, more than ten minutes had passed.

The sounds from up ahead were much softer now.

Only then did he get up. Having sufficiently rested, he walked slowly toward the battlefield up ahead.

As he moved forward, he saw red and white blood all over the snowy ground, and he accidentally stepped on something. It was the front limb of a Dragon Whelp that had already frozen into ice.

“How terrible…” Garen shook his head.

He continued to walk forward, and everything he saw was a chaotic mess. After he entered the large circular area, there were countless dents, holes, and scratches on the icy floor and walls.

Next to the giant Ice Stalagmite in the center, all four Level Four Giant Iguanas had been killed. There were charred marks and pale green acid trails on the ground, clearly the result of Enchantments.

Lastly, there were a few remaining unharmed Dragon Whelps surrounding the last Level Five Giant Iguana.

The Level Five Giant Iguana was now blind in both eyes, and its body was covered in black and green burn marks. It stood on the spot without moving, whereas the three Dragon Whelps around it had clearly finished up their Enchantments. They could only fly around it, occasionally smacking it, but evidently, their claws barely had any effect on the Level Five Giant Iguana. They could not even break its hide.

Looking at the injuries of the seriously wounded Dragon Whelps that littered the floor, they all seemed to have been hurt by the swiping of the Giant Iguana’s tail.

Garen himself knew just how powerful the Level Five Giant Iguana’s Tail Swipe was. It was not very strong, but it was far too fast. It did not have much of an effect on the muscly, thick-skinned Level Four Giant Iguanas, but it was just enough for Dragon Whelps, with their weaker bodies and lower strength.

The remaining few Dragon Whelps clearly had no other plans. Their claws could not break past the Giant Iguana’s defense, so they decided to wore it out, until they wore this Level Five Giant Iguana to death.

Garen walked over to them as stealthily as he could, but he was still immediately noticed by the Dragon Whelps lying on the ground.

“Garen!” It was Boris, lying down in a small crater and being treated by Leona.

“You’re just in time, go grab the thing!”

The three Dragon Whelps surrounding the Giant Iguana happened to be Toni, Deth, and another stocky Dragon Whelp whose name Garen did not know. When they heard Boris’ voice, all three turned around to look at Garen.

That unnamed Dragon Whelp’s eyes shone fiercely, and he actually ignored the Giant Iguana, lunging straight for the Ice Stalagmite in the center.

“Reyman, you!!” Toni instantly panicked.

That Dragon Whelp ignored her completely, dashing straight at the Ice Stalagmite.

He was very confident in his speed. Even if he was injured, he would still be the champion who obtained the Ice Stalagmite first.

The other Dragon Whelps also gave up on the attack and gave chase.

Garen smiled and chased after them as well. At the same time, he picked up a few pieces of ice from the ground.

The Ice Stalagmite in the center of these circle-shaped grounds was more than twice as tall as a Dragon Whelp, and looked like a pale blue, crystal-clear pillar of ice. Its tip was rather sharp, and the top half had already been knocked off, while the bottom half was still embedded into the ice layer.

The Dragon Whelps were chasing after the top half that had been knocked away. That was the true essence of the Ice Stalagmite.

Reyman quickly flew until he was above the Ice Stalagmite, and then he pounced down. A ball of purple light instantly appeared in his claws, and he tossed it backward.

Bam!

The ball of light exploded, turning into a fog of purple smoke that enveloped the two Dragon Whelps, Toni and Deth, behind him.

Only then did Reyman stand on the Ice Stalagmite, turning around to stare at Garen, who was walking up to him slowly. The last Dragon Whelp that had just shown up did not chase behind him stupidly, which was how he had managed to avoid the purple smoke.

“You sure are a vigilant one.” There was a black scar above Reyman’s left eye, the injury had nearly blinded that eye. As a result, the scar made him look slightly more brutal.

As a Dragon Whelp, he clearly already possessed the despicable and selfish ways of his elders.

“I bet you don’t have any more Enchantments now, do you.” Although it was phrased as a question, Garen’s tone was certain. “In that case, the Ice Stalagmite belongs to me. Hand over the Crystal Cores too, the four Level Four ones and the one Level Five from before.”

“What an appetite you have there…” Violence twinkled in Reyman’s eyes, and he tensed up all his muscles. His small body was only as tall as half a man, but it gave off a strange sense of power and muscle.

Whoosh…

A faint Draconic Aura spread from his body.

This Draconic Aura was clearly far beyond what Dragon Whelps like Garen who had just experienced it could do.

Garen felt a strong wind blow into his face, and his body actually began to turn heavy, as though he was suddenly carrying an immense burden.

Was this the Draconic Aura’s effect?

His heart jolted in surprise. This was his first time encountering the usage of Draconic Aura in actual battle. This Reyman was definitely no ordinary Dragon Whelp, for him to have such capabilities at this age, he must clearly be a high-level descendant from his clan.

“Interesting…” Garen only knew that Draconic Aura could strengthen a fighter’s physical fitness. However, he had not known that this thing could actually be used to oppress an enemy in battle.

His muscles tensed and relaxed, and he instantly eased up a part of the pressure from the Draconic Aura. A little bit of oppression pressure was nothing to Garen with his 21 Strength points.

He glanced at his status.

‘Safive — Strength 21-1, Agility 15(14)-1, Vitality 12-1, Intelligence 17-1, Potential 19%. Soul Limit 170.

Level 1 Draconic Aura, Level 1 Arcane Art Basics.’

All of his attributes had actually been reduced by an average of one point.

But even if he was being oppressed, he could still 20 Strength points. That made him stronger than regular Dragon Whelps.

Still, the reason he had not leaped into battle at the first chance was that he was slightly worried that the opponent might have saved up some Enchantments. If he got too close and was locked on by the enemy’s spirit power, he would not be able to dodge any Enchantments that easily. Instead, he would be forced to take it head-on, and that would really get dangerous.

Reyman looked at Garen, who remained calm, and had an ominous feeling.

He did not know where this little punk popped out from, but he somehow seemed to be unfazed by the Draconic Aura.

Whoosh!

All of a sudden, a white light crashed toward Reyman, aimed straight for his nose.

Reyman was caught by surprise and lowered his head hurriedly. Thankfully, he had trained his combat skills sufficiently and so he could react extremely quickly, just in time to dodge this attack. As soon as he bent over, though, he saw something white come flying at him.

Pff!

Reyman roared in pain and ran straight at Garen. His frustration and embarrassment had turned to fury.

Meanwhile, Garen was now certain that he had no Enchantments left. Putting aside his fear, he went straight at Reyman.

Lowering his head to avoid Reyman’s claws, aimed at his neck, Garen lashed out with his elbow, his tail slicing through the wind as he whipped it out. It swiped Reyman’s neck with a bang.

Bam!

He pounced forward immediately as well, stomping down on Reyman’s stomach. His claws carved out several long and deep wounds on Reyman’s stomach. He could almost see the bones in the abdomen.

With merely this little greeting, Reyman — an expert in close combat wrestling among the Dragon Whelps — was instantly defeated. He could not put up a fight at all.

Reyman slid out quite a distance, lying motionlessly in the snow. It was as though an electric current had passed through his entire body, and everything was trembling slightly. This shaking dispersed all of his power, until he could not even get back up.

He looked at Garen in the distance, and saw that Garen had no intention of giving chase. Instead, he landed on an Ice Stalagmite.

Garen flapped his wings, standing lightly on the edge of the Ice Stalagmite. Defeating Reyman was as easy as breathing to Garen. As long as the opponent was not in the same Realm as him, all close-combat battles would only result in instant annihilation, as seen in his eyes. The only reason Reyman could survive was because Garen had been merciful.

“The Ice Stalagmite… is mine now…” He crouched down with a smile, his claws pressing onto the half-pale-blue, semi-transparent Ice Stalagmite. Instantly, a tidal wave of potential aura surged into his claws.

Hiss… Garen could not help but exhale, feeling good. Within such a short time, he had already absorbed 10% of the potential aura.

“Good stuff!”

*********************

Ka-chak.

The black metallic boots stepped down hard on the snow and sank deep.

A suit of black knight’s armor, green flames burning in its eyes, slowly landed at the entrance of the tunnel outside the Ice Stalagmite.

“Is this where you ran to…” Its deep voice came from underneath the facial armor, and it strode into the tunnel, taking large steps.

********************

Garen felt slightly bothered.

He did not know why. Looking around him, he did not find any Dragon Whelps that might pose a threat.

The Ice Stalagmite was just by his feet, so he thought about for a while, and then lifted the entire Ice Stalagmite in his arms. But that shudder in his heart made him impatient and uneasy.

His Soul Ring kept vibrating, as though it could fall apart at any time.

“Danger!”

Garen had come across this kind of situation many times now. The Ancient Endor Demon Lords all had overwhelmingly powerful souls, and their bodies fit the laws perfectly as well, so they were extremely sensitive about predicting danger.

A situation like this was surely no coincidence.

Although he did not know why he felt a sense of danger, Garen rapidly calmed himself down and quickly made some decisions. Carrying the Ice Stalagmite in his arms, he decided to just abandon the Level Five crystal cores, flying straight into the distant sky.

He had tremendous strength, and he flapped his wings, diving quickly into the snowstorm.

“Garen!!” Boris yelled from below. But all he saw was Garen vanishing into the sky, without once looking back.

His heart fell. Together with Leona, the one with the lightest injuries, the two of them helped Saszt up.

“Why did he run?” Leona was heartbroken. “Does he plan to keep the Ice Stalagmite all to himself?”

“Forget it, he obtained it by himself, after all. We didn’t do much either.” On the other hand, Boris recovered quickly.

Just then, he vaguely felt a black light flash before his eyes, as though something had flitted past quickly.

“Did something just fly past just now?” he asked, shocked.

“No…” Leona shook her head. “You must be seeing things.”

For some reason, Boris frowned.

“I keep getting the feeling that Garen isn’t that kind of a dragon…”

Not far away, Reyman was still lying on the ground, and his eyes showed just how deeply lost he felt.

He was the one destined to become Dragon King. Ever since he was born, he had had immense expectations piled on him. They poured all sorts of training regimes and resources into him, because he had unbelievable natural talent that allowed him to raise his Draconic Aura to Level Three even when he was only two years old. His average physical fitness could defeat even a Three-Headed Dragon Whelp as long as they fought alone.

But in front of that Dragon Whelp just now, he felt as weak as a baby.

“Am I too weak… or is he too strong?” Reyman sank into the depths of confusion.

Chapter 1269: Pursuit 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen flew at lightning speeds. The snowstorm ahead of and around him grew denser and thicker, but he felt as though there was an immense danger that he could not shake off approaching him.

“The Soul Rings don’t lie, looks like serious trouble is brewing!” Garen had long since expected that the disharmony between his soul and his body would invite trouble, but he never thought that it would come so soon.

Panic began to rise in his heart.

But since he was carrying the Ice Stalagmite, he just could not increase his speed to its maximum limit. The only comfort he had was the massive amount of potential aura surging endlessly into his body from the Ice Stalagmite.

It had only been a short while, but he had another Attribute Point now.

Garen quickly added it to his Speed, and he instantly felt himself speed up. The anxiety in his heart eased up slightly.

Everything before him was a flurry of white snow, and he could not see anything at all, so he did not even know where he was flying toward. What he did know, however, was that if he did not fly and the danger behind him caught up, the results would not be as pleasant as he imagined.

The power level of this world was too high, and their research into the workings of the soul was too advanced. He could not hide himself well at all.

Whoosh…

Suddenly, Garen seemed to hear something ring out behind him.

He concentrated and listened carefully. Suddenly, his expression changed, and he sank downward fiercely, leaving his original position.

Psst!

Just as he sank down, a black light shot past the place in the sky where he had been just a moment ago, leaving a long trail of afterimages in its wake. After it broke past the snowstorm ahead, it vanished without a trace.

Garen’s forehead began to sweat. He lifted his left claw and saw that the back of the claw — the hardest part — had a deep gash carved out of it. It had been sliced open by the snow scattered as a result of the black light bullet that he had just avoided.

“Well… This really is serious trouble…” He flapped his wings even faster.

Soon, he floated upward again, avoiding the bolt of black light as it came back.

Hugging the Ice Stalagmite carefully, Garen used all of his power to fly forward madly as fast as he could, unwilling to linger for even a moment. If he still had some doubts earlier, they had all been put to rest by now. That guy behind him was terrifyingly strong, and completely beyond his current capabilities to resist.

Thankfully, Garen’s combat realm was too high, giving him a complete understanding and comprehension of the environment around him within a certain range. Otherwise, he never would have avoided that bolt of black light in time.

The unknown enemy behind him also seemed to have noticed that this attack was ineffective, so they stopped using it. Instead, they fell quiet.

However, Garen was not naive enough to think that they had given up.

Soon enough, the Ice Stalagmite gave him yet another Attribute Point. He quickly added it to his Speed as well. His speed was bumped up another notch.

The enemy behind him seemed to be slightly surprised and confused about how he kept increasing his speed.

***************

In the middle of the snowstorm, the pitch-black Suffering Knight shone with black light as it flew, weaving through the storm. It had vaguely locked onto a small thing flying in front of him. The snowstorm was too heavy, though, and it was quite far away. The first time the Suffering Knight attacked, he had missed, and as a result, the little thing was wary now. It had gotten even faster.

“This is no longer the speed of a regular Dragon Whelp…” The Suffering Knight was slightly surprised.

But since its master had ordered it, it gave chase determinedly, even though it could not match up to the target’s speed.

Any living creature would eventually grow tired, but it was different…

It looked down at the red symbols on the Greatsword, hesitated for a moment, and still chose not to activate it yet.

That was an Undead Imprint. When it had hit the little Dragon Whelp’s claw just now, it had already placed the imprint on the Dragon Whelp. Once it was activated, the Dragon Whelp would be instantly dragged into the Blinding Hell, forcing the Dragon Whelp into a one-on-one fight to the death with the Suffering Knight.

But this was the Suffering Knight’s strongest ability. If it activated that now, it would take at least two or three hundred years to recover. The target was a mutated soul, so it would not activate that ability unless it had no other choice.

****************

The time ticked by slowly, and soon enough, a day had passed.

Garen had already absorbed all of the potential in the Ice Stalagmite and gained thirteen whole Attribute Points, but he did not add them all to his Speed. He was already fast enough to leave the enemy behind him in the dust, and Attribute Points were precious, so he could not use them up so carelessly. Besides, he had a feeling that even if he added them to his Speed, he might still be unable to shake off that enemy behind him.

There was no reasoning behind this feeling, but Garen subconsciously trusted this sort of premonition.

He had flown at high speeds for a full day, so Garen was already completely worn out. He desperately needed to rest.

Even though he was being nurtured by the Soul Energy, his body was still that of a normal Dragon Whelp. It was already quite impressive that he could stay on the run for so long.

The enemy behind him would occasionally take advantage of his weariness. When his speed decreased, the enemy would close the distance again, scaring Garen into picking up his speed again.

But as a result, he had also glimpsed the enemy pursuing him.

It was a suit of empty knight’s armor, with a pair of green flames burning where its eyes should be. It was very similar to the Undead Knight in his Inherited Memories.

“I knew it! Dammit!” Garen had guessed that his soul’s uniqueness would be discovered by a master researching the soul, but he did not predict that they would come for him so quickly.

It was just a simple trip out, and he was already being chased down by an Undead Creature.

He just could not shake off the thing behind him, and for a moment there, Garen was stumped as well. He had completely lost his way around here, flying around everywhere in this snowstorm meant that he could not find any location markers whatsoever. Luckily, he had not encountered any high-level Elder Giant Iguanas even after flying around for so long, otherwise he would be just as dead.

Rawrr…!

Suddenly, there was a violent woman’s scream from behind him.

A green wave instantly scattered the snowstorm all around him, completely revealing the distance between the Knight and Garen.

The wave hit Garen’s body directly without any obstruction whatsoever.

Garen’s whole body stiffened, and he paused in mid-air for just an instant.

Pff!

Tiny wounds opened up all over his body, and white blood sprayed out of the gashes.

A pain that came from the depths of his soul jolted through Garen, rendering him so dizzy he nearly fell directly down.

His chest tightened abruptly. At first, he had thought that he could just keep running like this, but he had not expected the guy behind him to suddenly use such a terrifying attack.

He knew this Spell.

Inferno Horn… a Level Seven Spell that was created as a failed attempt to mimic a Level Nine Banshee’s Wail. Even so, it also had a terrifying destructive effect on the soul.

This was a special technique that only the strongest Undead Creature, the Suffering Knight, possessed!

“A Suffering Knight… This is bad!” Garen felt as though he was experiencing enough bad luck to last eight lifetimes. He bumped into a Level Seven Creature so soon after coming out, and he was just a regular Level Four Creature. Even so, he was already being hunted down by a Level Seven Creature.

Withstanding the pain out of habit, Garen glanced at his status pane.

That glance and the condition of his status pane made his heart thump heavily.

‘Safive — Strength 21 (19), Agility 17 (15), Vitality 12 (10), Intelligence 17 (15), Potential 89%. Soul Limit 170.

Level 1 Draconic Aura. Level 1 Arcane Art Basics.

Currently under influence of Inferno Curse: All attributes reduced by two points every hour, requires positive energy to dispel, or else it will only automatically wear off after three days of rest and waiting. If not dispelled with positive energy, the target will permanently lose an average of five points. Warning, this curse is stackable.’

It actually reduced all of his attributes by two points!

And that was not all. An unprecedented sense of weakness permeated through Garen’s body ceaselessly. He felt as though his body was a bucket that kept leaking water, his power was constantly dripping out of it.

He noticed the Inferno Curse icon at the very bottom, and swore inwardly.

An average reduction of two points every hour, and if he did not use positive energy to dispel it, he would actually lose five Attribute Points per attribute forever!

That was ridiculous!

If he could not manage to dispel it and it was disabled automatically in the end.

Four Attributes would result in a total loss of twenty points! That would take up all of the Attribute Points he just earned on this trip out, wouldn’t it?

Garen also noticed that his four Soul Rings, stacked on top of each other, were starting to crack slightly after that roar just now.

Evidently, this type of attack from the enemy was too powerful, and it was aimed straight at the soul. It was extremely strong.

No wonder the powerhouses of this world could even casually catch a creature from another dimension for their experiments.

“What now?” He was starting to grow anxious. If at first he had tried to wear out the enemy behind him, he had now completely given up on the plan after finding out that the enemy was a member of the Undead. Undead Creatures did not tire.

And he also noticed the last bit of information about the curse– the Inferno Curse was stackable.

“Dammit! This damned thing stacks!?” For the first time, he had the urge to insult someone’s mother.

Once was enough to crack his Soul Rings and potentially cause him to lose twenty potential points forever. How could he take one more hit!

He guessed that this might be because his level was too low and his Vitality was not enough, so he just was not strong enough. After all, that was a Level Seven Spell, and he had managed to endure it without dying despite being only Level Four. This was already extremely remarkable, in any other situation, it would practically be a miracle. Even if the Inferno Curse’s main effect was to weaken, and not to kill off the enemy, it was still very impressive for a Dragon Whelp.

There was a three-level difference right there.

Although he was panicked inside, Garen’s many years of experience allowed him to instantly calm down, suppressing any unnecessary emotions.

Under these circumstances, where he did not know how the enemy locked onto his tracks, the chances of hiding being ineffective were too high, so all he could do was run.

But if he just kept running like this, he would still end up dying eventually.

The Soul Energy in Garen’s heart slowly began to tremble. He started to carefully sense the presences of all the creatures around him. Although he could not let his Soul Energy leave his body to explore, he still had the Demon Lords’ Natural Ability, Dream Control.

As one of Ancient Endor’s Demon Lords, the most troublesome thing he could encounter was an enemy discovering his uniqueness when he was in his smallest and weakest state. Before Demon Lords came of age, it was also catastrophic for them to be discovered.

Even though they matured extremely quickly, if they were discovered at such a time, they would still only be one or two levels higher in terms of survival power compared to other creatures at the same level.

It was already very remarkable for Garen to withstand a Spell three levels higher than himself.

Put into perspective, it was like fighting a steel knife with a balloon, and the balloon actually managed to take a hit without exploding. It was practically a miracle!

His Soul Rings trembled slowly. Under these dangerous circumstances, he pinpointed the locations of all the creatures around him, and they all appeared in Garen’s mind, rapidly using up a large amount of his Soul Energy. He could not care less, however. If he was going to be stingy about little things like that at a time like this, he would truly be done for.

“Bottom left!”

He rapidly decided on a direction. The Soul Rings had given him the safest guide in this difficult situation, and although this direction seemed to be extremely perilous as well, it was already much better than the other few directions.

Garen never thought for a moment that he would die in this snowstorm without knowing anything. Since the enemy did not kill him off at the first opportunity, this clearly meant that it had other considerations. As long as Garen still had space to maneuver, he would surely have a chance to turn things around.

Garen also firmly believed in that.

“It seems that after living peacefully for so long, I’ve also started to let myself go…” Garen began to reprimand himself. Perhaps it was because his days so far had been too easy and carefree, maybe that was why he had ended up in such a dangerous state without even knowing it.

The snowstorm was growing stronger.

He flapped his wings and sped up, diving toward the bottom left.

*****************

“Sure is running fast… Is that its final struggle?” The Suffering Knight sensed the Dragon Whelp ahead of it from far away, and had already noticed that the target’s speed was dropping. The second Inferno Curse that it was about to unleash faded slowly.

“Looks like it’s just a matter of time before I catch it. There’s no need to use up too much energy…”

It glanced at the glyphs on its Greatsword and decided not to activate it, after all.

Speeding up, it rapidly gave chase.

A vacuum layer separated the all-encompassing snowstorm around, and not even one snowflake actually touched his armor.

Chapter 1270: Pursuit 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In an unknown snowy mountain range, the sharp and straight peaks of the mountains were reflected in the lake water.

The surface of the lake was as clear as a mirror, free of even the slightest ripple. It was just a sea of deep blue. Other than the reflection of the snowy mountains, all that remained was the blue sky.

The lake was oval in shape and not very large, bordered completely by the broken edges of the white ice. The water was so clear that it was almost transparent.

On one side of the lake, there was a large and quiet white snowy mountain, grey-brown in the parts that were not covered in snow.

On the other side, there was a layer of snowstorm clouds.

Looking at it from afar, the cloud layer was forced into the distance, enveloping the ground there completely within a flurry of snow. It looked like a completely different world from the quiet cleanliness over here.

The sunlight faintly fell onto the surface of the lake and the left side of the snowy mountain. It projected a faint golden light, but also some miniscule dark shadows on the other side of the mountain.

Boom…!

Just then, two figures abruptly shot out from the white snowstorm cloud layer.

The one in front was a smaller white Dragon Whelp that looked to be in bad shape, and seemed to pretty badly injured.

The one chasing behind it, on the other hand, was a pitch-black humanoid in black knight armor.

On after the other, the two of them shot out toward the snowy mountain like bullets, leaving a long white trail in the sky.

“Here?” Garen vaguely sensed that something was amiss with this place, but he did not have the luxury to dwell on it.

He felt weak all over. His attributes had been reduced twice consecutively, and his Agility had already dropped by four points. The Knight behind him was faster than him now, and the distance between them had been reduced from more than a thousand meters before to just several dozen meters now. Thank goodness he had added four points to his Agility in time, and he still had eleven points to be used, but he still managed to put a distance between them in time.

This was the place his Soul Rings predicted would be able to help him.

He had no other choice now.

The quiet snowy mountains, the mirror-like lake. This was a place nearing perfection, but there was no sign of life whatsoever. Even an idiot would have noticed that something was wrong with this place.

But this something wrong was precisely what Garen wanted right now!

He dashed straight for the snowy mountain fearlessly.

That place was the center of everything without a doubt. If there was something unnatural here, it would surely be concentrated there.

***************

“This place!?”

Soon after the Suffering Knight entered this area, it sensed that its connection to its master had been instantly severed.

Shocked, it slowed down slightly and began to observe the snowy mountain ahead of it hesitantly.

Its surroundings were completely clean, without even a single living creature. The atmosphere here was heavy and dead, completely devoid of life.

A feeling that sent shivers down its spine rose from this place faintly.

“Should I continue to give chase?” The idea had barely occurred to it before it was immediately squashed down.

“The master’s orders are absolute, no degree of danger should stand in the way of my mission.”

It instantly tossed everything to the winds and quickly gave chase, showing no intention of leaving whatsoever.

“But I have to finish off that guy ahead as soon as possible… I can’t drag it on any longer.”

He looked down at the red glyphs on the sharp Greatsword as they lit up slowly. They glowed with a blood-like red light.

****************

Garen could feel the strength draining out of his body and hurriedly added another point to his Vitality. He only had ten attribute points left, so if he could not dispel the curse this time, he would incur heavy losses even if he used up all of the attribute points.

His body felt slightly better now, and he flew toward a crevice in the snowy mountain, swaying as he went.

It was ice-cold in the crevice. Even though he was a White Dragon, he could still that piercing cold permeate through his entire body.

Resisting the discomfort, Garen sped up and flew into the crevice. The crevice had many twists and turns, curving around and around as it stretched on downward.

He could not see the bottom of the crevice below him. All he could see was a sea of pitch-black darkness, as though it was a bottomless abyss.

Psst!

Suddenly, he felt as though something brushed past his face.

Garen was stunned. That thing was extraordinarily fast. On the other hand, he was completely exhausted right now, his spirit stretched to its tolerance limit. Two days of non-stop flying without daring to take even a moment’s rest had pushed him, a mere Dragon Whelp, to his limit. That was why he had no idea what the thing that flew past him was.

“It does not have the aura of a living creature… Whatever! No matter what, it beats falling into the hands of a Soul Master!” He continued to dive head-first into the crevice.

The crevice grew wider and wider as he went, becoming larger and also colder, bone-chillingly cold.

Garen felt as though he was flying toward the center of the world. It was a very eerie feeling.

Ahead of him, there was only darkness without the slightest hint of light. Even if he had a natural talent for night vision as a White Dragon, he still could not find even a fleck of light. He had to rely on the flow of the current to sense the area around him.

The Suffering Knight behind him was growing closer and closer, as though it had gotten somewhat hurried.

Psst!

Psst-psst-psst!

All of a sudden, several black things shot past Garen abruptly.

His body stiffened abruptly, his body had somehow become completely frozen. He could barely even move his wings. His body began to fell straight down, toward the bottom of the crevice.

This time, they were too close together, so Garen could finally clearly see what the thing beside him was.

They were basically wisps of black smoke with human faces.

The black smoke swam quickly through the crevice like fish in water. It was thick and concentrated, and more currents of black smoke kept whooshing past Garen’s body.

One hundred, two hundred? One thousand, ten thousand, a hundred thousand? A million?” Garen counted these wisps of black smoke until he lost count, and only then did he see that there was light here now!

His whole body stiffened, and he allowed gravity to drag him toward, into the depth of the crevice abyss.

In his night-vision dragon eyes, he could vaguely see a ball of transparent light, lighting up slowly at the bottom of the abyss. It looked like white light, but its source was that foggy transparent sphere.

That light source was still at least several kilometers away, and from a distance, he could see that there were countless black smoke faces surrounding that light source.

This all-encompassing black smoke seemed to have a life of its own, and it flew around the light source, staring with distorted hatred in its eyes.

The countless black smoke surrounded the light source, forming a giant tidal-like whirlpool. That colorless light source sat at the bottom of the whirlpool.

And Garen felt as though he was falling toward the bottom of the whirlpool. He was completely helpless, and it was like he was falling into hell.

“This place… what is it!!?” He heard the roar of a Suffering Knight behind him.

“Dosima, angelier… Silent flames of hell, eye of suffering, open up your arms, face the solidification of eternity…” He heard a deep voice singing a chant behind him.

Garen instantly felt a spine-chilling sense of threat surge forth from behind him.

His Soul Rings began to shake uncontrollably, as though it was encountering an unprecedented danger of the highest level. Many cracks appeared, one after the other, on the Soul Rings.

That illogical chant that also seemed to contain an unnatural magic power transcended the long distance and went straight into Garen’s ears.

“…Final Battle to the Death!” When the last note ended, Garen saw light.

It was not the faint white light from beneath him. Instead, it was a blinding red light that blossomed from behind him, blood-like viscous red light!

That blood-like red color washed over him like countless waves, faster than he could imagine. Garen just felt as though the red light had appeared behind him in an instant, and was just about to touch his skin. A sense of weakness and helplessness, accompanied by suffering and despair, spread throughout his entire body.

“No!!”

He roared madly! The danger had come so quickly, and even if he had already mentally prepared himself a long time ago, when he felt that weakness all over his body, a deep-set terror still surged up from the bottom of his heart.

All his Soul Rings were trembling madly, many countless and tiny cracks appearing all over them. Even if he had to detonate all of his Soul Rings, he still refused to allow himself to fail without putting up a fight!

Garen’s eyes began to shine with terrifying Soul Energy. If he lost his Soul Rings, he could still condense them again, but if he lost his soul, it was all over!

His eyes revealed an unprecedented brutal determination.

Ka-chak!

One of his Soul Rings exploded abruptly, turning into an immense wave of powerful Soul Energy that rushed about madly in his brain.

Each Demon-Lord-Level existence had, without exception, experienced countless challenges and growth before they reached the level they were at. Garen was no different.

In the history of Ancient Endor, there had never been an instance where a Demon Lord was abducted! Never!!

The first Soul Ring exploded, and Garen’s strength, as well as his physical fitness, was forcefully doubled.

The second and third Soul Rings also abruptly exploded at the same time!

Countless soul shards scattered everywhere, and Garen’s body expanded rapidly like a balloon being inflated. And he was still growing larger and vaster! He had grown into a mature White Dragon’s body in almost an instant.

Finally, a small wound underneath his scales split apart.

Barroom!!!

At the bottom of the abyss, an unimaginable wave of heat sprayed out suddenly.

It was as though heaven and earth had frozen in an instant. Everything, all of it, seemed to freeze in time, held in place by the faint white light from the abyss below.

Inside the light source, a huge and terrifying golden eye opened slowly. A woman dressed in a black dress that was tight around her waist stood in the middle of the eye.

The woman opened her eyes slowly. Her skin was whiter than snow, her hair darker than the night, and her figure seemed to have been forged according to the most perfect golden proportions. She was completely flawless.

Although she had opened her eyes, there was no light or consciousness in them at all. As though she was still deeply asleep, she raised her left hand slowly, like a sleepwalker.

Her palm was aimed directly at Garen and the Suffering Knight.

Barroom!!!

There was another immense tremor.

A giant, unimaginable pressure traveled across several kilometers and instantly landed on Garen and the Suffering Knight.

Garen felt as though an entire giant mountain had fallen on top of him in an instant. That feeling was just like how he had felt when he flew toward the sun of the Mother Planet for the first time in the Mech World.

Heavy, immense, irresistible.

“…Draconic Aura!!” An agonized voice came from behind him. It was the Suffering Knight’s voice.

That was the last thing Garen heard.

Time seemed to be flowing backward… His body shrunk rapidly, and he soon returned to his original Dragon Whelp body. The Soul Rings inside his body had also somehow naturally returned to their original Soul Ring state, even though they had already been blown to pieces. They looked almost completely undamaged.

Chapter 1271: Existence 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was as though everything returned to the state when he first entered here.

Garen completely lost consciousness.

As for the Suffering Knight behind him, his entire body armor exploded like an expensive crystal glass shattering into millions of pieces. Countless black characters and symbols attempted to escape like tadpoles but were frozen by a vast Draconic Aura. Bam!

All the characters once again exploded into finer pieces. This time, they disappeared into the most basic negative energy flow into the air.

“Lord…!” The Suffering Knight’s last voice echoed into the abyss before nothing could be heard again.

Everything returned to peace. The Draconic Aura subsided and as just it was in the beginning, as though it never appeared.

A school of black smoke with human faces encircled Garen. They attempted to creep into Garen’s skin and ears. Every one of them wanted to occupy Garen, this young dragon’s body.

However, there was a thin layer of light over Garen’s body that prevented him from any harm.

As time slowly passed, it was a permanent darkness into the abyss without being able to tell between the night and day.

An unknown time had passed until Garen slowly regained consciousness.

His compact surroundings of black smoke with human faces dispersed like scared little fishes. At the time same, Garen, who was levitating as a result of being cupped by them, took a sharp fall.

He immediately fluttered his wings, struggling to stay afloat.

Seeing the darkness everywhere, Garen recalled the earlier situation.

“What just happened?” He felt a splitting headache.

The Suffering Knight who pursued after him was gone. He suddenly remembered.

“Could he be killed by the earlier Draconic Aura?”

He was most pleasantly surprised by the Soul Rings that he detonated remaining intact. It was a miracle.

He clearly remembered that at the final crucial moment, he blew up all his Soul Ring to obtain the upper limit of the strength. Who would have thought that all his Soul Rings remained in one piece?

“How funny!” Garen muttered in his heart. Although he didn’t understand what happened, it was obvious someone had saved him.

He drifted in the darkness and stared beneath him. He saw a colorless light source not near away from him.

He flew downwards. It seemed that this unknown existence saved him. As he has been rescued, he should head down to thank it face to face.

As he flew down and closed in, Garen landed at the edge of this huge light source.

The light source was small, only at a diameter of over ten meters. It was pale white within that light source; the insides could be seen indistinctly.

He circled around this light. The bottom of the abyss was flat, as though someone had polished a smooth surface as there was no staggering when on foot.

This wasn’t a small palace.

Garen went around the place and sensed indistinctly.

He found a stone tablet in the surrounding.

The pitch black stone tablet was half-rooted on the ground with the other half on the surface. There were words engraved on the side. It was the Draconic language with which he was familiar, yet the semantics were somewhat ancient.

Garen carefully read the words with the little light.

“Guilty of heinous crime… All-Devouring Dragon… Earth’s Core Capital…”

The content after that was muffled, as though it had been scratched all over.

Garen couldn’t restore it despite carefully studying it long. He tried to claw at the stone tablet.

Shhh.

His claws instead were ground into a layer of powder.

The durability of the stone tablet was so hard that even his sharp dragon claw left no mark. This left Garen in surprise.

He spun around the light source again in the darkness and found the same stone tablet at another two areas. There were similar handwritings engraved on them respectively.

One of the stone tablets read “Forbidden Zone.”

While the other stone tablet was “Slumber, Do Not Disturb, Disaster.”

The remaining writings were too blurred. Many of the sentences in the middle could not be made out.

Garen looked through the stone tablets and investigated around once more.

The odd thing was that this was the center of the abyss, yet none of these black smoke with human faces dared approach it. They seemed to be afraid of something.

Garen gave it a thought before walking to the outer area.

Walking along the surface of the abyss, he went about and around.

He finally got a hold of the structure here.

The entire abyss was the size of several soccer fields. It was circular in shape. The light source protecting the stone tablets was just located just right in the middle.

It was soon when Garen found a sticky black thing in an empty area. He felt the presence of this thing to be similar to the Suffering Knight who had gone after him. So he captured it.

This thing was soft like a sticky rubber ball. There was a large symbol beaming in dark red. It looked like the letter Y, but with a twist.

The moment he held it in his hands, he felt a breeze of Soul Power aura leaking from within the rubber ball.

“Soul Power!” Garen was delighted and swiftly retrieved the ball and held within his claws.

Strangely, looking at the light source from afar, Garen could clearly see what was within it.

It was a golden round object of a dragon’s eye. In a dim light glow, it wasn’t clear. However, it could be distinguished that it was a dragon’s eye with a golden vertical iris.

Garen was shocked.

If this was in some other world of the large beasts, it would be understandable. However, for this world of dragons to have birthed such a large eyeball, its body must have been quite the size.

In this world, such a large dragon definitely wouldn’t be a nobody.

Staring from afar, he could somewhat make out a woman in a black dress standing afloat within the dragon’s eye.

“If this was a seal that could seal the person inside, that must be one hell of a power.” He was struck by this idea.

Looking at the dragon’s eye, he thought about it before shouting out loud.

“Thank you, Lord, for rescuing me. I am Garen, a warming of White Dragon Clan.”

His voice echoed in the darkness, but it received no response.

It was silent. The woman inside the round light source remained still as though she didn’t hear his screams.

“Thank you, Lord, for saving me!” Garen shouted out once more. This time, even louder.

Yet, there was still no response. It was still silent at the bottom of the abyss.

Garen was hesitant but remembered the content on the stone tablets. Could the woman within be in deep slumber? Could it be that she rescued him unconsciously? Impossible!

Even with an unconscious defense, he himself wouldn’t be about to leave unscathed at this rate unless the other party specifically protected him.

“This is not a place that you should come to. You should leave.” Suddenly, a cold male voice was heard from the light source.

The moment Garen heard this voice, he felt the Soul Power quaver and resonate. It was as though the other person’s faint noise was enough to break his Soul Rings.

His blood rushed as his heartbeat raced. He only calmed down moments later and that was when he realized that the curse on him was lifted.

Taking a few deep breaths, he gave one last stare at the woman in the center of the light source.

Garen fluttered his wings and flew upward, exiting the abyss.

It was as though he had the will of the woman in the light source this time, as the black clouds with human faces gathered beneath him in tides, swiftly holding him up and tossing him out to the outer world.

Garen took one last look below as the light source reached further and further out of sight, dimmer and dimmer until it disappeared from plain view.

“Once out, do not mention to anybody about here. Remember!” That clear male voice shot through the distance and snuck into his head.

Garen wasn’t puzzled that although the person was a woman, she carried a male voice. These major existences had various peculiarities, so this was not something out of the norm.

He only felt odd that the person rescued him for no reason at all. A Level Seven Suffering Knight was easily crushed like an ant by her, let alone Garen who was weaker.

With such a doubt hanging over him, Garen was fired by the black smoke out of the rift of the Snow Mountain. It wasn’t long before he was flying back to the blizzard on the other side of a lake of ravaging snowstorm.

Within the abyss.

The woman within the light source made a motion, stretching her arms slightly.

“White Dragons have always been selfish. Their souls are as dirty as black dirt. Who would have thought there’d be an odd one out here. His soul is as clear as crystal…” The male voice echoed within the light source.

“Odd one… Hehe… Striving huh… Such an interesting little white dragon.”

It reminded her of herself in the beginning. An oddball within the dragon race, going against the nature of their race all the same.

A sense of fatigue crept within her as she fell back into slumber, or perhaps delved back into practice.

******

Once Garen was about to find his way back to the clan in a struggle, over a month has passed.

After he returned to the family, all the dragon whelps thought he was dead and didn’t think he would actually return. The dragon whelps of the nurturing center, especially the dragon whelps that lived from snatching ice stalagmites, stared at Garen in a displeased manner. He snatched away the trophy, the largest ice stalagmites after all. It was a good thing there were several Level Five and Level Four Crystal Cores shared by all. Otherwise, their hatred towards Garen would have deepened.

Upon returning, Garen explained what happened to Satwo, Sathree, and Safour, saying he lost his way in the blizzard and lost the ice stalagmite with no hope of bringing it back. He finally made it home with much difficulty.

Originally, the few siblings did not believe it, but seeing the wounds on Garen’s body as well as his lack of strengths, they took his word for it.

Garen had yet to attend any classes during his return when Saszt, Boris and the lot arrived at his residence to ask about the situation.

“What! You lost the ice stalagmite!?” Boris’s mouth was wide open in disbelief.

Saszt, who was beside, was clearly distressed.

“How did you lose it? If I knew you were going to lose it, I would have gone ahead and given a few bites!”

Leona was more concerned about Garen’s body.

“What’s the news on your injury? Why are there this many wounds?”

“Wounded by Giant Iguanas…” Garen helplessly replied, “I lost my way halfway and encountered a few Giant Iguanas of high levels. I could only scatter about but was caught by a Level Five Giant Iguana. After a round of being beaten up, good luck allowed me to find my way home.”

“Blame your greediness!” Leona said with contempt.

“I was prepared to snatch it away and bring it back to share within us secretly. Who would have thought…” Garen made an aggrieved face.

“Really?” Leona was dubious. It was easy to win over little girls.

“Of course it’s true. We are a team!” Garen said out loud. Of course, he wouldn’t dare mention that he planned to pocket it at a time like this.

Chapter 1272: Existence 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I believe in Garen!” Boris exclaimed with a face of sincerity.

“Me too,” Saszt added. However, before speaking he stared at Boris. He had always followed Boris’ lead.

The few dragon whelps started to get active in Garen’s cave as they conversed about recent events.

“Oh, right, Garen.” Boris became serious. “That’s one thing you need to be careful about.”

“What?”

“Reyman, our White Dragon Clan’s most talented dragon whelp, has been coming often to ask about you.

“He seemed to have harbored ill intent after losing to you.” Boris was worried.

“Reyman, huh…?” Garen recalled this dragon whelp which he killed within seconds. He was the only one that left an impression with that nice Draconic Aura.

“You need to be careful.

“The elders are nurturing him as the future White Dragon King.” Leona was concerned.

“Don’t worry, I’ll take care of it.”

Garen nodded in a gesture that implied he understood.

“Don’t lower your guard,” Boris ultimately urged. “And another thing, the completion of your task has most likely fallen through…”

“…”

******

Elder’s Peak of the White Dragon Clan.

Deep into the cold cave, four old White Dragons bearing staffs were quivering as they shook on four large icy pillars. Around the icy pillars stood with many sharp icicles that wrapped their bodies in the middle.

On top of the four staffs, a dull white glow was released, shining over the entire cave.

“The West clan has come in contact with us again.

“How should we respond this time, Great Elder?” One of the old dragons asked in a low voice.

On the highest icy pillar was an old White Dragon with wrinkles all over and a pair of droopy eyes. He didn’t seem focused.

“Our collaboration with the King of the Deladia Empire has just begun, yet they kept announcing a ban on dragons, Do they think that we are still that small clan that split up? Ignore them.”

“Great Elder, can the Deladia Empire really lead us to glory? The expedition this time had caused a loss of ten summoned adult dragons. Not to mention, the Clock of Fate is unhappy with us lifting the ban on the participation in the war of the Deladia Empire. They could send out wizards to join the battlefield,” another Elder whispered, “I am worried that the loss will outweigh the gain.”

“But we are left with no choice,” Great Elder dully replied, “take advantage of Dragon Beasts and Earth Dragons.”

“We suffered much loss on Dragon Beasts and Earth Dragons at more than a hundred of them!” The last elder shrieked with a withered female voice. We have a total of over a hundred twenty adult White Dragons in our clan, and this counts the new members that had sought refuge recently. The next maturity would take at least fifty years. We can’t wait any longer. It hasn’t been a year and we already lost ten clan members…”

“Your Excellency Hurricane Erger has given me his words that the intensity of the war will lessen.

“Unless it was out of absolute necessity, they will not seek our help,” Great Elder cut her off. “So do not worry, Tasha.”

“The nobles of the Snow City should never be trusted,” Tasha rebutted.

“But we found no better snow mountains to inhabit. All the human nations cast us away and only this place… Only this place was willing to take us in and provide us with a level of protection. Shouldn’t we offer them a little return?” Great Elder asked.

For a moment, the few elders were silent.

“The next batch of young dragons will be fifty-two years later. Hopefully, we can make it until then…” Tasha uttered in a low voice and flew away, leaving the ice pillar.

Thus, the meeting of the elders ended.

******

The classroom valley at the Elder’s Peak.

Garen was crouching lazily in a corner, looking at the remaining dragon whelps grapple and wrestle with each other with enthusiasm. After the hunt, the members of dragon whelp lessened by a third. Now that with some new additions to the class, there were about fifteen to sixteen whelps.

Garen swept a glance around in boredom. He realized that no dragon whelps dared look him in the eye. Those he swept a glance at quickly turned away and lowered their heads.

It seemed that his performance when he sped killed Reyman was over the top and these dragon whelps were no idiots. Who would willingly be tortured with such a discrepancy of strength between them?

So basically no one was willing to be in the team as him on this one on one combat. Leona, who originally teamed up with him, immediately sought another to practice with.

In a bored stiff state, Garen started to reflect upon dividing his remaining attribute points.

There were still ten points left that he did not add on account of fleeing, mainly because of the fact that adding or not made no differences. Rather than using them all, it was better to leave it for recovery in order to sustain longer in battle.

Now, he could deliberate on how he could divide them.

The best thing was that he obtained the core of that Suffering Knight. It should be a core as that was what he guessed. This item could endlessly nourish his Soul Power. It was equivalent to a few Soul Rings.

This way, the accumulation of his potential aura could hasten from five points in two months to five points in a month. It was a terrifying speed.

He got to give it to a Core of a Level Five being. Garen knew that if Lady Luck was not on his side, he probably would not have come across such a treasure.

Adding this to the mix, he now had sixteen attribute points to distribute.

After returning, he did not hesitate to distribute them evenly on his strength, agility, and vitality.

He realized that all three of these attributes could not be ignored in this world. The dragon race naturally had stronger physical dispositions. By wielding this nature to its fullest extent and with his safety ensured, he could then focus on spellcrafting.

Strength should be targeted on destroying defenses. If he didn’t have enough power to tear the skin of his enemy, then killing them would pose a problem.

Agility would be useful for fleeing. It could be of great use when snatching resources and treasures.

Vitality was crucial as this attribute could exempt many types of spellcraft. The higher the vitality, the higher the level of the types of spellcraft that could be exempted. Even those that could not be exempted would be weakened to the lowest limit. It would be very useful.

After careful consideration, these three attributes could not be disregarded.

Garen then distributed evenly on the three.

He immediately felt a major change.

“Safive — Strength 26(26), Agility 26(26), Vitality 19(19), Intelligence 17 with potential 19%.

Soul limit 170, Level 1 Draconic Aura, Level 1 Arcane Art Basics.”

“Strength has increased from 21 to 26, the same could be said about Agility, from 21 to 26. Vitality went from 13 to 19.”

He felt his body expanding tougher.

“Let’s start the combat practice assessment!” The White Dragon instructor yelled.

“Scramble over!

“Follow my line up and start to fight one-by-one!

“Stop when I say stop!” The instructor was a new adult dragon. His little eyes reeked of viciousness, as though he had harbored ill intentions.

It was said that he was originally teaching the youths. However, after violently abusing over ten young female dragons and causing a public outrage, he was transferred to the dragon whelp’s combat class.

More than ten dragon whelps obediently stood together. Garen, too, stood up with them.

“The top three of the assessment will obtain one Kavan Gold. You should know the use of Kavan Gold. I do not need to reiterate its importance. So work hard, you little bastards!” The instructor roared.

The dragon whelps numbered one and two flew up onto the ice block ring in the middle of the valley.

It was a dull combat and the winner continued to fight the next one. This competition was weighed on the highest number of wins and the lowest number of losses.

With no exception, it was Garen’s turn on stage.

He stood on the ring and looked down.

“I guess no dragon would dare come up.” He looked at the instructor. “Just announce it a win then.”

The instructor glared at him. Dare there be a dragon more arrogant than him. This left him a little displeased. He looked down at the group of dragon whelps. Indeed, each one of them was intimidated.

“What a bunch of losers!” He cursed under his breath.

“Garen! I will fight you!” Suddenly, a high pitched voice was heard coming from the valley entrance.

A physically-tough dragon whelp plunged over, fluttering his white wings and landing on the ring. His eyes were fixated at Garen.

“Reyman?” Garen recognized this dragon whelp. No, he didn’t look much like a dragon whelp any longer. Reyman’s body resembled more of a youth’s, about the height of a human adult at four meters high. He was a towering being.

Garen looked at his size. He wasn’t far off compared to him.

They were considered the genius of the dragon race so their growth was faster than any regular dragons.

However, Garen knew that his current strength and agility was at 26 points, well above the standards amongst the young dragons.

Based on his observations, a regular dragon whelp would average below nineteen points. They would first grow in strength then equip the remaining attributes with the growth until their youth where their strength, agility, and vitality would average around 20 to 30 points. Naturally, it would increase the level of their magic resistance and spellcrafting. Adulthood would raise them to an average of between 20 to 40 points. If spellcrafting endowment was added, then they would be considered the top amongst the Level Six Beings and could combat against some weaker Level Seven Beings.

Garen did a comparison upon returning and found out that if the Suffering Knight were to meet with two adult White Dragons, then the one taking flight would be him. This was the true ferociousness of the dragon race, considering the White Dragon Clan was one of the weaker types.

“You sure you can beat me?” Garen stared at Reyman with interest.

“You are fated to be the strongest general under me!” Reyman was full of confidence as he shouted, “Come! Come under my wing, we will lead our clan to utmost glory!”

“Under your wing?” Garen smiled, “I will only go under an existence stronger than me.” Saying this, he recalled that woman at the bottom of the abyss rift. He could confirm that that woman definitely of a dragon race. Even if she wasn’t the strongest among the dragon race, she was at least an ancient one.

“Then I will defeat you!” Reyman was overconfident. It could be seen that there were scars and wounds that were freshly healed on his scales all over. He must have gone through some tough training from returning.

Chapter 1273: Youth 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Roar!

Reyman did not waste any breath and charged ahead. He swiped his tail and clawed at Garen’s waist.

However, Garen’s claw had already blocked in front of him.

With a parry, the two claws smashed onto each other.

Garen did not move while Reyman flew away from the impact. He fluttered more than ten times to counter the force.

He hung in midair and started to chant incantations.

“This guy actually cultivated spellcrafting as well?” Garen was stunned as he saw a green bracelet on Reyman’s wrist beamed in a dim light. He charged forward to elbow him.

Wham!

It was blocked, but Garen’s tail managed to whip at Reyman’s mouth.

Ow…!

The whelps beneath saw that Reyman took a hit on his mouth and couldn’t help but yelp. This was equivalent of having a human stomped on the mouth by a foot, an utter disgrace!

Reyman’s incantation was cut short as he was blown away by the lash.

He knocked onto an ice wall with a bam and the impact left a mark resembling a spider web.

Such a powerful display of strength had the instructor’s eyes twitching.

Garen stood on the ring, swiping his tail as he casually looked at Reyman who was attacked far away.

Another speedy kill…

“You’re too weak.

“You should return and train for a longer period,” He threw these words and then stared at the instructor.

“Can I get down the stage now?”

The instructor looked at him three times before slowly nodding.

“Yes.”

This fellow’s strength was similar to a young dragon. How ferocious! He was considered a genius amongst the dragon race.

However, it was mainly his fighting instinct that allowed him to strategize appropriate attacks at the right time. He was naturally born to be a fighter.

“Wait! I wish to challenge you!” Suddenly, a dragon whelp flew high and landed on stage.

It was a young whelp that followed Reyman from behind. He garnered no attention in the beginning but now that he suddenly made his appearance, he attracted everyone’s attention. After Reyman was killed so quickly, he dared to challenge. He must have something up his sleeve.

Garen carefully looked at this dragon whelp. He was smaller than Reyman. Although he wasn’t as tough-looking as him, he was still bigger than any regular whelps.

“Who are you?” He asked directly.

“Cuboshaw, brother of Reyman.” The dragon whelp’s ears were special, being long like an elf. His eyes were bright as they gleamed in unknown confidence.

“Then, come.” Garen didn’t mind who would come at him. They were all a bunch of little children anyway.

He had just said these words when Cuboshaw swooshed to his right, clawing at his waist. His speed was faster than Reyman more than a tad. He was similar to Garen’s speed.

Garen was struck by this. The growth of his body wasn’t extraordinary. If it weren’t for the nourishment of the Soul Power and the increase on his attributes, he would be a regular little White Dragon and Cuboshaw’s speed could have caught up to his agility at 26 points. It seemed that there was no lack of innate and acquired training, he must have gone through some brutal training.

“So it seems I can’t underestimate the dragon race training in this world…” He pushed his elbow to block his opponent’s claw. At the same time, he tilted his head to spew a mouth of white dragon breath that formed into a white sword stabbing at Cuboshaw’s face.

“Roar!” Cuboshaw released a compressed vigorious pressure. It was the Draconic Aura!

This Draconic Aura was explosive and had Garen’s speed and reaction slowed down by half a beat. This gave him a chance.

He didn’t care that his face that was frozen with a dragon breath. He lowered his head to ram into Garen’s back.

Bam! Cuboshaw’s tail lashed onto the back of Garen’s right limb, causing a dull collision. The area at which he was whipped seemed to bring about an attributable attack as Garen’s white scales was dyed to pale blue. It seemed to be some sort of poison as Garen’s back leg grew stiff.

Stomp stomp stomp!

After the attack, Cuboshaw retreated three steps and landed on the other side of the ring.

A cloud of green poisonous gas spurted from a ring he wore on his right claw, engulfing Garen within.

“Garen! How sneaky you are to use tools!” Leona, who was beneath, couldn’t bear to watch any longer as she yelled out with concern.

“That’s right! It’s not fair to use spellcrafting tools on the ring!” Boris and the rest hollered.

“What’s not fair? Whether it’s winning, losing, life or death, the human will not give you any fairness on the battlefield! They have always bullied others with numbers!” Cuboshaw smiled coldly. “If I were to kill him here, then it can only be blamed that on his lack of skill and no one else.”

“Instructor!” Leona looked at the instructor with disdain.

The instructor who was the only one who could stop this did not make a move. He stared coldly at all the dragons.

“What he said is true. We should stop at nothing to win. This is the practice taught to us by the humans. Many dragons die in the hands of the humans for standing firm with the old stance.”

Cuboshaw continued to smile coldly. He disregarded the dragon whelps that were stirring below.

“So you’re saying that I can also carry with me a spellcrafting tool in a competition!?” Boris coldly rebutted. He could tell that the poisonous gas was a Level Five spellcraft. No matter how strong a dragon whelp, they would sustain a major injury. Although Garen’s body seemed tougher than any regular whelps, he was still worried that he would be unable to bear it. Looking at the section where the green fog enveloped, he started to grow anxious.

“If you dare, you can come up on stage to try it out,” Cuboshaw was confident.

“What’s there to be scared!?” Boris was agitated as he fluttered his wing to fly up there. However, quickly he was pulled back by Saszt from behind.

“Boss, no! Cuboshaw has at least three enchanted equipment and he himself is a genius in spellcrafting. He could blast at least five times the spellcraft. There’s no point for you to go up there!”

“Then tell me, what can we do?!” Boris was enraged.

“I’ll go!” Leona charged forward and got up the ring.

“Isn’t this Great Elder’s seventh granddaughter?” Cuboshaw recognized Leona. “What? You’re up here to avenge your little boyfriend?”

“Shut your mouth!” A white glow overcame Leona and gathered into a white light blade before her. She shot it at Cuboshaw with a swoosh.

However, the light blade contorted by an unknown force when flying midway that it exploded into a spark of light.

“It’s Counter Current Disturbance!” Leona recognized the spell craft. It turned out to be one of the

With a swoosh, Cuboshaw’s figure appeared in front of Leona. His claw mercilessly struck at Leona’s face.

“A lesson for you to know that with impulsiveness, comes punishment…”

Cuboshaw flashed a malignant smile. With this move, Leona’s face would surely suffer a large scar that would permanently disfigure her.

“Interesting,” out of the blue, Garen’s voice was heard from the poisonous gas.

Immediately, a white figure blazed out and knocked to the side of Cuboshaw.

Wham!

A weight similar to a mad elephant rammed onto Cuboshaw. He wailed out loud as he was knocked away.

Swish!

It was not known when Garen dashed out of the poisonous gas. He was unscathed. He followed up with a vicious claw on Cuboshaw’s waist.

Wham!

Another loud crash was heard as Cuboshaw crashed onto the ground being seized by the waist. The pain almost had him unconscious. He must have broken a few bones around his waist.

“Cuboshaw!” Reyman watched with anxiousness. It was really a fight to the death for Garen! If this were to continue with another two strikes, Cuboshaw would lose his life!

The instructor beside was watching with eyes twitching. He was gasping in awe within on the viciousness of Garen.

The last claw that Garen raised was aimed at Cuboshaw’s head.

“Help!” Cuboshaw finally lost his cool as he screamed out.

“It’s over,” Garen violently whipped his claw downwards.

Wham!

His claw could not make it all the down. The instructor had somehow made his way before him with his claw locked against Garen’s.

“Instructor, what is the meaning of this?” Garen curled his lips into a smile as he looked at the instructor was who was no more than half a meter away from him. This adult White Dragon body as similar to an elephant and taller than him by a tad. His physique was much tougher.

“Do not overdo it. It is not allowed to stir trouble in the Nurturing Center,” The instructor coldly answered.

“But earlier, he intended to bully my friend.” Garen smiled.

“I said, do not overdo it.” The instructor frowned.

“I said, earlier he intended to bully my friend.” Garen returned with the same words. The smile on his face was slowly fading away.

“I don’t care. This is a ring and whatever I say, goes!” The instructor grew impatient.

“Whatever you say, goes? Then go to hell! Roar!” Garen howled and knocked onto the instructor. His claws repeatedly struck over ten times like lightning. His tail was a stake stabbing at the instructor’s face. He exploded with a full blown cold killing intent.

The instructor felt chills as he immediately camouflaged in full body ice armor. He lowered his head and drew in Dragon Breath while at the same time, clawing both claws at Garen.

Kaboom!!

Two White Dragons, big and small, collided with each other, exploding a white layer of ice fog.

A white figure flew out and landed with his claw on the ground. It pulled a long hissing scratch before stopping.

The white figure was Garen. He bent over with his head down without moving. The muscles on his body were in baling knots that it gave off a unified solid feeling. A stretch of slight white chill lingered around his body and faded. Drops of dragon blood slowly dripped onto the ring from his right claw.

And on the other end, the instructor’s figure emerged from the white fog. He was clenching onto his abdomen. It looked as though he was suddenly startled and suffered no wounds.

He stared at Garen coldly for long before uttering one sentence.

“No exceptions the next time!”

“Thank you for your understanding.” Garen smiled and got up as a human would with two back limbs erected. His white tail was gently swiping behind him like a python.

The instructor howled before turning and fluttering his wings to fly out of the valley. It wasn’t long when he disappeared out of sight.

“Class dismissed,” A voice was heard from afar.

Woah!

The dragon whelps below burst into an uproar. Garen dared defy an instructor! And an adult White Dragon, too!

Chapter 1274: Youth 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Cuboshaw lay on the ring but no one knew whether he was dead or alive. In the earlier chaos, Garen slashed a claw in the face, disfiguring him. He was now being picked up by Reyman.

“You need to be careful, Garen. Cuboshaw is very vengeful…” He looked and whispered at Garen.”

“You should be more worried about him,” Garen didn’t mind. He was happy, but it was not about this. Instead, during his encounter in the Level Five poisonous gas attack, he made a pleasant discovery.

His soul and body were freed of his disharmonious state without any reason. Now, even if an Undead Master or a Soul Master was to stand before him, they would not discover the odd state of his soul and body.

That poisonous gas itself brought about soul temptation and corroding effect.

However, as a principal attack toward the soul, Garen had a strong fitting soul so he wasn’t afraid of this sort of attacks. So, this level five spellcraft was less harmful than a pure corrosion.

Moreover, Garen’s vitality had reached the higher standard of a young dragon that could weaken spellcraft by a level. Hence, he was immune to the majority of corroding spellcraft. The remaining harm was nothing to him.

It was then that he broke free from the encirclement and rescue Leona.

“Garen!” He turned and was welcomed by Leona’s passionate embrace, “You’re just so cool!”

Leona’s entire body was hanging on Garen.

The White Dragons respected those who were powerful. As long as one displayed a strong enough strength, he would earn respect and receive attention.

As he had resolved the harmonious issue of his body and soul, he didn’t have to keep a low profile. Receiving attention would gain him more resources and obtaining the fastest growth was the matter at hand.

That was why Garen took the opportunity to go full force in the end, letting the instructor experience his current ability.

If everything were to go well, the instructor should be on his way to the Elder’s residence. Discovering one with a great promise was a great phenomenon for the future of the White Dragon Clan. He would receive great rewards from this.

“Garen, you really scared the shit out of us…” Boris and Saszt got up the ring together with the three siblings, Satwo, Sathree, and Safour who rushed over from the news and gathered around Garen.

“I really thought you were done for!” Saszt patted his chest and gasped.

“Five is the strongest!”

“Yes, Garen is the strongest.” Sathree, Safour and the rest had full confidence with Garen.

“But it’s better not to go against the instructor the next time.” Satwo was still feeling a little uneasy. He recalled Garen’s earlier arrogance to challenge an adult White Dragon. If this was the wilderness, he would have been eaten up without questions asked.

The last move pulled by Garen scared him to a full-blown sweat. His body was now still trailing with icy bits from condensing the sweat.

“The next time I’ll see who would dare to bully me in class!” Sathree was beaming with pride.

Garen was hemmed in the middle but was lost in his thought on how he resolved the harmony issue. However, no matter how he tried to recall, the only possible lead was that encounter down in the abyss.

His Soul Rings had all exploded yet in the end, miraculously resumed to normal.

Without a doubt, that powerful existence at the bottom of the abyss saved him.

“I really need to find a chance to return for a look,” Garen did not like the idea of owing anyone, moreover this was a life-saving debt. He needed to find an opportunity to return the debt. Although he was now weak, as a Demon Lord the speed of his growth surpassed any regular being. He would seek an opportunity in the future.

******

The instructor fluttered his wings and glided a half round from the side of Elder’s Peak into a pitch black cave. An old White Dragon crouched at the entrance of the cave. He opened his eyes to give a glance but did not move as though he was still asleep.

The instructor flew another few hundred meters inside the cave and quickly arrived a large hemispherical grotto. A deep blue cold lake was right in the middle of the grotto.

An old White Dragon twice the size of the instructor mounted in the waters. This old White Dragon was flipping through a huge human reference book with interest. A pair of large-sized presbyopic spectacles were framed on his nose.

“What is it again?” He did not bother to lift his head as he threw the question. He seemed to know the arrival of the instructor.

“I found a budding dragon that I think can enter the Gifted Camp,” The instructor respectably answered in a low voice.

“What kind of budding dragon?” The elder dragon yawned, “Hand-to-hand combat or spellcrafting?”

“Hand-to-hand,” The instructor quickly replied. “He is highly skilled in combat.” He added on in fear the elder dragon might pay no attention.

And of course, the moment the elder dragon heard it was hand-to-hand combat, a streak of disappointment flashed by his eyes.

“You should know that our White Dragon Clan only has three slots in the Gifted Camp and only the geniuses of the Spellcrafting department can draw the attention of those old farts.

“Fine fine, what’s the level of his Draconic Aura?”

He casually threw another question.

“Er… Level one… He just grasped the fundamentals.” The instructor was hesitant.

“Just a newbie with Level One Draconic Aura yet you want to waste one recommending slot?” The elder dragon finally lifted his head and fixated his gaze at the instructor on the opposite end of the lake. “Are you sure you’re not kidding?”

“No, not kidding.” The instructor solemnly nodded. “He’s not even one year old but his body has reached the standard of a young dragon! He’s really outstanding!”

“No matter how strong his build is, although the bodies of the dragon race are tough, there is a limit to it.” The elder dragon sighed. “The Arcane Technique is able to exhaust the Time-Space Mysteries.

“And this is limitless. You need to understand this.”

“However, if supplied with one of one Ice Stalagmites every month at the Gifted Camp, he would definitely become the strongest warrior at earliest!” The instructor wasn’t willing to give up.

“Return. Warriors can only achieve immortality with Draconic Aura. If his Draconic Aura is no good, then he’s not good enough and too young at the present. Let’s have a look after a period of time.” The elder dragon waved his arm and a large force caged the instructor up. This was an arm of a wizard that instantly tossed him a few hundred meters out of the cave.

Landing outside the cave, the instructor still could not reconcile. He found one with great promise with difficulty to turn around from his awkward situation yet Great Elder did not approve of it.

“I can only observe for now.” He fluttered his wing and flew away.

******

Deep within the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.

In a dark cave beneath a snow peak.

“Baschin’s destroyed… Even his Soul Imprint did not make it back.”

A hoarse voice was coming from deep within the cave.

Green flames lit up in the eyes of knights in armor packed on two sides of the cave. The dark cave beamed a path of dull green.

“Only by destroying all imprints entirely in an instant or sealed in an isolated space would he be unable to escape the Soul Imprint,” A knight in armor glowing in silver pattern responded in a low voice.

“Is there such an existence close by?” The hoarse voice asked.

“No findings,” The silver-patterned knight answered in a low voice.

“Then it must be due to that abnormal soul. An abnormal soul inhabiting in a White Dragon whelp… Perhaps it’s a lure.”

“The White Dragon Mountain wouldn’t feud against us out of the blue. It could be a misunderstanding. I heard that a little White Dragon clan moved around here. It could be their doing.”

“Should I send troops to crush them?” Another silver-patterned knight opened up.

“No… The clan must have an ancient dragon on watch.

“Master’s wounds have not healed completely.

“I can’t attack an ancient dragon.” The earlier silver-patterned knight rebutted.

“But Baschin can’t just die in vain,” the withered voice continued, “The lead should be on that abnormal soul.

“Use the Soul Detector to monitor the soul.

“Strike him once he leaves the White Dragon territory.”

“Understood,” The two silver-patterned knights answered in unison.

******

The life in the Nurturing Center on Elder’s Peak was disinteresting.

At least, to Garen. It was training every day, study, training, study, and repeat. They were taught a few basic techniques which were valuable to regular dragon whelps. However, for a combat expert like Garen, it was meaningless.

So he started to nap in class.

It was odd as the instructor treated him with leniency and the other whelps dared not say anything as Garen’s ability surpassed them all.

Even though it was Garen was sleeping, the truth was, he was slowly training his Draconic Aura.

The Draconic Aura was also an application of the spirit power so even ancient dragons and elder dragons proficient in Arcane Technique who did not bother with the Draconic Aura would still have a forceful suppression of the Draconic Aura. It was the reason.

Garen’s soul power was naturally powerful but his spirit power was different from the will power of the Mech World. He hadn’t grasped fully the relation between spirit power and soul power.

His body build naturally grew bigger. With the round core sacrificed by the Suffering Knight, he gained five attribute points in his pocket every month.

In a blink of an eye, a year of peacefulness has passed.

Garen was over a year old and graduated early from the dragon whelp’s Nurturing Center. He did not participate the second hunt and following the words of the instructor, his participation in the whelp’s hunt would be an act of bullying. That would be truly unfair.

So Garen officially joined the youth class.

There were many classes for dragon whelps but only one in the youth class. There were over forty dragons in it. The difference between ages varied widely, There were some forty over years old while some over more than ten. However, Garen was the only one year old there.

Even Reyman who was coined the future White Dragon King did not possess the qualification to join the youth class that early.

However, Garen wasn’t the least bit concerned about this. The reason he left the idling whelp class and joined the youth class was for the chance to go hunting in order to obtain more Crystal Cores to speed up his growth.

The youth class could participate in the summon system of the Deladia empire’s human wizards.

Following the Dragon Alliance Treaty of the end of year 445, the young dragons could forge a deed with wizards by paying a certain fee as a price to summon young dragons into battle from a far away distance.

This was one of the contents of the agreement signed by the elders and Deladia Empire’s King.

This was why Garen wasn’t that opposed to joining the youth class that early in order to integrate sooner into human society in this world.

The instructor had witness Garen’s combat strategies with a seasoned hand. Only the battlegrounds of young dragons could provide Garen a better chance to grow.

He had, after all, patted his chest before the elder.

To allow a dragon whelp to join the youth class was rarely seen in history…

Chapter 1275: Summon 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kevin Rother was a regular noble wizard. His declining aristocracy had regained a little incline thanks to his qualification as a wizard.

However, all this faced tremendous change as he was struggling to revitalize the household.

He was selected amongst the wizards to become one of the chosen ones who could forge a pledge with a dragon.

This was of the utmost glory and in the entire Deladia Empire; only wizards at Level Five could be called Great Wizards and be at an equal social class as nobles. Level Four wizards were at an awkward phase where they would be neither here nor there.

Kevin thought that being thirty over years old, his wizardry potential had reached its maximum and he could improve no further. Yet, who would have thought he would be struck with such a good luck.

“Perhaps it could bring about a turn for the better for my daughter and family.” He was holding this thought as he went ahead to the empire’s assessment point.

In the circular building of the assessment point, he found out that he wasn’t the chosen minority.

Those chosen for the pledge constituted about more than ten wizards in just their town. Amongst them were Level Three and Level Two wizards. God knows how these Level Two wizards made their way in as the Dragon Alliance Treaty required a large payment to sustain just one time summon.

“Your turn.” Kevin was pushed in the line from behind. He returned to his senses and walked ahead to sign his name on a book.

“If you are selected by the dragons, this badge will become your summoning tool to communicate coordinates.

“Don’t lose it,” The official in charge of general affairs gave a reminder. He was also a Level Five Great Wizard and he said so coldly, carrying an aura of a commanding authority.

“Understood, sir.” Kevin took the badge and left the pack in a hurry. He shifted his head to look at the line behind him. There were still seven eight of them. He felt a little perplexed.

Walking out of the assessment point, he turned back to look behind him with worry. Wizards from far and wide were still rushing into the white, circular, bread-like assessment point, getting up and down the horse carriages and walking in.

These wizards had one thing in common: wealth.

Kevin felt a little down in the dumps. Upon receiving news that he had been selected, he thought he had lucked out. However, he didn’t think that there were this many who were selected as well.

“Wizard Kevin.”

A crisp voice was heard coming from the side.

Kevin turned to the voice. It was a young lady with green skin. He recognized her. It was Selena, the only Druid around town.

“Tree Crust Spell?

“Master Selena, have you encountered some trouble?” He asked in shock. The Tree Crust Spell was only cast on self during battle. This was a Level Five spellcraft and could last for a long time. It could last up to a day.

“No, I just came across a berserk wild boar,” Selena did not explain further. Druids had always remained neutral and cold. They rarely spoke to outsiders on their private matters.

“But as for you,” She looked at the badge in Kevin’s hand. “An advice for you. If it were me, I would never accept this badge. Once you summoned a dragon, you’ll know what’s bound to happen.”

Selena and Kevin were on good terms. Both of them often traded potions and materials with each other. For her to offer an advice, it was already going out of her way.

“You mean…?” Kevin wasn’t an idiot, he quickly connected the dots with recent activities in the empire.

“The higher-ups of the empire have signed the Dragon Alliance Treaty with Red Dragon, Black Dragon, White Dragon, Green Dragon, a total of thirteen clans.

“There’s over a hundred adult dragons and a few hundred young dragons that joined the treaty.

“Why is all this happening?”

Selena dully said this and glanced at the badge in Kevin’s hand. “Don’t let the people around you be sad.”

Saying this, she left following the dirt yellow streets to the direction where she stayed without paying attention to Kevin anymore.

Kevin stood in front of his horse carriage, his mind was blank for a few seconds. He wasn’t like Selena who was a Level Five professional. For a professional at a Great Wizard level, even a Druid could be referred to as a Great Druid. It was a qualitative change from a Level Four and the channel of intel would be different. It was obvious that the input from Selena was a gesture arising out of goodwill.

“Master?” The coachman whispered at the side, “Do you want to leave?”

Kevin lowered his head and looked at the badge in his hand.

“Kevin?” A gorgeous female wizard saw him from afar and called in a tender voice, “You’re able to get a badge? Tsk tsk, really just about anyone can get their hands on the badge now, huh?”

The female wizard was accompanied by an old man in a Great Wizard robe. He was approximately over fifty and had a tough build. He dully glided his glance at Kevin.

“I hadn’t seen you for over ten years.

“You’re still making no progress, Kevin.”

“Great Wizard Chandela, Alice.” Kevin forced a smile and responded politely.

“The Grey Robes of Grey Shadow Society really is random. They just give such an important badge to just anyone,” Alice said in a sour attitude, “giving a badge to a low-level wizard who has no hope of leveling up. One summon would cost him his entire inheritance, what’s the point?”

Other wizards and passerby looked over. Kevin felt those surrounding them were looking at him as their gazes were scorchingly stabbing at him.

“What was it you said to me before?” Alice wasn’t going to let him off the hook. “There will be a day that I will stand before you as a Great Wizard! I’ll let you taste the feeling of regret!” She imitated an impassioned tone. She then stared at Kevin who has his head down with sarcasm.”

And now? I still hadn’t tasted the feeling of regret…”

“Can I go now?” Kevin felt miserable. He acted out in a sudden impulse and made a bold statement. He thought that he would be able to triumph over nature, surpass the endowment restriction and become a Level Five Great Wizard. Yet, more than ten years had passed, and he still remained a Level Four without any hope of breaking through.

Level Five was a stage where any professionals would admire with envy. To be able to reach this stage, they would uncover a specialty that was uniquely theirs.

And a Level Five Great Wizard could be more powerful than any regular wizard by a large margin. The key was the technique to cast instant spells.

To be able to grasp the instant casting technique on Level Zero and above spellcraft. Although this would exhaust double the everyday spell slot, such a technique would give the wizards an upper hand in battle without chanting.

This was a qualitative change.

“Just go then. You respond with the same line all the time, it’s so boring!” Alice was obviously trying to put him down. As a matter of fact, although wizards weren’t as ingenuine with etiquette as nobles, they wouldn’t go too far in public. Alice did this as the conflict they had had was overwhelming.

When she broke up with Kevin and found the present Great Wizard partner, she once felt guilty and planned to offer Kevin a hefty amount of compensation, but Kevin chased her out of the door in public, tossing all of them out. He even threw in a promise boldly saying that he would one day make a breakthrough to Great Wizardry and stand before her, making her feel the taste of regret.

Yet, more than ten years had passed. Their daughter was now over ten years old yet Kevin remained in Level Four like the majority of low-level wizards who could almost never see the day they would make a breakthrough into Level Five.

Only one in a hundred wizards could make a breakthrough into Level Five. It was considered a high ratio. This was as cruel as an apprentice at a threshold to formally become a wizard.

Kevin got up the horse carriage. Even the coachman felt his face burning. He hit the horse’s rear hard, rushing to leave the scene.

The houses and shops on both sides swept past one by one. The outsiders started to gather more and more on surrounding roads but Kevin did not have the mind to observe this.

He was bottling up with rage and wanted to release it, but he didn’t know how to.

He dared not take action. The Great Wizard that Alice found had his own wizard tower. There were high and low ranks between Great Wizards. Great Wizards that has the support of nobles to build their own wizard towers were different amongst the common Level Fives.

A Level Five Great Wizard within the range of the wizard tower could fight against a Level Six professional.

Hence, that old man that was named Great Wizard Chandela wasn’t someone he could just go against or defy.

Now he just wanted to return him to see his daughter. As long as his daughter was able to have a better development and future, everything else did not matter.

His daughter now was his everything.

He placed all hope onto Maria.

The town wasn’t large. The horse carriage exited the town and passed Forest Cathedral to his household residence. A little estate that wasn’t that bad.

A large pinwheel lay erected between a few areas of infertile land. A black stone house was deep within with its own front garden. Looking from afar, one could see a figure caring for the plants in the garden.

Kevin looked at the figure in the faraway garden. It was a young graceful teenager more than ten years old. She was similarly dressed in a wizard’s robe, but there was a special white robe with a moon crescent symbol embedded in the chest.

That crescent moon represented an elite group under the Grey Shadow Society – Moon Trace Watchers. Those who were chosen to join the Moon Trace Watchers were absolute geniuses who were elite and had the chance to venture immediately into Great Wizardry.

The Grey Shadow Society was a large wizard organization that stretched across the Deladia Empire. If the Snow City of Deladia Empire was the highest assembly point for imperial wizards, then the Grey Shadow Society was the entire region, including all the wizards’ gigantic alliances in all five major empires. They represented the glory and ultimate achievement of battle wizards in the north. It was not something that could be compared with the Snow City. It was worthy of the strongest existence of the highest order.

Every time he changed upon this crescent moon symbol in his daughter, Kevin would overcome with deep comfort. Although he couldn’t make it, his daughter could.

The horse carriage galloped along the pathway between the fields and reached the front of the house.

Kevin got down the carriage and instructed the coachman to park the carriage. He took large strides to his daughter.

“Maria.” He wasn’t close but his loud voice was heard first. “Weren’t you in Casweya? How did you find the time to visit me?”

Chapter 1276: Summon 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Maria shifted her head over. She had an oval face and white skin. It was just that her eyes were a little small; this was caused by nearsightedness from reading and studying. Her small eyes ruined her overall appearance, channeling an aura of reservedness.

“I’m back for a matter. Father, why did you head out? I made my way back to inform you of an important matter!” She spoke with seriousness and let go of the watering can in her hands. Kevin noticed that watering pot had run out of water for a long time, yet she did not realize this. It was obvious the matter for which she returned was important.

“What is it, you say?” His mutter hid a few syllables and released a still boundary around to prevent any leakage of sound.

The half transparent membrane slowly spread out, enveloping over the both of them. The noise from the outside world was completely isolated while the voices inside wouldn’t be able to make their way out.

Maria looked at Kevin gravely.

“Father, do not accept the badge from the Dragon Alliance Treaty of the empire! Do not ever!”

Dragon Alliance Treaty? Badge? Kevin was stunned. First, he received an advice from Selena and his daughter came from afar to warn him.

Even a silly person like Kevin would know something was wrong.

He was about to surprise his daughter with the badge he clenched behind his back. Hearing this, he simply couldn’t whip it out.

“Why?” He struggled to calm down and asked in a low tone.

“Those who held the badges distributed this time have the obligation to participate in war and required to go into battle!” Maria answered in solemnity, “These badges could definitely summon the drags, but they too are obligated to join the battle.”

“Battle? Against the Black Streak Empire?” Kevin felt his throat going dry. He had some prediction that he had to pay a price as every want needed to be obtained by sacrifice. He just didn’t think that this badge would require him to pay such a high price.

“Yes, the moment of your acceptance of the badge and signing your own name would automatically count as signing an agreement to participate the war against Black Streak Empire. Our Deladia Empire is located at the juncture between the North and South. We must first take care of the Black Streak Empire separated in the middle in order to seize the rich soil of the South. This is a war that could destroy an empire; it not a child’s play!” His daughter, Maria solemnly declared.

“This is news gathered from mother. She specifically came to warn me from receiving that badge. Only those wizards who have no more hope would gamble by accepting the badge.”

Looking at Maria’s concerned face, Kevin felt lumps up his throat. He didn’t know how to tell his daughter that everything was too late.

He knew what he was made of. He was only a wizard who thrived through wizardry potions. If he could depend on his accumulated savings on selling potions to summon dragons a couple of times, then if he were to stand in battle his death would almost be inevitable.

He had never actually battled anyone before. He was a purely academic wizard.

The badge was already in his hands. This meant that the deed was sealed.

Kevin tightened his grip on the badge. He felt helpless and depressed.

Compared to the resources on his mother’s side, he was only a regular little Level Four wizard. He possessed no strong connections and could not provide his daughter with enough assistance.

As for her mother, she would often bring her to gatherings of those young nobles, receive advice from other Great Wizards, and travel abroad to other wizard organizations for study exchanges.

This was how his daughter came about to be a Level Four wizard at a young age, entering the Moon Trace Watchers and becoming a genius elite that was nurtured with importance.

Seeing her father’s expression, Maria sensed something amiss. She immediately became nervous.

“Don’t tell me, father, you…!”

Kevin took a deep breath in and looked into his daughter’s worried eyes. In the end, he nodded.

“I have already accepted the badge…”

These words had Maria’s heart sink deep but more so was sorrow. As a wizard, she had already considered the worst case scenario before her arrival.

“It… It’s okay. Don’t you still have me? Don’t worry, father. I have arranged everything.”

“Arranged? What arrangement?” Kevin was stumped. He didn’t think that his daughter could be this calm.

Wars against the Black Streak Empire had been known to always lead to major losses. Joining the battle, even if he was a wizard, the chances of him returning was only estimated at one in four.

Maria drew a deep breath in and regained her composure.

“Don’t worry, I have upgraded to a Level Four battle wizard!” She extended her arm to grab Kevin’s hand. “This time, I will protect you!!”

Gazing at Kevin’s hesitation, he quickly took out a small round black rock.

“Look, this is the proof of my drop out. I have discontinued my studies. You need not worry about my studies. I have taken care of everything…”

Smack!

A clear and crisp sound was heard.

Kevin’s hand was raised up high. He gazed at his daughter in sorrow, pain, and disappointment.

“Did I say I need your help?! Who told you to drop out! Who told you to drop out! Huh!?”

Kevin couldn’t help it as his tears gushed out of his eyes. He would never have thought that not only could he not help his daughter, he even became her burden.

What was the battlefield of the Black Streak? It has a death poll as high as one in four! If anything were to happen to his daughter joining him in battle…

“It’s okay,” Maria’s right cheek was swollen but a smile still beamed through. “I have already dropped out and your badge may not be able to summon a dragon. We don’t need to worry too much. Maybe we’ll be able to summon the strongest black dragon?”

Kevin looked at his daughter with torrenting pain creeping up wave by wave.

Finally, the father-daughter duo couldn’t help but embrace each other and whimpered.

They did not resemble one bit the honorable wizards.

******

At night.

All the wizards in town and wizards who accepted the badges gathered in the town center. A huge canopy was built there. All the citizens around were moved out to leave this town.

Accepting the badge was equivalent to signing an agreement. The empire would be in charge of the aftermath. Those who survived the battlefield and established a certain meritorious service would regain freedom and the dragon in pact would naturally be the wizard’s personal pledged partner.

This was the so-called high risk, high reward.

To be pledged partners with a dragon, even a low-level wizard would pose a huge threat to high-level wizards. After all, even the weakest White Dragon and green dragon clan was a level six standard in adulthood.

So under such conditions, naturally there would be many wizards willing to take the risk.

Kevin, together with his daughter who was dead set on following him, participated in this Summoning Affair at night.

He brought along his large amount of summoning materials based on the requirement. A mountain of gemstones, heptachromic gemstones and a small bottle of sulfur. It was said that it could increase the chances of summoning a black dragon and a red dragon.

This time they could choose the strongest black dragon or the second, red dragon. They were really fond of volcanos.

Carrying hope with them, they were dressed in long robes and standing in the midst of the crowd. Tens of wizards formed a circle and listened to a Great Wizard of the empire in the center speak nonsense in the center. Most of their thoughts were running through the kind of dragons they would be able to summon in a moment.

“The empire has sacrificed a lot to be able to sign the Dragon Alliance Treaty with the dragon clans. I hope everyone would appreciate this opportunity and chance upon the benefits from the risk. Think about it. Once you return from the battlefield, you can have a dragon partner of your own. Your social standing in this empire will be equivalent to that of a Great Wizard.”

The Imperial Great Wizard shouted with a tone of instigation.

“Tonight will be when you summon your pledged partner. Once you have summoned, you can not go back on your word. The successful wizards will heed the enlistment and onward to the border for mopping-up operations to battle with warlocks and wizards of Black Streak Empire. The process isn’t as dangerous as you’ve imagined. There will be hunting troops and assassination troops that will be assisting you. As long as you’re careful enough, completing the mission is a cinch…”

Hearing the Great Wizard’s nonsense, Maria tightened her grip on Kevin’s hand. She could feel the nervousness of her father.

“Don’t worry, father. I am here with you. It will be okay.”

“I’m alright, I’m alright. It will be fine.” Kevin nodded but felt sorrow creeping in. As a father and a senior, to think needed his daughter to comfort him in turn.

“I have participated in assassination and hunting talks in the academy. Don’t worry, it will be alright.” Maria was calm. It didn’t look like she was faking it.

Kevin felt his palms seating but gave his daughter a gentle smile, although even he felt his smile was stiff.

The success and failure would be known tonight. If he could summon a black or red dragon, then his safety would be ensured by a whole lot.

******

Garen had recently distributed the majority of his attribute points evenly between attributes. He only left a bit on his Draconic Aura.

Within the span of more than a year, he had accumulated 62 potential points. Adding these potential points onto the attributes wasn’t the same as other worlds that require many points to increase just one attribute. There were no restrictions here as one potential point was equivalent to one attribute point.

However, Garen suspected that it might be due to the fact that this body had risen to an essential change stage.

Once this body achieved a qualitative change, to rise it would require an amass of more potential points to a tad of attribute increase. This was the process of forcefully increasing a qualitative change. Truth be told, heaving the body would require a huge supply of energy and couldn’t be done just by mere potential points.

Yet Garen had yet to meet with this circumstance. He suspected that either the potential points here were embedded with enough energy, or that the body of this White Dragon had yet to reach to the qualitative change level.

Overall, he took sixty points out of these sixty-two potential points to be evenly distributed among these attributes which were strength, agility, and vitality, each attribute by twenty points.

The remaining two points was appointed the Draconic Aura.

Muscles defined everything.

Garen had always believed in this.

Strength was everything. He was most proficient in this strategy. The majority of his combat strategy hovered around the sportsmanship of strength above all so increasing strength and mass was the fastest way to effectively combat and ensure survival. The remaining free time after could then be used to research on the wizardry system.

The required potential points for Draconic Aura was two points. Adding these, his Draconic Aura was now level three.

Chapter 1277: Communicate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Initially, he did not plan on adding to this as increasing muscle masses to their optimum was his goal. However, after joining the youth class, to participate in the Dragon Alliance Treaty and hunt at the battlefield, the lowest condition was a Level Three Draconic Aura.

Garen wasn’t interested in the Draconic Aura. He only went to Level Two in a matter of a year. He used these two potential points to increase it to Level Three in order to reach the minimum requirements.

The White Dragons gathered around the stone platform that resembled a sundial that they had performed a divine assessment at Elder’s Peak.

More than fifty young dragons quietly observed the white elder dragon holding a staff in the middle, listening to his speech. (TN: Raw dictates elder dragon as ‘it’ but previously mentioned the gender as male)

“The Deladia Empire did not reach an agreement with just us.

“There’s the black dragons, red dragons, green dragons and the most powerful wizardry dragon, the purple dragons, that signed the war agreement. Once you as pledged summoning targets are summoned, you must remember not to cause any conflict with other dragon clans. Exercise self-control as there’s no clan to protect you on the outside. Once you stir up trouble, no one will save you. Only you can save yourself or perhaps your wizard companions. To the other respective clans, we, the White Dragon Clan’s vitality is not as black dragon nor red dragon, our venom couldn’t be compared to those of the green dragons, our wizardry couldn’t match the purple dragons, but we have our advantages. The Frost Dragon Breath isn’t much here, but it is a huge threat to other races and species, so pay attention to this and be careful not to spew the dragon breath just anywhere.”

“Basically, don’t spit at random places,” a White Dragon whispered beside Garen. He was Reyman (TN: Author referred Reyman as ‘It’ here). This fellow was spiteful of Garen joining the youth class, so he acquired special privileges to enter himself.

“I hope my companion is a Great Wizard,” One female dragon muttered at the side. It was Mehsa, Leona’s older sister. Because of Leona, she became close to Garen. In the beginning, she took extra care of Garen, but now the relationship between them was mutual.

“Ditto,” Reyman whispered.

Garen wasn’t bothered by it. He had now increased 21 points evenly on three attributes in just a little over a year. An average of twenty points was brought about by the increase of attribute points. This was an abnormally terrifying average increase within one year compared to the natural growth of this White Dragon body.

In other words, if he had not had the increase in attribute points, this White Dragon physique could not slowly grow strong with a slight average each year. It would be impossible to join the youth class or compare to these young dragons.

Now, Garen’s main three attributes had reached a horrifying 46 points. His entire body seemed smaller than an average young dragon, but no one could tell that the power hidden in his body surpassed that of an adult White Dragon.

Having his strength at 47 points was above the average of the adult White Dragons. If it weren’t for Garen being wary of causing a scene and keeping it concealed, he would have reigned over the youth class.

If time allowed, he could achieve the power limit of the soul. His limit wasn’t referring to the restriction of the White Dragons here. Instead, it referred to the attribute limit accumulated from reincarnating over and over.

“When will the summoning begin?” Garen did not ask about anything else but this.

“I don’t know. Now we are sending out the token positioning. Once the wizards begin to summon, they will automatically communicate via consciousness to reach a deal before opening the teleportation portal,” Mehsa explained, “the profit of the teleportation is out of the wizard’s pocket. Although it seems to be our pay, after subtracting the materials to open the teleportation portal here, whatever left that’s ours isn’t much.”

“Another thing, this is also our only best bet of obtaining other resources. The nearby hunting activity does not provide a hunting ground for us young dragons to set out,” Mehsa added on. “I heard that we will be battling it out with those from the Black Streak Empire. I wonder who will be our enemies?”

“There seems to be all kind of living beings, mainly the Demon Warlocks and various other demons.”

A few of the young dragons were murmuring softly beside.

Garen had on an indifferent face as he stood amongst the group of dragons. He was full of brawn but wasn’t outstanding in stature. The young dragons around him dared not come close to him. Only a few familiar dragons stood at close range.

The elder dragon in the middle raised his staff and chanted out loud. He then scattered some powdery substance. The glittery substance fluttered into the hands of all the White Dragons, becoming a frozen flower.

“Bring this back with you. These are the coordinates. There will be the first summoning tonight, you can take whatever item from the summoning wizard as fixed coordinates of a summoning portal. You won’t be needing this item then,” The elder dragon raised his voice.

“As for the gain of your compensation, it would depend on yourself. Seize the opportunity well.”

The elder dragon then cast a teleportation spell and opened up a glowing portal. He walked into it and disappeared in an instant.

The white glowing portal swiftly diminished into dimness.

The surrounding White Dragons then dispersed. Each of them carried a frozen flower with them. Some of them were discussing in low voices, some of them wrestling about without a care in the world. It seemed that the attitude of the White Dragons was different toward this battle.

Garen, together with Mehsa and Reyman, flew toward their new residence.

The location that was once a cave was completely abandoned. Garen depended on special privileges to reside in a cave of a peak nearby the training site.

Bringing along Safour and the rest in, the clan has started starting to secure the source of their meals.

They flew in the direction they came from.

Mehsa was chattering casually about the latest gossip while Reyman was analyzing the frozen flower in his claws. The three dragons were flying side-by-side.

Beneath them was the starry glow of lamps in the night. Within the thick forest were the many soldiers of the Deladia Empire. They were holding a torch or carrying a spear walking around a tower.

“These matters will be accompanied by the Deladia Empire’s Level Five Great Knights. The territory near this place is divided into five Great Knights, all of whom are Level Five,” Mehsa was well-informed. “Of course, to us dragons, Level Five is nothing.

“We’ll at the peak of level six once we’re grownups.”

“But, to be adults we need at least another few decades,” Reyman suddenly added.

“That’s why many humans just can’t wait. They are a species with a short lifespan. Life’s too short that they hope that they’re able to summon adult dragons to be their pledged partners. We are only secondary.” Mehsa laughed at herself.

Garen did not speak, instead, he lowered his head to look at the soldiers in the forest. These soldiers looked like the whites of Earth from afar. Their skins were pale, with tall and sturdy builds. One look was enough to tell that they lacked sunlight. The armor on their bodies was mostly large silver pieces of chest plates. It seemed that these soldiers were carefully selected to be able to be stationed here.

Suddenly, he felt something buzzing in his head. The frozen flower in his claw was emitting a man’s voice.

“I, Kevin Madgerski Raydra, once again call upon our alliances outside the summoning portal in the space-time borders to face battle together on account of this reward.”

A short Draconic language incantation was shouted out in chant.

Garen felt bees buzzing about in his head. This was his first summon, and quickly the summoning rewards were listed out one by one. Each of them was explained about their functions and values, all of which was introduced by this person named Kevin.

“It’s starting! It’s starting! My summoner is talking to me.” Mehsa suddenly stopped her nonsense and cried out loud.

“Me too.” Reyman nodded. He took a glance at Garen. This White Dragon that he made a resolution to defeat had his eyes closed all the same. It seemed he has too, received a summoning.

“I received over ten,” Reyman whispered.

Garen popped open his eyes and gazed at him in amazement. He then continued to tidy up the various voices in his head.

It wasn’t just Kevin. A pile of different voices was jumbled in his head. Different summoners were reciting Draconic language in different accents.

Large amounts of material rewards were displayed.

This summoning was basically a seller-seller selection process.

The White Dragons were selecting a buyer and spoils that came with it, while the summoners were selecting base on the dragon’s strength.

The crucial point was that the reward of the first summoning was only the most basic compensation. If they were fronted with a strong enemy in later days, then they must increase from this basic compensation.

Garen was now selecting his summoner. He could see the amount of the summoner’s material rewards. At the same time, the other party would be able to observe his appearance.

Just as he had expected, the tens of buzzing voices that were echoing in his head at first slowly reduced to only five to six after the exchange of image projectors. A few master summoners with rich rewards had obviously given up.

The remaining five to six voices consisted of two humans and three dark elves. Garen did not know how the dark elves made their way into the Deladia Empire. These beings that lived underground and loved spiders were not very welcome, but it wasn’t something he needed to consider now.

He should be making a decision now.

“So many humans. Over ten of them. Not bad.” Mehsa started to stir. “And fifty over dark elves!”

“Me too, with over twenty humans and three dark elves. But never mind these dark things, they’re way too ugly!” Reyman muttered.

Level Five Draconic Aura really commanded the market…

Garen sighed. He was a little regretful not upgrading his Draconic Aura to high levels. He didn’t think that the selection process in the summoning would be executed this way. The others wouldn’t be able to see his ability and could only pass judgment base on appearance and Draconic Aura.

His current Draconic Aura was only increased to Level Three after a year. It was considered quite high amongst dragon whelps. Yet, within a group of young dragons, it was nothing much as they were more at level four, five and even six.

“Heed my call and Reederdarisha’s call, oh great dragon race…”

“Oh warrior from the sky who overlook and look upon everything, your flesh and blood will be with me, I will forever battle…”

“…The Large Axe Tribe will be your most faithful and dependable companion! Come, all my cash in here!”

Among these few summoners, only three materials were sizeable. Of course, this was in comparison with other summoners. The first was a dark elf named Zoel. Who would have thought this dark race was rich as although she took out peculiar items, the majority of them were rare shiny Crystal Cores.

Garen chose her without any second thought.

However…

When he pushed his awareness over for an exchange, that Zoel carefully sized him up before revealing a face of disappointment.

“Damn! It’s a dragon whelp! Deenisha! Deenisha! Get over here!…” The voice traveled far and the communication was cut off. It was obvious the summoner was not satisfied with Garen.

Indeed, no matter how much of a genius Garen was, they were going up to a war. The wizards required immediate combat effectiveness and not future potential. A dragon’s potential served no purpose to them as that would only prove at least a few decades away.

Chapter 1278: Communicate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was speechless about having his communication cut off like this. He could only turn to the person with the second highest Crystal Core reward. It was a soldier dressed in full armor and helmet. It seemed to be a man who was serious and solemn.

He quickly pushed his awareness over.

The soldier first was stunned then proceeded to communicate with Garen.

“Your Draconic Aura isn’t much.”

“My Draconic Aura may be a little weak, but it reached the standard,” Garen argued.

“You’re still a dragon whelp?” A frown covered the face of the soldier under the helmet. “I have no objection on smaller beings but I need to ask this beforehand, can you breathe fire?”

“… I’m sorry, I’m a White Dragon… I can only breath ice…” Garen was helpless.

“White Dragons can only breath ice? I thought all dragons breathed fire… Erm…” The soldier was dumbfounded and quickly regained composure, “Then I apologize. I need a fire-breathing dragon. This has been a dream of mine since little,” He apologized endlessly, “sorry, sorry.”

“It’s alright…”

Garen did not know how this person could initiate a summoning ceremony. He didn’t look like a wizard.

The third.

It was a tall muscular bald man. He wore gold earrings, two bronze wristbands and had a chest full of hair. Beside him was the carcass of an unknown large beast.

“Quickly now, I pay a handsome reward. The Large Axe Tribe never discriminates against companions. Even though you’re very little, even though you’re only a White Dragon and not the black dragon I want, it’s okay. Leave the war to me. You just need to stand behind and breath fire!” The bald man said crudely.

Garen looked at the carcass beside him. Although it was camouflaged, that was a dragon, right? A young dragon that hadn’t died for long.

Did this person think he was an idiot? Only an idiot wouldn’t be able to see through this obvious summoning trap.

Garen was speechless. The supposed summoning trap was to bait dragons through rewards then proceed to kill the dragon for materials, treasure, and resource.

These tactics were normally done by evil wizards. It must be some disturbance by the Black Streak Empire.

He decisively ended the conversation.

It was empty and vast in his mind.

The remaining summoners were simply too wretched.

There wasn’t any Demon Core and Garen only needed them. The majority of these summoners were weak. The weakest was a Level Two. Seeing her pale state at the verge of spewing blood, bringing this companion to war would be inviting death with open arms.

Ignored.

He looked at another one. A tall skinny pole, wearing an impoverished wizard robe. The reward was a few old-looking antiques. Yet, there were no wizardry elements to them. How silly of him to summon a dragon with these things.

Ignored again.

The last one was this Kevin’s voice that first jumped into his mind. Although he hadn’t yet responded to him, he did not give up.

Garen was a little surprised. He offered to push his awareness over to be in touch with him.

“Do you have Demon Cores?”

“Yes, I have two, two Level Fours!” Kevin seemed frightened and immediately replied. He released out a summoning request and any dragons with a slight compatibility would heed this request. However, up to now, the summoning ceremony was almost over, yet only a little White Dragon responded to him. He had already made up his mind to give up and thought that there would not be any dragon that would take to him.

The things that he could take out to attract the dragons were too little after all, apart from some jewels. The dragons loved collecting these jewel, but the main attraction was the tools or scrolls that were useful to battles.

He heard nothing from the black dragons and red dragons that he was the most hopeful for. The purple dragons cut off communications from him at the first second.

As communications broke off one by one, Kevin fell into a deep slum.

But at the very last moment, he didn’t think the last contact transferred over his awareness.

“It seems that you don’t have any other dragon choices,” said Garen in a low voice.

Kevin was in awe as he lowered his head without saying a word. He hadn’t always been a confident person even as a Level Four wizard. Furthermore, he was facing a White Dragon that was the weakest of all dragons, but a dragon whelp was still a valuable kind of level four beings. His unrealistic hope was lost and he should be lucky to have a dragon that was willing to choose him.

Garen still has plenty of other choices such as the underground black ghosts but he really didn’t like these dirty-looking coals. Not just their appearance but the spider goddess that these black coals worshipped. That fellow was known for teasing souls, and if an abnormal soul such as his were to go over…

“Right, him then. I don’t have any other choices.” Garen helplessly stared at Kevin.

Kevin could see in Garen’s eyes that misery loved company. Both of them were leftovers from the selection and could only depend on each other.

“I’ll say… Could the rewards be replaced by Demonic Cores from now on?” Garen started bargaining, “I don’t oppose to jewels.”

“Sure, no problem,” Kevin answered swiftly.

“It’s best not to look for me if it’s a battle with no Demonic Cores. It’s not worth it,” Garen continued to demand, “if it’s a Level Five being and the risk of danger is heightened, then you need to increase the reward to at least one Level Four Crystal Core.”

“This… Isn’t it a little expensive?” It was hard on Kevin as his income wasn’t that expandable, and taking out two Level Four Crystal Core at a time was already much. Yet, now Garen requested for three Level Four Crystal Cores for every summon.

Three! That was a lot as it would be enough to buy the most expensive villa in town and hire over ten beautiful maids for a month of hedonism.

“This is already really cheap,” Garen casually added. “Just see how you manage it. Don’t tell me you can’t even take out these small number?”

He seemed casual and indifferent during negotiations, but he was, in fact, serious within. This person was his only way and best bet to swiftly gather the Demon Cores.

Ever since he got in trouble with that Level Seven Suffering Knight, Garen felt that something dangerous was waiting for him in the outer world mountain range so he dared not hunt for Demon Cores himself and stayed within reach of the Elder’s Peak.

Now this summoner here would be the main source of Demon Cores for a long time. He mustn’t take this lightly.

“And, the summoning should not be less than once in a month,” Garen continued. If he were to summon him once in a blue moon, what would he gain then?

“Your requests are… too high. I can’t bear the expenses…” Kevin was silent for a long time before answering in difficulty.

Garen was also speechless.

The two stared at each other. For a moment, nobody said anything.

After a while, Garen helplessly asked.

“How much can you take on?”

No matter how horribly he fared, he was still a dragon. A White Dragon whelp that was a level being. Even if a Level Four wizard was employed, it wouldn’t be this cheap, right? If one Level Four Crystal Core was used to open the summoning portal, wouldn’t that mean Garen could only earn that little profit only?

“I… I only have these two Level Four Crystal Cores…” Kevin’s face was flushed red as he answered with his head lowered. “If I sold my house then I can push in one Level Three Crystal Core…” This was all his inheritance.

All these years in order to provide for his daughter’s studies, he devoted himself to making potions and the profits were mostly for his daughter’s spending. Wizardry was the most expensive profession as just the wasted materials on experiments each year was enough to cause bankruptcy to a village noble. A small part of those failed experiments could be used to exchange some resources while the remains could only be destroyed and wasted. There was just so much money burned off in a year.

For most regular people, Kevin was financially doing well. However, to the dragon race, he was poverty-stricken and poor to the point that he couldn’t afford an underwear.

“These can be the cost for a one-time summoning…” Garen had no words but he has lost all other contacts. He has to choose this person. If he knew this would happen, he would have chosen… Sigh… He suddenly recalled that nobody chose him, apart from this Kevin.

In other words, he himself was left with no other choice.

“So, I can only depend on myself?” Garen thought to himself. He first had some certain expectations that perhaps he could earn higher level Demon Cores through summoning to increase his growth. It looked like now it was just wild wishes.

This person named Kevin was not only a poor man. He didn’t seem like a combat wizard. He was the academic type. There would be no hope for him in war. There was no telling how long he could survive.

“Okay okay, don’t come bother me if there’s no matter then.” Garen forcefully sighed and cut off his dream of earning Demon Cores.

“Now give me something from your side. And that’s it.”

“Oh… I’m sorry. I’m just too poor… This is the deposit for the first summoning,” Kevin helplessly placed his Level Four Crystal Core up the summoning ceremony.

With a swoosh, the Crystal Core disappeared and appeared before Garen. Garen’s awareness has also left a mark on Kevin.

The human and the dragon had instantly sworn in a partnership through the exchange.

“That’s it then. I like to sleep so don’t look for me if you don’t have any matters. Let’s talk when you have collected enough Demon Cores,” Garen left these words in a depressed mood and cut off the communications.

On the other side.

Kevin walked down from the dimmed lit summoning formation. His daughter went up to hold onto him with concern.

“How was it, father? Did you manage to pledge a dragon?”

Looking at his daughter’s eyes of expectation, Kevin wanted to deny as pledging and not pledging made no difference considering Garen’s attitude. Yet, he didn’t want to see his daughter’s disappointed face, so he nodded and forced a smile.

“I was lucky to meet a White Dragon. Although White Dragons are the weakest dragons, but the fella I met is very strong. I was surprised at first. That head, that body, couldn’t be compared to a regular White Dragon. He was basically equivalent to a black dragon. He’s really strong!” He was unexpectedly proficient in spinning lies. But the request for rewards is simply too much… He needed at least three Level Four Crystal Cores. I convinced him to lower to two level four and one level three Crystal Cores.” Kevin pretended to put on a satisfied but pocket-burned face.

“This is still very expensive. But at the very least, father, you have a dragon companion. You have at least a trump card at the battlefield.” His daughter was genuinely happy for him.

“So it’s best we do not summon him frequently but only at crucial times,” Kevin quickly added. Although he didn’t want to lie to his daughter, he really did not want her disappointed.

Chapter 1279: Outing 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After settling on the summoning contract, Garen retreated back to the cave. A Level Four Demon Core wasn’t even the least bit enough.

Safour was carefully drawing something in the cave. It seemed to be some learning task in the spellcrafting course.

Sathree and Satwo were off somewhere. They were recently seen out and about.

“Hey, four,” Garen pushed aside his restlessness and casually asked. “Do you know where did Satwo and Sathree go?”

“I’m not sure… I think I heard Satwo mentioned about going to some underground palace to hunt. I heard that it’s an accompanied combat with those from the Deladia Empire,” Safour turned to answer.

“The Deladia Empire?” Garen was stunned. This Deladia Empire seemed to be everywhere. Its relation with the White Dragon clan seemed to be closer.

“Yes, now all the dragon whelps are to participle in this teamwork to nurture combat compatibility.” Safour glanced at Garen and found that he was a little agitated.

“I’m heading out to buy some materials.” He found an excuse to leave promptly. He really didn’t want to be the receiving end of Garen’s foul mood.

“Buy materials?” Garen was stunned again.

He flew out and followed Safour from behind. They quickly flew to the bottom of the Snow Peak to a block built by humans. It was bustling there. There were five or six tradespeople bawling with a dragon guard at the side, protecting the peace.

The trades here must receive the permission of the elders.

“I really don’t know how these people obtained the White Dragon’s elders’ approval.” Garen flew down and followed behind a few dragon whelps. He retrieved his wings and left Safour alone as he walked to a stall to have a look.

The tradesperson was shouting a language he did not comprehend. However, this did not hinder them from communicating as the tradesperson immediately flashed a smile and proceed to raise a sign in Draconic language saying, “One Level Three Frost Type Crystal Core to exchange with two items.”

Garen was speechless as he looked at the items in the stall. There were all shiny, manmade items that could blind one’s eyes. Apart from them being pleasing to the eye, they had no function.

What caught him speechless was the dragon whelps that bought them. A dragon whelp beside him was forthright to whip up a Level Three Demon Core to trade for two glass items at another stall. It was obvious that the items were glass-made ones that did not worth anything.

“What a ripoff!”

Garen was speechless and went around other places. Some of them were selling man-made oil painting, some were selling high-quality imitation antiques, but most of them were selling various book reference.

These book references were extremely expensive and were sold by the number of Demon Cores. Moreover, they weren’t useful. They were all literature like novels and poems. They were mostly not even in Draconic language. Garen only recognized headings in the banners the tradespeople raised.

Leaving the trading street, Garen gave it a thought that if he wanted more Demon Cores to enhance himself, heading out to hunt was still the way to go.

He was still in debt of that mysterious woman’s help, it stood within reason that he should go and thank her.

Although he felt that the outside harbored great danger, if he wouldn’t head out due to danger and hold himself back just because of danger, then he wouldn’t call himself Garen.

He thought about it before flying off.

The current him was no longer the person from a year ago. Perhaps that danger wouldn’t pose that big of a threat.

******

Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.

Beneath an area of overly white snow, the ground started to rumble.

The noon sunlight was just beaming down, reflecting a white glow on the snow.

Clang!

Suddenly, the snow area was pulled open. A large amount of snow splattered about. A human-like life form in black armor was held in there.

Hiss…

The snow on the surface of the human-like life form’s armor melted and vaporized, giving others the feeling that it was at a boiling level. In truth, the armor almost bore no warmth, it even possessed an even lower temperature than the snow around.

“It’s here…” This human form was the Suffering Knight that attacked Garen earlier. His body was covered with layer and layer of something similar to black oil. That black oil started to melt and drip onto the ground, but the droplets strangely disappeared.

“It’s here… Have you informed master?”

At the other side, about a few thousand meters away, a black Suffering Knight erected from the snow the same way. The surface of his body was covered with a thick layer of something in oil form.

“Master can see it earlier than we can. Let’s first capture this abnormal soul. We should be able to find out what we want to know from it.” The two Suffering Knights were a few thousand meters apart yet they were conversing as though they were face to face. Their voices weren’t loud but could transmit to each other’s ears.

Swoosh!

The two Suffering Knights soared to the sky and headed in the direction of Garen.

******

The white snow mountain had a sharp peak as a volcano.

Looking from afar, the snow mountain was blue all around. Flying toward the snow mountain, Garen felt the air was cleaner. Compared to the era of technology, the cleanliness of air was far beyond imagination.

Leaving the White Dragon Clan’s territory, he dashed toward the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.

The last time he was shuttling back and forth within Fiery Blaze Mountain Range and was pursued unintentionally and arrived at the place.

Now, to find that area again would be difficult as he was sought after during that time and had the snowstorm affecting his vision.

Flying above the mountain range, Garen gazed down.

With shrouds of white clouds lingering, the dark mountain figure appeared indistinctly under the camouflage of snow.

He could sometimes see Giant Frost Iguanas moving around the mountain.

These Giant Iguanas had poor visions. They were only able to sniff their enemy at close range. The mountain was bustling with activity as he could see more than ten Giant Iguanas scattered around.

“This sort of place is what we call a good place to hunt.” Garen sighed deeply as he charged down toward a Giant Iguana.

He planned to hunt while looking for that woman that saved him.

The Fiery Blaze Mountain Range had Giant Iguanas that were at least Level Four. The remaining were either Level Five or level Six. Of course, it was still the outer range here, so although these level four Giant Iguanas were at the same level as him, it was only a representation of their spellcrafting and ability. On strength and vitality, Level Four Giant Iguanas were still considered powerful.

As a safety precaution, Garen followed the wind’s current down and slowly flapped his wings to a pass near the Giant Iguana to prevent it from smelling his scent.

His current strength and agility were beyond the past. His strength at 47 points had him similar to an adult White Dragon. An Agility at 47 points enabled him to zip pass tens of meters in a second without acceleration. A Vitality at 40 points would have him collide with a Giant Iguana unscathed.

The present Garen was an adult White Dragon in the clothing of a whelp.

The Giant Iguana afar was lowering its head chomping on a snow deer’s carcass. Red blood was splattered everywhere. There were some areas where it was frozen to red icicles.

Garen gently landed on the ground. His strong limbs deeply scratched into the snow. He crouched his body and paced himself towards the Giant Iguana.

The Giant Iguana took no notice as its white sharp fangs were feasting the snow deer’s carcass in large bites, making crackling noises.

Swish!

Garen leaped forward and took a tiger bite.

Similar to a white snowstorm, he pressed onto the Giant Iguana and took a bite, tearing its throat apart. The decades of meters in distance went by in a flash.

Blood sprinkled out and splashed on Garen’s face, but he wasn’t bothered.

He stood up and got up from the Giant Iguana. His claw grasped mercilessly on the collapsing Iguana. He looked on as it whimpered and struggled in pain but was tightly clasped by his claw.

With a swish, Garen clawed and drugged out the crystal core in the Giant Iguana, waving it around in his claw.

“Level Four Crystal Core, as simple as that.” He had given up on obtaining and hunting Crystal Core through summoning. That pest of a wizard was perhaps on the battlefield and have died in some corner.

“Next up.”

He left the Giant Iguana’s carcass and fluttered his wings in the air.

He quickly targeted a Level Four Giant Iguana.

Using the same sneak attack tactic, the Giant Iguana did not even lay eyes on Garen’s shadow and activate its frozen armor when it was bit in the throat in a blink of an eye, breathing its last.

The tactic was similar to assassination and succeeded at any turn.

Using the same way, Garen continuously gained two Crystal Cores. He started to aim at the Level Five Giant Iguana he wounded the last time.

The Level Five Giant Iguanas were larger than the Level Fours, especially that long large streamlined tail that actively whipped around like a python.

If someone was fooled by the Level Five Giant Iguanas’ heavy build and appearance, they would be met with extremely swift tail-whipping once they were close.

Garen had shared that fate the last time.

This time, he planned to make an attempt.

Without any disguise, Garen landed on the snowy ground and took large strides toward the Giant Iguana.

The back of this large Iguana has a burned scar. It seemed that it once battled with an enemy proficient with flames and left a mark. Its skin was tough and a layer of thick frozen armor covered its entire body. Different from Level Four, the frozen armors of Level Five Giant Iguanas could cover their entire body.

Sensing danger nearing, the Level Five became alert as it lowered its head at Garen. Arching its body, he was in a position to charge ahead.

“It looks like it has a certain level of intelligence.” Garen burst into laughter. A Level Five Giant Iguana wouldn’t normally use its head to attack. Yet, for this Giant Iguana to pose in such a position, it was obviously trying to confuse the enemy so those who thought it would approach with the head would let their guard down about its tail.

However, Garen wanted a face-on attack, so whatever the Giant Iguana was planning on, he wasn’t that much bothered.

Walking over, Garen started to accelerate towards the Giant Iguana when the distance between them was about fifty meters apart.

The Giant Iguana tensed up its muscles.

Roar!

It howled out loud, causing the ground to tremble. This Level Five technique burst out as a trembling splattered some snow around the area. A large wave of tremor mixed with snowflakes was going to collide onto Garen who was charging over.

Garen did not avoid and used his elbow to block head-on, banging violently onto it.

Chapter 1280: Outing 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Wham!

With a large slam, the Giant Iguana took a few steps back. The ice armor on its frontal head had a huge crack. Its quake was destroyed and his Level Five ice armor was almost broken apart.

The powerful effects of Garen’s 47 points of Strength had finally made an appearance.

This was the strength of an adult dragon and an adult dragon was the peak of a Level Six being.

Hence, Garen relied on this advantage to combat against a Level Five Giant Iguana. A Strength of 47 points entered the range of Level Six, meaning collision was equivalent to an adult dragon ramming into the Giant Iguana. The result went without saying.

The Giant Iguana was knocked out of senses and shook its head violently. Its eyes reeked of hesitation and fear.

Garen was done testing the levels of his strength. He was without reserve as he took large strides forward to claw the back of the Giant Iguana.

Crackle!

The ice armor cracked open, so did its skin. In the end, the crackle was the breaking of its bones.

The Giant Iguana was on its knees by Garen’s claw. Its limbs were torn apart neatly.

Roar!

The Giant Iguana cried out in pain.

Garen could quickly hear footsteps of surrounding Giant Iguanas rushing over.

“It was the same the last time. It seems Level Five Giant Iguanas travel in groups. Now that it’s happening again, it’s not a coincidence.”

He did not leave. He wanted to see the extent his combat abilities had reached.

At a similar disposition, he was confident no one could take him face on.

******

Two dark figures were shooting past the snowy mountain range like two black swords, sharp and conspicuous. All the Giant Iguana Elders bowed down in respect when they saw them from below.

They were the God from deep within the snow mountain. The subordinates of the mysterious existence of the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.

It wasn’t just an Undead Wizard behind these Suffering Knights. If it was just a Suffering Knight or an indeed master, the ultimate Giant Iguana Elders would show no fear. They were great in numbers after all.

However, behind the undead master, stood that existence that they dared not offend.

The Undead Wizard was also the last straw in the dark, protecting the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range from outsiders, plundering and killing at will.

As long as they did not proactively offend the Suffering Knights, everybody was safe.

The two Suffering Knights soared high and headed towards outside the mountain range.

Swoosh!

One of the Suffering Knights landed on the ground and looked at the messy blood stains and the carcass of a Level Four Giant Iguana that had been killed not a long time ago.

“He isn’t far.”

The other Suffering Knight landed and nodded at him.

“His powers have grown fast. He’s grown a lot in a year.”

“You said so yourself. It’s only a year. How much can he grow?” The other didn’t take it to heart. “The person we need to take precautions of is not him, but the existence that may appear behind him.”

“You’re right.”

Both of them investigated the scene. Its Demon Core was dug out, but it was the same for its eyes. There was nothing that could be salvaged.

They carefully inspected the possible direction to which Garen had left.

The two Suffering Knights soared into the sky and flew towards the direction of Garen.

******

Wham!

Four Level Five Giant Iguanas gnashed their fangs at Garen but they were shook off by Garen at the same time. They scattered away.

He was surrounded by four Giant Iguanas. All of them were Level Five Giant Iguanas. Instantly, the Level Five Giant Iguanas coordinated well with each other to encircle him and set off an earthquake.

Yet they were flipped over by Garen, a dragon.

The four Giant Iguanas somersaulted in the air like bowling pins, rolling far off and crashing onto the ground heavily, whimpering out with pain.

Garen stood in the middle unscathed.

If these Giant Iguanas were to come forth one by one, it may perhaps exhaust him out. However, all of them coming out at once gave him enough leverage and opportunity to spot their weak point. Moreover, his strength matched up with his speed to immediately erupt in action, creating a sort of explosive effect.

Four Level Five Giant Iguanas were all pushed away to the sky.

“Too weak!” Garen stood in the center without a scratch. With a minute difference in disposition, he was well-seasoned in combat skill which completely made up the difference in disposition. He burst out an ability that was well past his actual data and this created this over-exaggerated phenomenon.

The four Giant Iguanas fell onto the ground everywhere. Two of them knocked onto a nearby cliff and rock, rolling a few rounds. For a moment, they still didn’t even get up.

They were shaken by Garen’s strength mixed with a high-level skill. The shock was enough to injure their insides.

Garen slow paced toward one of the Giant Iguanas. He was prepared to dig out his Demon Core.

Suddenly, he lifted his head and stared at the faraway sky.

Two enormously strong sources of aura were shooting toward him at a high speed.

“That again?” Garen was familiar with this aura because he still carried with him the core that that being that hunted him.

The black figures flashed before him like the descending of two flashes of lightning. Two Suffering Knights dripping in black oil instantly appeared in front of Garen.

“You guys…” Garen narrowed his eyes and asked.

Swish!

He quickly left the place. The snow beneath his feet now had two snow pits.

The party wasted no time as they made a move. One knight took out a black knight’s spear in shape of an umbrella and swiftly maneuvered at him with sturdy yet accurate precision. It was as though he had predicted all of Garen’s evading position.

The other knight appeared at the side like a bat and drew a peculiar semicircle arc. A long black sword appeared in his hands. The exquisite long blade was as fine as a finger. He could flick five six blade lights in a matter of a second. At the same time, he flew to the side of Garen’s waist.

The two were so well-coordination with each other. One of them took the front while the other at the side, as though they had done so many times.

Roar!

Garen opened his mouth and spewed a mouth of cold dragon breath but stronger, was the sound waves of the huge dragon howl.

He unleashed a terrifying dragon howl. With a 47 point Strength and 40 point Vitality, this formed a powerful sound wave weapon and exploding to the front and his sides.

The humongous sound wave compressed the air and violently rammed face-on onto the two knights.

Buzz!

The actions of the duo paused. They didn’t think that Garen’s explosive roar was this powerful. They must have miscalculated that they lacked in energy, causing their movement to slow down for a moment.

Taking the delay of this very moment, Garen did not retreat. Instead, he plunged on and pounced forward.

His claw viciously grabbed onto the knight’s spear of the Suffering Knight, adding his high-level skill shock as well as the Ice Pressure Blade he was proficient with into the mix. His claw snarled at the weakest point at the side of the knight’s spear.

The Suffering Knight didn’t think he was this quick and was abruptly raised up that his knight’s spear slanted away and stabbed to the top of Garen’s head.

However, the strength of a Level Five professional was revering. The Suffering Knight was also an expert in hand-to-hand combat, so this Suffering Knight followed the flow to stab upwards. A sharp knife jumped out of the handle of the spear and cut towards Garen.

Garen’s tail whipped the side of the knife, knocking away the direction of the attack.

Yet, at that moment came the attack of the other.

The black fine blade pricked at Garen’s waist like needles, drawing five six sharp blade lights as if they were sufficient to penetrate anything, as they made contact on the scales by Garen’s waist.

At the slightest distance, Garen contorted the muscles of his waist and pierced through an impossible space between the blade lights.

“Suffering Eye!”

The Suffering Knight at the side shouted out. His black fine sword fired a black light, sinking into Garen’s scales.

Roar!

Energy from Garen’s entire body fired up, taking the Suffering Knight by the spear and ferociously smashing at it.

The combustion of his energy was so vast that the two Suffering Knights thought they were battling with an adult White Dragon.

Not only did he appear to be like an adult White Dragon, Garen’s disposition was similar to an adult White Dragon. If his actual battle experience was factored in, perhaps only the most experienced Dragon Guards could face him.

Wham!

He couldn’t retrieve his spear fast enough that it hit violently onto the Suffering Knight’s helmet.

The heavy sturdy knight’s spear had a huge indent from the shock of Garen’s terrifying power.

The Suffering Knight flew backward and a large amount of black oil and black smoke from his body splattered out.

“You have a death wish!”

The Suffering Knight in front of him was furious as his knight’s spear lit up a red symbol.

Once Garen saw the symbol lit up in red light, alarms were blazing in him. He quickly retreated and flew away without hesitation. His speed was faster from the time he attacked.

Out of the sudden, the red symbol on the spear of the Suffering Knight instantly dimmed without a locked-in target. The speed of his opponent was simply too fast.

With a joint attack of two Level Seven professionals, he could still continuously tried many attack and defense.

If this fight of Garen’s was to be spread, it would definitely create a great stir in the White Dragon Clan.

“It’s that thing again from the last time? Too bad, without locking in, it is meaningless.” Garen smiled as he flapped both wings and erected to the sky, flying far.

In a short time frame of close combat, he managed to catch them by surprise. However, if he were to stall, then the red symbol locking technique was something scary. Immediately getting away was the best choice.

“He’s trying to escape! Seize him!!” The wounded Suffering Knight got up in embarrassment. He had been smashed tens of meters away that his helmet sunk in. This was the most humiliating moment in the history of his countless battles.

His helmet was crushed in by a little White Dragon that was only a few years old. If words were to travel, then he would be a laughingstock in presence of their master!

He didn’t need to stay more as the Suffering Knight with the knight’s spear soared into the sky and sought after Garen.

The two Suffering Knights could not halt a White Dragon whelp. This was a definite blot in their fame as knights.

Two black lights, one on the front and one at the back, pursued closely behind Garen.

Chapter 1281: Talent 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen flew at a high speed up above in the white snowy mountain as he was moving toward the perimeter outside of the snowy mountain. He recalled his feelings and sensation back in the day when he flew about casually as he tried to find the magical place once more.

Both the Suffering Knights were in tight pursuit from behind and they were clearly enraged by him. They had tried countless of time to corner him by splitting up so that Garen would move to a certain direction. However, Garen had completely ignored them since his speed was faster than theirs. Hence he would fly about in his own path.

As he was flying around, he vaguely noticed that some of the Elder Giant Iguanas that he passed by were very respectful toward the Suffering Knights. Since they seemed to be allies, Garen did not dare to fly deeper in. Instead, he decided to fly toward the outskirts.

The sky gradually turned dark as the night approached. The three of them were still flying in the sky at high speed. The mountain ranged below them seemed to be endless as they flew into an unknown area.

Garen soon gradually realized that the snowflakes started appearing more and more as they danced chaotically with the strong gale.

A tornado-like blizzard had started forming.

Garen flew into the tornado blizzard that had yet to fully form and felt a familiar sensation welcoming him.

“This is it!” He was slightly delighted. He was extremely familiar with the blizzard which lasted for days as he was chased by a Suffering Knight in the same condition for a few days last time.

He was able to hold up against a Suffering Knight for a long period of time. It was way easier than before now that he was twice as fast. However, Garen did not wish to simply get rid of the Suffering Knights’ pursuit, so he would occasionally reduce his speed to kite them along to prevent them from losing sight of him.

“Damn it! Where is this guy trying to escape to!? We’re in a blizzard! We’ll be taken to a place that isn’t worthwhile at all!” The Suffering Knight who was holding a Knight’s Spear could not help but curse out.

“I feel that he is kiting us.” The Suffering Knight with the sword pondered as he spoke softly. “We have to find a way to inform the higher up. Perhaps he’s planning to lure us to a stronger being that is backing him. Didn’t he… do that the last time?”

“Be careful.”

“Don’t worry… I will use what the superior gave me when it’s necessary.”

************

The more Garen flew, the more familiar it became. It was the same circumstances as before, where he could not see anything in front but a pure white blizzard. Garen could not have differentiated up and down if not for the gravity pulling him down.

However, he was familiar with this sensation.

“This feels really strange…” Garen’s Soul Ring felt a very slight vibration that he had not experienced before. It felt like the air around him was trembling.

He tried to fly straight on, fighting against the blizzard’s resistance and paying close attention toward two of the Suffering Knights tailing behind him.

Two days had passed in a blink of an eye.

Garen had no idea how long he had been flying and estimated that he had been doing so for the past two days and nights. However, the blizzard did not seem to have an end, as it kept blowing strong at him.

However, he felt that he was approaching closer towards the eye of the blizzard.

At last, the blizzard’s pull became stronger as Garen flew towards where its strength was at its peak.

Pew!

In a blink of an eye, everything was clear in front of him.

He had, once again, flown out of the blizzard.

What appeared before his eyes was a pure and serene azure lake. The calm lake water mirrored the huge snowy mountain in front of him. The sky was completely blue; it did not feel like he was at the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range at all.

The air was so clean to the point where bacteria were seemingly unable to sustain in such a condition.

Garen once again felt the strange ubiquitous presence.

He turned around to look at the humongous blizzard cyclone which connected the sky and earth as two Suffering Knights clumsily flew out from it. However, they did not seem to be tired at all as they recovered the moment the got out from it.

“The Undead live up to their name. They really don’t know what exhaustion means.” Garen laughed coldly. He then turned his head around and ignored them as he flew directly towards the snowy mountain.

He started searching for the crevice that he found last time.

Soon, he found the crevice that he found on the side of the snowy mountain and went inside it.

“It’s too dangerous here!” The Suffering Knight holding the Knight’s Spear said softly as he flew to the entrance of the crevice Garen had entered.

“We have lost contact with our superior. It seems that he uses this method to kill our comrade.” The Suffering Knight with the sword said sternly. “Should we pursue?”

“Can we catch up?” The Suffering Knight with Knight’s Spear questioned back. “I feel like he’s kiting us.”

“Should we start setting up here? The superior will solve this incident if he arrives.”

“No. It’s unwise to do so without knowing our opponent’s background. It will bring a lot of trouble to our superior.”

“They can’t do anything to us as long as we don’t enter it.” The analysis of the Suffering Knight with the sword was very spot on.

“Very well.”

Both of them were once warriors who had survived hundreds of battles. Although a portion of their soul and mind had degraded after turning into an Undead, they were still equipped with a very high awareness and trait.

They did not follow Garen into the crevice. Instead, they started flying around slowly as they analyzed the surrounding.

**************

Garen followed the path as he kept flying downwards.

He did not care if the other two were tailing him as he kept flying downward with his curiosity fully filled up in his heart.

The crevice became larger and darker as the end of the abyss was too dark to be seen.

The crevice gradually turned into an abyss in which darkness swallowed everything, be it living or the other.

Garen dismissed it as he flew straight down to the very bottom.

He did not know how long he had been flying, as the concept of time did not seem to be applicable inside. Ultimately, he could see a faint white light at the bottom of the abyss.

“This is it!” He was excited as he hastened up and flew towards the white light.

Black smokes with countless human faces started appearing again as they surrounded him. They were sighing in such a manner that it felt like they were either crying or chuckling at the same time.

Garen ignored the black smoke. Although they were rather terrifying, he had nothing to fear as they were unable to harm any living beings.

He flew directly toward the light source, and soon the transparent sphere appeared before his eyes once again.

“I’ve come to repay you, the one who saved my life!” Garen floated in the air as he shouted loudly in Draconic Language.

His voice traveled towards the ball, scaring the black smoke faces away like terrified fishes.

The light source did not respond. It was completely quiet as if there were no living creatures within it at all.

Garen did not panic as he waited patiently.

After ten minutes or so…

A movement started to appear at the bottom.

The light ball became half transparent, revealing a woman in a black tunic skirt.

She widened her eyes, but it gave off a sensation that she was not focusing her sight at all.

“Why have you returned?” Her lips did not move but her deep and hoarse voice had transmitted into Garen’s ears through a special method. Although she was speaking in Draconic Language as well, she had an ancient accent when she spoke.

“I’ve saved you last time, but that doesn’t mean I am in the same mood to do so again…” The woman’s voice sounded like a man’s. It did not fit along with her physical beauty at all.

“I come to this place because I want to know how my life savior looks like. My name is Garen and I am from the White Dragon Clan. I’ll definitely repay you in the future when the opportunity arises!”

Garen said with a serious look on his face.

“I don’t need you to repay me back.” The woman responded. “You can’t repay me, to begin with.”

“Whether you accept my gratitude is your concern, and it’s my decision to repay you, whether you like it or not!” Garen said straightforwardly. “I just want to do what I believe is needed!”

His words were so decisive that it seemed to have caught the woman’s interest as she looked at him with her senseless gaze. Her eyes were like a torchlight as a blinding light instantly beamed out from it, causing Garen’s eyes to turn red. He was on the verge of tearing up even though he was hundreds of meters away from her. He felt that It was as if he was shot by a laser beam.

“Interesting…” The woman’s deep tone had a hint of laughter. “A little kid from another plane… Your soul… is quite special.”

Garen was shocked but he immediately calmed down. It was very normal of her to be able to see through him since she was able to casually fix his Soul Ring when it exploded.

“Special?” He lowered his head in an attempt to avoid directly into her eyes as he said sincerely. “I know my soul is special, but I don’t know which part of it is special at all.”

“Anguru Byron, the God of Pharmacy, once created a multi-dimensional medicine and released a total amount of sixteen million five hundred and fourteen hundred thousands of them… I didn’t expect to be able to see a successful sample here.” The information which the woman gave out in a deep tone had greatly shocked Garen.

“The God of Pharmacy?!” He was astonished.

“You’re in a very interesting situation and possess a very high research value.” The woman revealed a smile on her perfectly calmed face.

“What you’re saying is that the reason my soul is special is due to the multi-dimensional medicine created by the God of Pharmacy?!” This was the very first time that someone was able to determine the origin of his soul’s deepest and darkest secret.

If she was not lying to Garen, then her existence is way much higher than Garen’s…

A lot of thought went pass his mind in an instant, but he managed to suppress all of these thoughts in an instant as well. All of his thoughts could be under strict surveillance as he faced against such a powerful existence. Any of his ill thoughts would be observed just like a bacteria under a microscope.

“The quality of your soul has reached to a certain strength as you trained on your own. I am interested in your process of enhancing your soul as it may be beneficial to my own training,” The woman continued speaking with a weird male’s voice.

“What you’re suggesting is…?” Garen trembled.

“I will make a deal with you.” The woman said in a deep tone.

“A deal?”

“You have two choices.” The woman said softly. “First, you’ll cooperate with me with my experiments until I fully understand the reasoning behind the change in your soul’s quality. As a reward, I will give you a prized item you wanted, which will be able to strengthen your soul. Its effect will be ten times more compared to the one you currently have on you.”

“Ten times more…” Garen understood that she was referring to the Suffering Core he had picked up. The core was able to increase his potential points twice as fast as before.

If he were to obtain a treasure that was ten times stronger…

Chapter 1282: Talent 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Now, Garen wrapped the Suffering Core with a leaf and hanged it at the back of his hind leg so that he could enhance his Soul Energy whenever he wished.

He would be able to obtain thirty Potential Points in a month if it was ten times stronger. This would greatly reduce the time required for his progression!

He only required a maximum of ten years! He would then be able to recover back to his strongest form where he would be able to destroy an entire planet!

It was an incredible temptation as he did not have to search for resources high and low in the future and potentially put himself at risk. All he had to do was to cooperate with her in her experiments.

“Second. You’ll cooperate with me to finish my experiment and I shall adjust your soul and give you a similarly-powerful ability.”

The woman explained calmly.

“You. Which one will you choose?”

The abyss fell into silence as a subtle matter had subtly seeped into Garen’s conscious to tempt and shake his ideals. These matters seemed to be released from the woman’s body. They were colorless, odorless and shapeless, similar to a worm.

Garen did not respond instantly. It was as though the woman did not have any concept of time at all as she remained still, waiting for his response.

Perhaps time was counted in terms of years to these beings and a year would be equivalent to an afternoon nap for them.

“I…” Garen finally spoke up. Half an hour had passed before he finally opened his mouth.

“I don’t want anything.” He blurted as it ached his heart. He felt rather unfortunate as it was an ultimate temptation to him, regardless of the first or second option. The temptation was similar to putting a scrumptious meal in front of you when you were hungry or placing a clear water in front of you when you were thirsty.

“To repay you for saving my life, I don’t want anything and will cooperate with your experiments unconditionally!”

Garen suppressed the temptation and the dilemma in his heart as he felt that his Soul Ring had become purer than before. He withstood the temptation in his mind and made a decision which resonated with his desire without being influenced by external factors. This was considered a training to him as well.

“You don’t want anything?” The woman was shocked.

She pondered for a moment before revealing her understanding gaze.

“I see…” She seemed to have noticed the small change in Garen’s soul and finally revealed an expression on her face for the very first time.

“You were able to withstand the temptation and make a decision based on your belief. Impressive. Since you’ve already decided, how about you come to this place every year on this day to help me with my experiment? Are you fine with that?”

Garen nodded.

“I understand!”

“You have to understand that this is your own decision. I will not give you any reward,” the woman repeated.

The woman looked at him in silence for a while before the surface of the light shook.

The black smoke resembling countless of faces gathered swiftly and fused together on Garen’s neck, condensing themselves into a long, thin and exquisite black gemstone necklace.

“This is the pass for you to enter here so that you don’t have to spend so much energy rushing in. No living being can enter this place without my permission,” the woman said calmly.

“Understood.” Garen lowered his head and touched the necklace. It was cold and had an unexplainable clear sensation; it was as though he was touching some extremely clear water. The sensation was extremely weird as he was clearly touching an actual item.

“My name is Garen. You are…”

“You can call me Ann.” The woman shut her eyes as the light membrane returned to its muddy state where no one could see clearly what’s inside.

“Ann…?” Garen repeated.

Ann did not respond; it was obvious that she no longer wished to converse with him.

Garen pondered for a moment before flying out of the abyss as he flew towards the crevice.

What surprised him was that these black smoke faces did not dare to fly around him after the black gemstone necklace was placed on him. Instead, they avoided him out of fear.

Ann had given him the most important piece of information. If she did not lie to him, then Garen finally knew that his gifted ability was one of the accidental successful products from the medicine that was created by Anguru Byron, the God of Pharmacy who produced tens of millions of them.

Garen believed that Ann had no reason to lie to him, so her words were very believable.

He kept pondering as he flew his way back to the outside world.

If the abnormality of his soul was really caused by this world’s medicine, that meant that this world’s God was able to communicate with his original world where Earth was located.

His heart was brimming with excitement as he thought of this. It had been so many years. It was his deepest desire to return back to Earth and live the day before he transmigrated. His exhaustion grew each day as he wandered outside again and again as he transmigrated.

He had been trying to go back all these while but he could not find any information related to his world.

As Garen flew out of the crevice, the first thing he saw floating outside were the two Suffering Knights waiting for him.

“You’ve finally come out. I thought you’d already died inside,” the Suffering Knight holding the Knight’s Spear sneered.

“I thought I could have taken you down in an instant but we almost messed up instead. Let’s see how you’re going to escape from us this time,” the opponent spoke in an extremely confident tone.

Garen tried to sense behind him to realize that Ann wasn’t responding at all. It seemed she had decided not to meddle in. She was definitely in the better mood last time when she assisted him.

He could no longer hope that Ann would help him once more.

Two Level Seven Suffering Knights… Tsk tsk. Their existences were considered a high-level undead even among the undead beings, second only to the strongest Level Nine Horrifying Knights. They were considered as the upper-class beings among the knights. If they were to be placed in the human civilization, a Level Seven being could become the lord of a remote country and be awarded by the title of Earl.

On the other hand, the Deladia Empire which was located in the north was an empire with an incredible strength. Two beings of this level could simply appear in the wild and Garen only had himself to thank for his incredible luck.

“Although Ann will not help me, I have promised her that I will assist her in completing her experiment. If I were to be in a life-threatening situation, doesn’t that mean her experiments will never see its end? That means…” Garen had made up his mind. Although it was rather impudent of him, it was necessary for him to achieve victory so he was willing to look past this shamelessness.

He sneered in his mind as he looked at both of the Level Seven Suffering Knights with malicious intent. He decided to use them to test Ann’s attitude towards the experiment.

“Both of you.” Garen reached out his dragon claw. “Come at me at once.”

He gave them a scornful look.

As expected, both the Suffering Knights were not easily irritated by his gesture and decided to attack him at once.

The steam of black light rushed toward him as red symbols appeared on both the sword and spear at the same time. The symbol’s light which resembled the color of a fire suddenly exploded and instantly sucked the three of them inside, disappearing instantly in mid-air.

“The Final Death Match!” Both Suffering Knights and Garen appeared inside a narrow red dimension at the same time. They seemed to be trapped inside a spherical dimension.

Both Suffering Knights yelled as they rushed towards Garen at the same time. He was not able to avoid in such a narrow space and there seemed to be a law that prevented him from evading at all. The only thing he could do was to face them head on!

The two Suffering Knights had managed to create a dimensional rule which completely favored them. The dimensional rule was based on the real world and stood above the real world at the same time. It was the first time Garen witnessed such a strength.

However, Garen had never feared to fight against others head on! It was a good opportunity to test his limits as well.

Garen mustered all of his strength and as he was about to release them, an excruciating pain could be felt by his waist! This pain took him by surprise and he had lost all of the strength that he mustered a while ago. With this instant delay, he had no choice but to stare at both of the Suffering Knights’ weapons that were quickly approaching him.

The scales on his body stood up as he felt an intense danger fast approaching him.

Draconic Aura!

Boom!

Garen instantly gathered a Level Three Draconic Aura and exploded it in front of his chest instead of the fast approaching weapon in front of him.

Boom!

His body was instantly pushed back by a small distance due to the explosion, allowing him to avoid both of the incoming weapons.

As Garen avoided the crisis, he diverted the flow of his entire body’s strength and crawled up into a white ball.

Pew!

Then, he widened his body and attacked with his dragon claws while using his Ice Pressure Blade and Vibration Technique. At the same time, the wings on his back started vibrating at a high frequency. The 47 points of his Agility was instantly pushed to its limits as he focused all of his strength onto his dragon claws.

This was the absolutely invincible Unrivaled Dragon Claw! It focused on attacking the chest areas of its opponents!

Garen did not know why he recalled the line of a certain movie he had seen in the past. However, his current posture could be considered as an extremely authentic dragon claw attack, right?

As he recalled this strange idea, what was considered an extremely mighty posture had become a dreadful posture.

His claws were heading directly toward the Suffering Knights’ chest…

“How dare you!” What surprised him was that the Suffering Knight with the Knight’s Spear was actually a female. She was embarrassed and angry at the same time. She, who already had pushed her strength to its very limits, had decided to even squeeze every ounce of her strength out as her anger engulfed her.

The dragon claws, knight’s spear, and black swords clashed against each other within the red dimension.

The incredibly tough dragon claws cracked before it shattered into millions of pieces. Both of his hands were almost amputated as well. His claws were not amputated because of his incredibly high defense and 40 points of Vitality. Even so, he had suffered tremendously.

The white dragon blood spilled everywhere as he was pushed to the inner wall of the red spherical dimension.

Ultimately, he was only a Level Six. His strength would have been shocking to everyone since he was not instantly killed when faced with two Level Seven beings.

However, he was surprised as both the Suffering Knights in front of him had suddenly lost their defenses as they did not pursue after him immediately. They stood still as they took out a small yellow scroll each from their pauldron’s crevice. The scroll, which was tied with a red thread, had its thread pulled open as both of them were about to open up the scroll.

“How dare you!”

Suddenly, the entire red dimensional space started trembling.

The space shattered, revealing the snowy mountain and blue lake outside of the red dimension.

Ann’s voice traveled instantly from an unknown location as an invisible power and landed on both Suffering Knights.

Boom!

Both the Suffering Knights were instantly lighted with a black fire. The fire did not possess a high temperature, and it gave off an extremely shrilling aura.

“Have mercy!” Both Suffering Knights cried out.

Creak!

The black light flashed in front of Garen and blinded him in the process. Both the Suffering Knights who were on fire vanished instantly as if they had never existed.

He looked at the sky in front of him shockingly…

“It ended just like that?”

Chapter 1283: Mishap 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“You still aren’t leaving yet?” Ann’s voice instantly appeared in Garen’s mind.

Garen was speechless as he levitated in the air. He stared at the crevice pitifully as he hoped that Ann would throw out the Suffering Cores. Since she might not see them as valuable items, he would gladly take them away.

It would be a waste for him to not take these cores.

However, it seemed that Ann did not intend to throw them out.

Garen shamelessly waited for a while longer and reluctantly left after realizing that it was hopeless.

He turned his head around and looked at the snowy peak before flying back into the blizzard.

He was unsure of Ann’s identity, but he knew that she was way above him, especially when he first witnessed the ridiculous power where time seemed to have been reversed. Garen had never encountered such a ridiculous power, even when he was in the Mech World where the laws were the most lenient.

To be able to instantly recover what had already been destroyed. Something this ridiculous could only be referred to as a miracle…

Garen then flew into the white blizzard which connected the sky and the earth, carrying the remnants of his doubts along with him.

It was different from the previous experience as the necklace on his neck vanished as if it had never existed. At first, Garen could not see anything in front of him, and the next thing he realized was that he had already arrived at the entrance of the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range, which was directly in front of him.

The sky was already dark, and the purple crescent moon showered everything underneath it with a silver moonlight.

Garen was certain that he was inside the blizzard a moment ago; there was no longer a single indication of a blizzard around him.

“The blizzard appears at one second and disappears at the next. This is indeed mysterious… Perhaps it is a secondary plane independent of the primary plane?”

He did not put much thought into it; it would be pointless even if he had done so.

He increased his speed as he started flying toward the White Dragon Clan.

*************

Deep within the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.

A faint green fire was burning inside the cave.

“It happened again… They couldn’t even release the Projection Scroll in time.” A pale, old voice came from the depths of the cave.

“We have already lost three knights. We have never encountered such a loss since the past few thousand years,” the silver-striped Knight said softly.

He and another silver-striped Knight were kneeling down in front of the green fire.

“I’ve done enough preparation this time but they couldn’t even open up the scroll in time… My tracker had disappeared as well.” The old and pale voice sounded confused. “Perhaps there exists a secondary plane nearby, since leaving the primary plane is the only way to disconnect the tracker that I created.”

“Master, do you wish to negotiate with the White Dragon Clan?” A beautiful female voice came from one of the dark corners.

“What’s the point of looking for them? Even the White Dragon Clan does not wish to provoke the being behind that abnormal soul. That being is, at the very least, a Level Nine since it was able to eliminate two Level Seven instantly,” The old and pale voice responded.

“What do you mean?” The female voice sounded puzzled.

“We shall wait and see. Soon, something will happen to that small clan… And we will act when they’re too busy with their own affairs. The movement of the Snow City… is soon…”

“I understand…” The female voice stopped speaking. She seemed to have recalled something as she understood what he was referring to.

**************

Four months had passed in a blink of an eye.

Garen had holed up inside the clan ever since his return for several reasons. Firstly, he was waiting to be summoned to collect Demon Cores. Secondly, it was obvious that the opponent had an incredibly-powerful organization backing two of the Suffering Knights whom he encountered back then. It was an organization so powerful that he currently could not fight against. Hence he decided to stay within the Elder’s Peak to continue his training.

The rest of the teenage dragons from the teenage class had been summoned to participate in the war and only a few dragons had yet to be summoned. Garen was one of them. He even suspected that the summoner had accidentally died somewhere in the battlefield.

Since there were no updates, he decided to wander around within the White Dragon Clan.

Ever since he was reincarnated into this world, he did not dare to wreak havoc everywhere because his soul was unique. There was supervision being done by the God, not to mention the old White Dragon God lived in the area too. However, he felt that he had almost solved the issue in which his soul and body were not coordinated with each other.

Hence, he finally had enough courage to start understanding the overall situation around him.

He would set out every morning and start moving around the residential area. He would slowly fly around the Elder’s Peak and avoid places protected by the Dragon Guards as well as private properties that had obviously been spread with the Draconic Aura.

It took Garen four full days to finish checking out the entire White Dragon Clan’s area.

The Elder’s Peak was not just a single peak. With the main peak as the epicenter, there were thirty-two other secondary peaks surrounding it, all of which housed the strongest and highest authoritative White Dragons.

Further out from the main peak was the residential area of the weaker White Dragon families. The outermost regions were the forests and breeding grounds. There were humans from the Deladia Empire living in the forest, together with the Thunder Snake of the Vassal Clan. There were also Dog-headed Humans as the minority. They knew how to speak in the Draconic Language even though they had just migrated here for less than a year. The Sacrificial Scroll unique to the Dog-headed Humans were the popular currency among the humans. They relied on the White Dragon Clan to protect them from the wild creatures and the small market that the humans had created had started to develop. The items that could be bought had expanded, and the variety had increased as well. Naturally, the prices had become more reasonable.

Occasionally, living beings from the other clans would bring their specialties along to make a trade as well.

They had been breeding dragon beasts species in groups in the breeding ground. They were the main cannon fodders in the war and would often be sold to the humans as pets or carriers. The material required to create the Dragon Leather Scroll which the Wizards required originated from them as well. The Dragon Leather Scroll and the Dragon Blood Ink actually did not derive from the bodies of the authentic dragon clan. In fact, they were products obtained from these dragon species.

In these aspects, the White Dragon Clan seemed to have reached a long-term agreement with the nobles from the Deladia Empire.

Garen realized that the humans within the clan had steadily increased over time and the Elder’s Peak had enacted an Act preventing any conflict between the human and dragons. The majority of the White Dragons were willing to obey the law after several severe punishments toward a few Adult White Dragons. After all, conflicts were not the only thing humans was able to bring upon them. They could also bring upon all kinds of food, resources and shiny objects which they adored.

As the White Dragon Clan worked alongside with the Deladia Empire, their food and drink were greatly assured for the past year or so. All they had to do was to give up some items that did not matter to them. These items included the dragon scales that had been shed off from their body, dragon claws that had to be cut off due to overgrowth, or previous collections which they were bored with or no longer benefited them. In return, they would obtain a luxurious life and no longer be required to go out to risk their lives as they hunted for their own food.

Garen returned to his cave at the mountainside as he took a turn around the entire Elder’s Peak. He had a slight gist of what the humans were trying to do.

They planned to domesticate the White Dragon Clan to the point where they could not live without them. Then they would form an alliance or even enslave them!

However, these were none of his concern. Perhaps it would be better this way as it would be a win-win situation compared to the wandering lifestyle.

He returned to his cave as he continued to accumulate his Potential Points. Three months had passed in a blink of an eye, and a new batch of dragon whelps had been born.

The day was the sixteenth day of the seventh month.

A new batch of dragon whelps had hatched in the clan and had enrolled in the Nurturing Course. The Soul Inspection was being held on the Elder’s Peak. It was a major event as the soul inspection ceremony was still held by the Great Elder.

Garen did not head out to see the ceremony. Instead, he decided to stay inside in his cave alone to rest. He had started to value the Draconic Aura after he realizing its effect during the battle with the Suffering Knights.

However, something seemed to have occurred during the Soul Inspection ceremony. Sathree and Safour, who had attended the event, rushed back to the cave.

“Something terrible has happened!”

Sathree shouted as he rushed towards Garen impatiently.

“Something terrible has happened in the clan. Garen, how could you have the mood to stay inside here. Let’s go have a look!”

“Something terrible?” Garen widened his eyes as he looked at the hysterical Sathree and Safour.

“What’s going on? Isn’t the major Soul Inspection ceremony being held right now?”

“It’s the Soul Inspection. Boris’ grandfather is in trouble!”

“It’s not just them, Leona’s grandfather is in trouble as well! The three elders had allied with the humans and betrayed the clan!”

“They’d imprisoned the Great Elder and said that he’s a rebel!”

Both dragon whelps took turns to inform Garen as to what had transpired as they rushed toward him, trying to pull him to the scene.

“Boris and Leona are currently being isolated and questioned! Saszt tried to save them but he was taken away by his parents. We couldn’t think of any idea and had no choice but to come to you to solve this issue!”

“Garen, you always have a solution to a problem. Please think of a way to help them!”

Although the dragon whelps are naturally selfish, they had befriended Boris and Leona after getting along with them for a long time. They came rushing back and reporting everything because they were friends.

Garen was pulled out of the cave by two dragon whelps and they flew directly towards the Elder’s Peak.

He had obtained thirty-five Potential Points since his return seven months ago. Thirty out of the thirty-five points were all added to his Strength, Agility, and Vitality, pushing his Attributes to an unprecedented state. The remaining five points had been used to increase the effect of Draconic Aura.

Both of his Strength and Agility had reached 57 points and his Vitality had reached 50 points.

Garen’s body size was technically no different compared to a typical teenage dragon, which was the size of a horse. Still, his fighting ability had technically reached the level of the strongest matured White Dragons.

His powerful Vitality had given him a stronger Spell Immunity and an even higher physical defense.

Garen brought two of the dragon whelps along and rushed directly toward the sundial-like interrogation platform which was located at the side of the Elder’s Peak.

A lot of White Dragons and humans could be seen gathering over there from afar through the white mist.

The sundial was a complete mess as the sharp long needle was broken; a battle seemed to have occurred there.

Boris had been restrained by two teenage dragons as he was pressed onto the ground, unable to move at all. All he could do was to give off an agonizing roar.

The entire situation was divided into three parties. The first one was the humans in a gorgeous silver gold attire. They were in a group, and aura kept oozing out from the strongest humans among them. Two of the warriors in golden armor had caught Garen’s attention as the weapons they were holding were releasing a terrifyingly powerful threat; it seemed to be weapons that had been stained with the Dragon Blood.

One did not even need to look to know that these two Warriors were incredibly powerful.

On the other hand, the White Dragons were separated into two groups where one was a bigger group than the other.

The third elder was smiling with a staff in his hand as he represented the majority of the dragons. He had two White Dragon Guards in a silver heavy armor by his side as he spoke to the minority of the White Dragons. There were a huge group of powerful Adult White Dragons hovering in the air behind him as they kept growled at them.

Most of the White Dragons in the minority were all adults; all of them were in disdain, annoyed and angry.

“The second elder will never betray us!”

“You can’t simply judge the second elder with your evidence!”

“This is a conspiracy!”

“Third elder, are you trying to let the Great Tiamat see through your evil soul?!” The strongest Adult White Dragon among the minority group walked out and shouted.

Chapter 1284: Mishap 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“See through me? I can see through your despicable souls!” Third Elder’s slender dragon face smiled. “Right now, before the First Prince of Deladia and with His Highness the Prince as our witness, we’ve just put the faction in order and completely eliminated the tumors that were hiding within the clan all along. This should be a great and glorious occasion! Phosphorus, as the strongest warrior of the clan, you shouldn’t obstruct me!”

“This isn’t just an obstruction, you’re destroying the clan!” The Adult White Dragon named Phosphorus spoke in a deep voice and took one step forward, while several shrouds of intense Draconic Aura was released from his body slowly.

This Draconic Aura was so enormous and powerful that the air around him had distorted naturally, while numerous fine black lines would appear occasionally. These lines were cracks that had split open when the surrounding space could not help but tremble.

Third Elder smiled and lifted his staff. The end of the staff was releasing a dim, white light to block off the Draconic Aura. This was a divine strength with the characteristics that greatly surpassed Draconic Auras; it could nullify its Coercion.

There was a pale-skinned man with handsome features on the side where the humans were clustered. He smiled and looked at the rod within the White Dragon Clan before him while being protected by two Golden Knights.

“Our Deladia Empire has reasons to believe that your honorable clan can definitely obtain even more glorious developments than before under Third Elder’s leadership. As long as your honorable clan agrees to engage in deeper levels of relations with us, both of our parties will receive extremely exceptional mutual benefits respectively.”

While these important figures were having a discussion, Garen took this opportunity to squeeze into of the group from the White Dragon faction from the back quietly.

His Young Dragon physique appeared insignificant among the herd of Adult White Dragons that were the size of elephants. He squeezed past them before being pushed in front of Boris quickly.

Although Boris’s entire body was wounded, he did not give up on struggling at all and resisted with determination. However, the White Dragon that was restraining him turned around and slapped him immediately when he was tired of Boris’s struggling. He was beaten until blood flowed unceasingly from his head. The other dragon was completely unconcerned that he was on the brink of death.

Leona was slightly better-behaved. She merely remained on the side and cried terribly while being immobilized by fear.

All of the other Dragon Whelps, who were usually on good terms with them, were currently nowhere to be seen.

Without the protection of their grandfathers, Leona and Boris were merely Dragon Whelps that were slightly stronger than the rest. There was not much of a difference between them and the other dragons.

Third Elder’s oldest grandson Wylow was currently showing off his strength before the two dragons.

“Look here, look here. little Boris who was so unimaginably arrogant a while ago has now been obediently restrained below me. He can’t even turn his body around to get up! Leona, I’d already told you earlier that you wouldn’t have a future with Boris. Do you regret it now?” Wylow sneered cynically.

“I’ve already signed an Eternal Contract with His Highness the Second Prince. The entire Deladia Empire that has sworn to this is currently behind me! Do you really think that depending on the Great Elder, that single old man, is equivalent to resisting a whole, powerful empire? Idiot!”

Wylow was already a five-year-old Dragon Whelp, but he had taken a liking to Leona who was always playing with Boris. He was clearly humiliated because of the conflict that happened between Leona and Boris previously.

He was currently beside himself with joy now that he had gained the upper hand suddenly.

“Fight me if you have the skills!!” roared Boris while panting gruffly.

Wylow seemed to pay no mind. He cast his gaze towards Leona who was on the side instead.

“What do you think? Can you see my current powers now?” He sneered. “You’ll only have to listen to me obediently if you want to save your granddad. I’ll go to the place where he’s located and ask my grandfather to show him mercy. Since you adore me so much, you’re probably really happy that I can release your granddad, right?”

Leona’s tears trickled down her face terribly. She had initially assumed that today would only be a day for her to watch the show. It was supposed to be a day of great joy; she would have never imagined that such a horrible mishap would happen.

She was merely a normal little Dragon Whelp who was completely powerless, unable to resist this situation that she was encountering.

Wylow was surrounded and protected by Adult White Dragons, leaving her with no way to revolt at all.

The Dragon Whelps and Young Dragon bystanders around them did not dare to make a sound. Too many White Dragons had received favors from the humans now. Moreover, the White Dragons possessed selfish natures and would not concern themselves with unrelated matters. Hence, numerous cold gazes were the only things that were cast their way.

Leona merely felt extremely exhausted. She truly missed the time when her grandfather protected her previously. That sense of security and relief…

Plop.

She felt an external force pushing her back suddenly. It was a great force that caused her to fall in front of Wylow immediately.

She struggled to get up, but she was instantly and violently restrained by a large amount of strength behind her.

“Release me!” she cried loudly.

“Oh no, stop crying. I won’t mistreat you the next time we’re together!” laughed Wylow loudly while walking behind Leona.

“Let me see how this little female dragon has developed? It looks like you’ve matured pretty well!”

The surrounding White Dragons laughed in a slightly lewd manner.

Wylow became even more pleased and proceeded to reach his hand out and grab Leona’s tail. Apparently, he was planning to lift her tail to look at her reproductive organs below.

Even though the White Dragons were considered to have slightly less polite than humans, actions like these were unfathomable in public in front of a large audience. He was actually thinking of looking at a female dragon’s reproductive organs while a crowd of so many White Dragons looked on around him.

Aside from insulting her, he did not even view Leona as a dragon at all!

He was going to display her most private areas and show them to everyone around him. These actions were considered obscene in any civilized groups.

“That’s enough! Stop!”

A voice interrupted Wylow’s laughter suddenly. He felt his dragon claw drop suddenly before a Young Dragon appeared before him instantly, holding one claw above his own.

“What’s your status? How dare you speak to me like this?” Wylow’s face darkened. His grandfather was currently the most powerful individual in the entire clan. Thus, he could simply act as he pleased unscrupulously. A burning fury ignited in his heart when this dragon actually dared to step forward and stop him.

The White Dragon who had rushed out was naturally Garen. His Young Dragon physique stood in the middle of the White Dragons around him without the slightest hint of awkwardness or fear.

“This matter ends here.” He glanced at Wylow indifferently. “If this matter passes the point of no return now, you may not have anywhere to go when you encounter difficulties in the future.”

Although his relationships with Boris and Leona were nothing special, they were still his friends in the end. When they were in trouble, it would be impossible for him not to appear personally and check up on them regardless of his feelings or rationale.

However, he was unwilling to terribly offend Third Elder who was currently in power.

“Garen… You’re Garen?!” Wylow had actually recognized him unexpectedly. A hint of fear flashed in his eyes suddenly.

He remembered the other party. He had initially assumed that it would be unlikely for Garen to come forward for Boris and Leona, as he thought that Garen’s personality had always been cold. However, it looked like this assumption was inaccurate now. Nonetheless, judging from Garen’s state, it seemed as though he had only come forward because Wylow had gone too far.

When Garen defeated Reyman in the beginning, the Elders in the clan, including Wylow’s grandfather, had unanimously agreed to use Garen as the breeding focal point when they were cultivating a mate for him. After the observation period had passed, they had basically already determined that Garen was currently the most talented White Dragon in the clan now, while even Reyman merely ranked behind him.

Wylow’s grandfather valued him appropriately as well.

Hence, the White Dragons did not want to fight with Garen to the point where things were strained.

“So this is Garen, huh.” A trace of a smile appeared at the corner of his mouth immediately before a hint of a triumphant look flashed in his eyes when he looked at Leona on the ground.

“Since you’ve appeared personally and made this request, I’ll grant it! I won’t shame you this time.” He would get another chance to settle his scores with both of them anyway.

The last sentence that he had added earlier came from his heart.

Garen nodded and that was considered as his response. He would not have bothered with an insignificant figure like this fellow if his backer was not Third Elder.

“I’ll certainly need to invite Brother Garen over to my cave to spend time with me when I’m free. Grandfather and Father have admired you for a long time.” Wylow walked forward at the last minute before throwing these sentences out.

“We should definitely do that if the opportunity arises,” Garen simply said that as a form of courtesy.

Only then did Wylow happily take his few White Dragon Guards away before they turned and left.

Garen watched them left into the distance before they returned to Third Elder’s side. He could see Third Elder smiling and nodding at him from afar among the flock of dragons to indicate his approval.

Garen returned the smile to show respect.

As an Elder and an Oracle, Third Elder had Level Nine powers at least. Moreover, his strength would probably reach Level Ten as Tiamat’s staff could arouse Divine Power simultaneously.

Generally speaking, all Professionals who had surpassed Level Nine were already known as Pinnacles.

The highest-leveled Professionals were usually ranked at Level Nine. From Level Six onward, there would be an extremely huge difference between each level. Many accumulated years would be needed to charge forward and achieve the rank above. They could not make an impact and upgrade themselves easily unlike Level Six and below.

Level Ten beings had already obtained the authority to impact the demigod realm. Obviously, there were very few individuals who knew how to become demigods in the end. The Secret Book of Becoming Demigods had always been the most prized secret in the clan because it was a scarce resource that the Gods controlled strictly. Only those who had chosen to join the Gods, passed the faithfulness assessment, and signed a contract with an extremely powerful binding force that resembled the Underworld River Oath could obtain this type of knowledge.

Level Nine was actually the highest position within the entire mortal realm already. This was the summit of relying on one’s own body to train and practice. Moreover, it was also the apex of what all beings could achieve by depending on their own determination and talents.

The supernatural realm that was considered as the inhuman layer came after that. Obtaining or realizing divinity and conviction before igniting a sacred fire was not something that normal beings could achieve without inheriting it. Its degree of complexity greatly surpassed the fantasies of any life forms. They would have to experience extremely brutal murders and struggles as well.

Therefore, Garen understood that he currently did not have the right to clash with beings like this no matter what.

Moreover, there was no need for him to provoke the issue now that Boris and Leona were safe.

“Are you okay?” He turned around and looked at Leona. This girl was lying on the ground and crying pitifully before she clambered up and pressed herself against Garen’s chest tightly when she heard his voice.

“Oh…” Everything that happened to her today was extremely cruel indeed.

Boris crawled up beside them. His body was covered in blood while both of his arms were fractured. When he saw that Leona had flung herself into Garen’s embrace, his complexion turned white while his entire dragon’s body seemed like a suppressed but active volcano that could erupt anytime.

Garen glanced at him.

“You should go home. These matters are already out of your control,” he sighed.

Some of the onlooking Dragon Whelps in their surroundings wanted to approach and comfort them. However, they did not walk forward in the end and merely watched the three Dragon Whelps.

Safour, Sathree, and Satwo were among the flock of Dragon Whelps, but Garen instructed them not to come out.

“Thanks for the things you did today.” It seemed like Boris was squeezing the words out through the spaces between his teeth. He clenched both of his claws tightly while his entire body trembled slightly.

The Enchanted Equipment that he wore on his body originally had now gone missing. It was clearly snatched by someone else.

“It’s fine. Both of you need to be careful next time,” Garen reminded. “It doesn’t look like that brat will let you off so easily.”

“Yes.” Boris nodded vigorously. He scanned the four corners and looked through his entire surroundings seriously as if he was trying to engrave everything in his mind deeply.

Everything that happened today would perhaps remain in his memory forever!

Chapter 1285: Contract 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The incident that happened during the ceremony had greatly provoked Boris and Leona. From that day on, they were unusually determined to practice their Draconic Auras. They would often ask Garen for help regarding various problems as well at the same time.

Garen did not hold back from teaching them. His knowledge was excessively plentiful to the point where these two little fellows had the misconception that he was an Elder Dragon with an abundance of experience.

It seemed like none of the difficulties that they had encountered were too hard for Garen.

More than a month gradually passed like that.

Third Elder stabilized the overall situation and imprisoned both Great Elder and Second Elder while announcing that they had officially formed an alliance with the Deladia Empire. The princes and princesses of the Empire would come and select partners from the clan to form Eternal Contracts.

Eternal Contracts were unlike ordinary Soul Contracts. Lives would need to be linked in exchange for these contracts to be signed. These were formidable commitments that every creature could only sign once in their lives.

They did not have any other functions except for their only purpose, which was to share lives.

In other words, the lives of the dragon race and humans that signed these Eternal Contracts would be treated as one before they were split into two equal parts after that. The dragon race whose lifespans greatly surpassed the humans would undeniably find this extremely unfair.

The dragon race’s lifespan would be reduced by at least half due to this. Moreover, human lifespans were usually insignificant in comparison to that of the dragon race.

The weaker members of the dragon race would live to at least a thousand years old.

This rule had caused dissatisfaction among numerous White Dragons, especially the members of the dragon race who had set themselves high above the masses. No dragon would be willing to make an agreement with a Contractor unless they were of the standards of specialized Level Six Professionals or above.

However, the side of the Deladia Empire had taken the initiative to explain that only princes and princesses who had potential would sign these Eternal Contracts on their behalf. It was not difficult for promising geniuses with aristocratic statuses to become Level Six Professionals in the future.

Moreover, the Deladia Empire truly possessed an abundance of princes and princesses on their side. There were a few hundred of them at least. The geniuses that were selected from this group of people did not fall too short. However, realistically they would not be valued highly in their own country despite their aristocratic statuses because there was a surplus of them.

Hence, their positions would be greatly secured if they could find a powerful White Dragon to sign a contract with them.

Thus, this activity was quickly launched in the Dragon Clan. However, it was only limited to Adult White Dragons because they were currently the ones that could form into the greatest powers and forces within the shortest amount of time. Humans could not spare a few decades waiting for Young Dragons to become adults. As for Dragon Whelps, that was simply impossible.

Therefore, this transformation would not affect Garen greatly.

He continued training in his own cave. His Draconic Aura had finally reached Level Five after being upgraded by his Potential Points. After training himself painstakingly and consuming all of his last ten Potential Points that he had accumulated, it was beyond his expectations that he only reach the Level Five stage.

Draconic Auras that were only at Level Five or below had to be stimulated by certain specialized realms before they could be upgraded. That was only one of its fundamental changes. It was similar to all the other professions as there seemed to be only one dividing line before Level Six could be achieved.

Another change that he had discovered was that his body’s attributes had finally exhibited certain phenomena which meant that his Potential Points needed to be increased.

He would previously require one Potential Point every time he wanted to increase one attribute. However, it had directly jumped to needing three points now. Now that his body had undergone a single change, it seemed that his previous Potential Points were not as effective anymore.

After all, Garen’s current Attributes had already surpassed fifteen points on average by now. He belonged to the standard domain of Level Seven creatures.

Since the standard of a regular Adult White Dragon was between thirty to forty points, he had already greatly surpassed the normal standard now.

According to Garen’s secret observations, the strongest Warrior named Phosphorus and the five Ice Dragon Guards who were his subordinates were perhaps the only ones who possessed characteristics that were stronger than Garen among the entire White Dragon Clan. He could not seem to see the limits of Phosphorus’ power, but he knew that he had achieved the Level Nine standard at least. It was naturally impossible for him to lack great power as a Warrior who dared to directly confront Third Elder who was a Level Ten existence.

If the Elder was considered as the strongest source of combat power within the entire clan with the presence of the Divine Staff, Phosphorus and his Ice Dragon Guards were the strongest forms of support and strength in the clan. Phosphorus grasped the military power in the palm of his hand completely while all of the Dragon Guards and the training of the Teenage Class were arranged by him.

Garen received an invitation after training in the cave for a short while. It was an invitation from Third Elder.

Third Elder’s grandson had given him some face and released Boris and Leona the last time. Therefore, he needed to pay a return visit no matter what this time as an indication of gratitude.

After all, this was an extremely brutal political struggle. It was highly likely that Garen would not eliminate someone completely as he did not want to ruin his attachments towards the clan.

Garen tidied up briefly and brought a few little gifts which were the Crystal Cores of the Giant Frost Iguanas that he had brought back when he left to hunt. He had yet to finish absorbing them completely and left a few for future use. It was a good time to use them now.

It was a good opportunity for him to give them out as little presents now.

Garen left the cave immediately and followed the Dragon Guards that had arrived before flying towards the highest point of the Elder’s Peak.

A white ice palace was being built there now without him knowing. Numerous human and dwarf craftsmen were currently hard at work up there. White Dragons would fly around the area occasionally to protect it.

These people were not surprised when they saw Garen and the two other dragons flying over. They had clearly arrived here some time ago and had already gotten used to it much earlier.

They flew along the side of the palace toward the back before quickly descending in front of the entrance of a large cave where numerous frozen water stalagmites had formed. These sharp frozen water stalagmites enveloped the main door that led to the cave. All of these pointed stalagmites were as dangerous as sharp thorns that were aimed precisely at the entrance of the cave. They seemed like sharp swords that were suspended above the head of every creature that entered in order to deter them.

“Please enter. The Elder is waiting for you inside,” said The Dragon Guard to Garen softly.

Garen nodded and drew his wings before taking long strides toward the inside of the cave and walking there.

Bang, bang, bang.

The deep noise of his footsteps could be heard when he stomped on the cave floor, yet he left no traces behind. Since numerous White Dragons had already threaded on this ground countless times, it was already extremely solid to a terrifying degree.

There were two Dragon Guards who were keeping watch on both sides within every hundred meters. When they saw Garen entering, these Dragon Guards awakened from their dazed states and merely glanced at him indifferently before collecting their thoughts and resuming their rest. They were clearly here to rest while keeping guard.

Powerful billowing Draconic Auras permeated throughout the interior of this entire cave endlessly.

Garen encountered five consecutive Dragon Guards along the way. Their Draconic Auras were ranked at Level Six at least. The thing that secretly shocked him was that the powers of Third Elder’s subordinates were clearly not weakened simply because the strength of the other two Elders had diminished.

The pure white cave that was tinged with light blue extended all the way towards a distance of a few kilometers. Garen only saw Third Elder who was currently talking to a human in a section within the cave where a skylight was located.

Sunlight cascaded through the skylight and formed a light pillar that coincidentally fell on Third Elder’s aged dragon scales. It gave him a few additional white halos, making him appear slightly younger.

Meanwhile, the person to whom he was currently speaking was around one hundred and eighty centimeters tall and considered to be average among the humans. However, the gold cloak on his body was draped over a dark gold full-body armor that he wore underneath, while a powerful sword that was embedded with colorless crystals hung at his waist. The circular crown on his head that was embedded with gold gemstones was the most eye-catching aspect of him.

The gazes of that man and Third Elder shifted over simultaneously and fell on Garen just as he had entered.

Whoosh whoosh!

It seemed like two consecutive fiery lasers had landed on his skin. Garen could only feel his entire body tremble violently before his ears were fully deafened instantly. His ears were then filled with a humming noise that sounded like the buzzing after thunder. Subtle internal wounds appeared within his body immediately.

The Draconic Aura throughout his entire body was released hurriedly. He covered his body in a defensive force field while his Draconic Aura increased from Level Three to Level Four to barely nullify the terrifyingly intense pressure that was brought on by the gazes of those two individuals.

His mind understood suddenly that he had chosen an inappropriate time to enter. Third Elder and this king were clearly exerting pressure on each other as a more convenient way to exhibit their powers as bargaining chips for negotiations. The frightening strength of these two Level Nine powerhouses had instantly landed on his body the moment he entered. Thus, this was the main reason why he had nearly vomited blood.

“Is that Garen?” Third Elder withdrew his pressure first.

Meanwhile, the other man smiled faintly and withdrew his Coercion as well. It seemed as though he had transformed from a prehistoric beast back into a regular middle-aged man.

There was a little black goatee below his chin while his short black hair made him seem experienced and tidy. He looked grave and strict from head to toe. Moreover, he gave off a dignified, lofty, and unapproachable air even when he smiled.

“So, what do you think about reaching a deal now about the matters that we were discussing, King Thunderclap?” Third Elder glanced at the king.

“Were you referring to this little White Dragon before me?” The King asked in a slightly pondering manner.

“Of course,” said Third Elder in a faintly proud voice, “as the most talented White Dragon in my clan, Garen will surely meet your requirements.”

“Requirements?” Garen’s eyes narrowed when he vaguely felt that the discussion between these two individuals was regarding him. “May I ask what you were going to tell me when you called me here, Elder?”

His mind felt somewhat uneasy when he thought of the news of the Eternal Contracts that were spreading like wildfire recently.

“I’ll need a period of time to observe,” said the King quietly. “You know that my choices include the Black Dragons and Red Dragons as well.”

“Your Majesty the honorable King Gus, Garen will definitely not disappoint you if you choose him. I believe that there are but a few prodigies in the other Dragon Clans that can rival Garen.”

“However, you must understand that Black Dragons are naturally immune to all spells below Level Seven while their hand-to-hand combat skills are stronger than White Dragon Whelps of the same age. Meanwhile, the magic abilities of Adult Purple Dragons are equivalent to Level Seven Great Wizards. These are better choices in my opinion,” said Gus while smiling.

“But will the other Dragon Clans promise to sign Eternal Contracts with you?” Third Elder smiled.

Indeed, both of them understood that if the White Dragon Clan was not helplessly forced into a corner with seemingly nowhere to go, they would not choose to sign Eternal Contracts with humans with short lives and become the dependents of the Deladia Empire.

The entire White Dragon Clan had turned into the shame of the White Dragon Mountain merely because of this. After becoming the shame of the entire dragon race, they abandoned themselves and gave up their nobility and pride as creatures with longevity. They would be spurned by the rest of the dragon race in the future.

This was a heavy price to pay.

Therefore, Great Elder and Second Elder had objected to it all along. However, they had never expected that Third Elder would secretly collude with the top-rate human powerhouses to take action immediately and imprison the both of them under house arrest. Had they not possessed excessively strong powers and loyal troops, Third Elder would have probably killed them long ago.

The King smiled and shook his head while looking at Garen.

“There’s no rush now.” He needed to find someone who would be useful to him before he could sign this Eternal Contract. After all, they would live and die together. Hence, if the White Dragon here was too weak and was killed by someone else, wouldn’t he instantly die as well?

“You may continue your deliberation, then. As a Pinnacle, you should have a three-hundred-year lifespan at least. Moreover, members of the dragon race with stronger talents have longer lifespans. Therefore, they will be even more beneficial to you,” said Third Elder while continuing to recommend Garen.

Chapter 1286: Contract 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“I’ll consider it.” Gus nodded faintly. There was a brief whooshing noise before he actually disappeared.

The body that contained enormous strength forces earlier was actually just a projection!

Garen’s heart trembled slightly. He had already understood why these two individuals were talking about him.

A hint of dissatisfaction stirred in his heart immediately. He was not fully against the idea of being able to sign an Eternal Contract with a peak powerhouse. However, aside from merely rejecting it, he would become the peak existence sooner or later. Therefore, he was completely unconcerned with how this Eternal Contract could help upgrade him.

Moreover, this contract would require him to reduce his lifespan by half and give it to another person for no apparent reason!

Unhappiness arose in his heart faintly because Third Elder was deciding on his behalf.

“Garen, come here.” When Third Elder’s voice drifted over, Garen raised his head and saw that the Elder was looking at him attentively with a gentle gaze.

He lifted his legs and walked toward the front of the Elder slowly before standing on the spot where the other man was standing earlier.

“I have been summoned by the Elder. What are my instructions?” He asked in a slightly respectful tone.

Third Elder sized Garen up from head to toe. It seemed as though his powerful gaze could see through Garen.

“I’m sure that you must’ve overheard our conversation earlier?”

Garen hesitated for a moment before nodding his head soon after that.

“Yes, is it about the Eternal Contract?”

“It’s fine if you understand.” Third Elder turned around before taking a black, leather-covered book out of the enormous bookshelf behind him. These books were the size of bathtubs when they were opened by humans, but they were merely little books to the dragon race.

The whooshing noises of turning pages could be heard when he flipped the book open before the book skipped to a certain page in the middle automatically.

“King Gus is the strongest existence in the Deladia Empire. He’s also King Thunderclap who has grasped the Thunderclap ability. He’ll become a demigod if he advances to the next step. He’s wildly ambitious and hopes to find a member of the dragon race who will sign an Eternal Contract with him to extend his lifespan to its maximum limit. Since his selection choices span across all the dragon races, we’ve recommended you from our clan.”

Garen was silent.

“You must understand that King Thunderclap is truly the most supreme being. There are people who have surmised that his powers have already reached the peak of this physical world as he had achieved the Level Fifteen grade in theory. Once he has chosen you, your social status and powers will receive explosive increments,” said Third Elder in a tempting manner.

“Level Fifteen?” Garen was slightly shocked. “Didn’t you say that Level Nine was the highest peak?”

“Level Nine is the peak of the Professionals and that’s the end of the road for them. Only those who have finished walking on the path that is considered their own can continue moving forward. In theory, one only needs to break through Level Fifteen and achieve Level Sixteen before becoming a demigod. King Gus has almost reached the final step. However, his lifespan is nearly insufficient…” said Third Elder while smiling.

“Then what is the difference between Level Nine Professionals and the beings that have surpassed Level Nine?” Garen did not reply or state whether he agreed or not, instead another question was asked.

“Difference?” Third Elder pondered before answering properly, “There’s no great difference. The dividing line between Level Nine focuses on Spellcrafting. In reality, the difference between the corresponding levels spans across an extremely vast divide. Moreover, Level Nine Professionals have already reached the peak of all creatures. If their levels are upgraded again after that, their greatest power will be their Level Nine Spellcrafting grade. However, there are great differences between their usage limits, endurance, quantity, types, and strengthening abilities among other things.”

He flipped to another page of the book before he continued speaking.

“Take, for instance, a Level Nine individual who still needs to chant and can only use Level Nine Spellcrafting. Compare this with another person who has five Level Nine Spell Slots daily and can also exist promptly. Who do you think is stronger?”

“Understood…” Garen had roughly understood the difference. He continued staying silent.

“So what are your aspirations regarding the Eternal Contract?” asked Third Elder gently.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows. He was careful not to expose his emotions when he replied.

“If King Thunderclap is willing, I’m naturally indifferent. Good opportunities like these are hard to come by.” His opinion did not actually count because this plan was clearly something that Third Elder had seized determinedly. If he was not grateful for this, it would mean that he had failed to appreciate his kindness. When he was faced with a terrifying being that was comparable to a Level Ten individual, Garen did not even have the confidence that he could even succeed in escaping from his soul.

This was easily not just a grade.

After Level Six, there would be an enormous division every time one passed a level. It was equivalent to the differences between Spellcrafting powers.

“That’s good.” Third Elder smiled. The traces of the faintly menacing atmosphere lightened as well. “Study properly. I’ll inform you once we have more information about this matter.”

“Thank you very much, Elder.” Garen lowered his head. Third Elder was an Elder Dragon who had lived for at least thousands of years or even ten thousand years. He had a vast amount of experience and would certainly not be easily tricked by Garen. Therefore, he could not expose even the slightest bit of unwillingness.

“Good. You may return first, I’ll summon you if any matters arise. Also, please remember to prepare yourself. The battle on the border had started immediately, and you will be summoned soon. They’ve been preparing themselves all this time for this battle throughout the last ten years.”

“Understood.”

Garen put his presents down and turned to leave politely. Only then did he go down before proceeding to walk out of the cave.

“That’s right. Regarding the matter with Boris and the other dragon, if you were really displeased, I’ll tell Wylow to be mindful of himself,” said the Elder simply.

“Thank you very much, Elder!” Garen turned around and bowed again. He had received a satisfactory answer in the end.

Clearly, Third Elder was saying these things to him directly because he was giving Garen face by using his status and position to pay attention to such insignificant matters. He was making sure that Garen would be grateful.

Otherwise, he would never have minded these trivialities because of his honor as the Elder.

After retreating from the Elder’s cave, Garen passed through the corridor that was being protected by the Dragon Guards and discovered that these guards were Level Seven beings at least. As Adult White Dragons were usually Level Six beings, the Level Seven White Dragons here were clearly meticulously strengthened through cultivation.

After leaving the cave, he flapped his wings and flew from the entrance of the cave before charging downward along the edges of the snowy peak outside.

The Dragon Whelp Training Institute that he had previously attended was located at the middle level of this snowy peak. He heard a series of cold sneers just as he flew past this area.

“Beat him! Beat him up! I’ll take care of everything as long as you don’t beat him to death!” It was Wylow’s voice.

Garen looked over in the direction of the voice. He instantly saw that a few Dragon Whelps had currently surrounded another Dragon Whelp. They were punching and kicking him in the canyon where the Dragon Whelp combat training class was located. They would occasionally lash at him with their tails by using numerous merciless whipping-motions.

Wylow stood outside the circle and yelled insults.

Garen furrowed his eyebrows slightly and looked carefully at the Dragon Whelp that was being bullied before realizing that it was actually Boris.

The banging noises that came from the kicking and punching echoed over continuously, while the Dragon Whelps sneered and hit Boris violently.

Garen charged downwards immediately.

Bang!

He landed behind the group of Dragon Whelps firmly. He fell on the ground heavily, causing the snow to fly and scatter everywhere when it quaked.

His movements gained the attention of Wylow and the other Dragon Whelps instantly.

“It’s Garen, huh?” he said while forcing a smile. He felt slightly apprehensive when he saw that Garen was clearly taller and more muscular than him. However, his confidence was immediately restored when he quickly remembered his new status as a White Dragon who had already signed an Eternal Contract with a prince.

“What’s wrong? You thought of coming back to see everyone in the Dragon Whelp class suddenly?” he said while trying to stall.

“What are you doing?” said Garen coldly, “have you forgotten the things that I said previously?” After being repressed over at Third Elder’s place earlier, Wylow was a complete eyesore to him now.

“But we’re not doing anything? Haha, we’re just teaching Boris some combat techniques.” Wylow squinted his eyes and looked at Garen sideways. “Garen, there’s nothing here that concerns you. I’ve given you Leona, already so don’t be ungrateful.”

“Ungrateful?” sneered Garen. “For the Elder’s sake, I’ll give you three seconds to leave.”

Wylow was dumbfounded and felt as if he had misheard him. Did Garen actually dare to speak to him like this?

“Did you just… say that? Three seconds?”

“One.”

“Garen, do you really think that I’m afraid of you?”

Wylow’s expression darkened immediately. Numerous muscular Dragon Whelps moved towards Garen and surrounded him after being signaled by Wylow. The Dragon Guards who were patrolling the surrounding area flew over here when they noticed that something was amiss. They were clearly focused on guarding Wylow’s safety at all times. It looked like Third Elder was extremely favorable towards Wylow indeed.

“Two.”

However, none of this was enough to scare Garen. As Garen was someone who would probably sign a contract with King Thunderclap, even Third Elder would have to consider Garen’s attitude towards himself in the event that the contract was successful in the future. When that time came, he would probably become a key existence that could influence King Thunderclap’s attitude.

Wylow was unaware of this, but he was already certain that since he had signed an Eternal Contract with a prince from the Deladia Empire, Garen would surely not be brave enough to do anything to him!

Moreover, since there were numerous protectors in his surroundings, what was the worse that Garen could do besides hitting him?

“Garen, mind your own business!” Boris roared stubbornly despite being assaulted. “Who told you to worry about me?! Go away! Go!” One of his eyes was almost swollen to the point where he could not open it. There was a faint hint of worry in his gaze when he looked at Garen.

Bang bang!

Both of the patrolling Adult White Dragons landed behind Garen and encircled him.

“Garen, don’t act rashly. After all, Wylow is Third Elder’s closest grandson,” said a White Dragon softly.

Garen turned around and glanced at the two White Dragons. Next, he looked at Boris whose entire body was covered in wounds, almost crippled from the beatings. A hint of impatience flashed in his eyes.

“I’m warning you not to concern yourself with the matters here.”

His words that were tinged with menace instantly angered the two Adult White Dragons faintly. They had never expected that this prodigious White Dragon with a reputation that had spread far and wide would actually be so wild!

Despite being a prodigy, he was merely a Dragon Whelp. Nonetheless, he was apparently daring enough to threaten Adult White Dragons. This simply meant that he was unaware of the complexity of things!

The commotion here had attracted the attention of many other Dragon Whelps who were attending classes inside. A few Dragon Whelps ran out in succession, while one instructor who was among them walked out as well. It was actually a teacher who had taught Garen previously. He was about to stop this incident when he saw it but it was too late now.

“Garen, I gave you face last time,” said Wylow coldly. “I’ve heard that you have three more brothers and sisters, right? It looks like I have to take good care of them…”

“Three.” Garen spat out the final word.

The entire place turned silent at once.

The entire bodies of the two White Dragons stiffened while they glared closely at Garen. Two shrouds of Level Six Draconic Auras pressed down on Garen’s body instantly.

Garen circled his surroundings and scanned them.

Boom!

He exploded a large pile of snow suddenly before the length of his entire dragon body increased by several meters dramatically. The muscles throughout his whole body condensed frantically like surging water. Level Six Draconic Auras could not suppress him at all! Garen’s entire physique had instantly expanded by one whole degree.

Those two Adult White Dragons pounced at him fiercely and attempted to press Garen down. However, Garen pushed them away violently towards his left and right sides respectively the moment they touched him.

Bang! Bang! Both of the Adult White Dragons were instantly sent flying by him with just two movements as though they were just pieces of trash before crashing against the frozen wall on the side painfully.

Bang!

Garen used one claw to grab Wylow who was dazed with fear. He grabbed at his neck and suspended him in mid-air.

He was almost as enormous as a full Adult White Dragon after his entire body had expanded, while the scales that covered his body were twinkling with a cold pale sheen.

Shh!

A scorching hot ray was shot out from the hands of one of the Dragon Guards on the side. It was clear that another Dragon Guard who had rushed over was taking action now.

“Put him down! Garen!”

Chapter 1287: Underground City 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The Dragon Guards’ rays were released at astonishing high temperatures, rapidly melting the ice and snow nearby within a radius of several meters. However, upon landing on the side of Garen’s waist, the rays were quietly absorbed by his white scales.

Shh!!

All the Dragon Whelps and onlookers gasped in shock.

This was Level Seven immunity!!

The Dragon Guard had immediately used a Level Seven Spell – Scorching Ray. It was a Level Seven Spell strengthened and derived from Level Four Scorching Radiation. Although it was initially a Level Four Spell, once its composition was revised and intensified, it could stir up the powers that were released by Weave, and as such was truly a Level Seven flaming ray!!

However, Garen seemed to be immune to it?!

He was actually immune to Level Seven Spells at this age??!!

It was really…

None of the Dragons knew how to assess Garen’s talents anymore.

Particularly the instructor who had recommended him in the beginning. Gaping with his mouth wide open, he was speechless as he was in a complete state of shock. His only thought was, oh man I’m so gonna get rich!…

The two Adult White Dragons that were whipped away crawled up slowly. Upon witnessing this scene, they broke out in cold sweat, too afraid to step forward.

When they saw Garen’s current physique and recalled the frightening strength that he had used to strike them, they realized that he had surpassed the normal White Dragons and they were not able to challenge him anymore.

Gradually, the red ray dimmed. Garen’s dragon scales only had bits of faint, black burn marks; the rest were not affected.

The Dragon Guard who was holding that scroll which was released earlier looked embarrassed. He looked at Garen dumbfoundedly, not knowing how to react as Garen grabbed Wylow by the neck. This may not be his strongest spell, but the powers of the other spells were not anymore greater than this. If this spell was not able to hurt Garen at all, the other spells could only hurt him to a limited degree as well.

“You’re really irritating.” Garen lifted little Wylow to his front, lowering his head to look at him closer.

“Kill me if you can!!” Wylow’s face was green from anger and fear. He was angry because he had been badly humiliated, and afraid because he did not expect Garen to be so fierce.

“Kill you?” Garen’s ferocious dragon mouth curled slightly at its corners, exposing his sharp, pearly white teeth.

His body’s Level Five Draconic Aura erupted fully. He had managed to offset a large part of the Draconic Auras weakening effects towards himself so that the value of his attributes would only decrease by one point on average.

Even so, his age was a concern to the surrounding members of the dragon race as they regarded him as a challenge that was hard to surpass despite everything.

“I won’t kill you, of course.” Garen drew back the corners of his mouth and grinned, “however, I can let you experience what is pain.”

He grabbed one of Wylow’s arms with his other claw while smiling menacingly.

“You…”

Shh!!

Ahh!!!

Amidst the violent, tearing noise, Wylow could be heard screaming in pain. He could only stare blankly at his right arm, which was literally ripped off. His flesh and muscle membranes were torn ragged, a large amount of white dragon blood spurted out.

Seeing this, the surrounding dragons felt intense chills surging from their tailbones up to their heads. Garen dared, he actually dared to rip off an arm of the Elder’s grandson?!

This was simply too brutal!! It was simply unimaginable! He was extremely audacious!!

“Enough!!”

A dragon’s ferocious roar echoed in the distance suddenly.

It was Third Elder!

His enormous, white body glided over swiftly, bringing with him a powerful and fearless Draconic Aura and using most of it to pressure Garen.

Garen turned around and flung Wylow away in passing. Wylow rolled on the ground a few times before he stopped, fainting from the pain.

He looked at Third Elder, who was flying towards him.

“Do you have any instructions? Elder?” His expression remained unchanged. Noticing that Garen could still remain calm despite causing such great ruckus, the surrounding members of the dragon race could not help but secretly admired him.

Third Elder was holding the Divine Staff, which emitted a ray of white light that shrouded Wylow who fainted on the side.

He only looked at Garen after that. Surprisingly, he merely furrowed his eyebrows gently and glanced at Boris, who was almost crippled by the beatings, and the other dragons surrounding Garen.

He remained quiet and did not say a word. He looked over at the other dragons around him numerous times before an Adult White Dragon approached him and explained the situation to him quietly.

Third Elder remained silent for ten whole minutes, the atmosphere was oppressively quiet.

His last gaze finally landed on Garen. The corners of his mouth drew back as Third Elder actually squeezed out an extremely natural-looking and gentle smile.

“It looks like I didn’t explain everything in time beforehand. Regarding my promise, it remains unchanged. But Garen, don’t you think that you’ve gone too far?”

“Elder, I was momentarily furious and could not help but acted rashly…” Garen suddenly understood that the Elder had already decided between him and Wylow. He immediately put on a helpless face tinged with some grievance.

He sensed that Third Elder’s gaze was scanning his body continuously. Third Elder was clearly extremely satisfied with the potential that Garen had displayed today.

“That’s true as well. Wylow had never experienced great obstacles since young. It was also beneficial for him to have you demonstrate to him the true definition of a powerhouse. Perhaps it will influence his future development positively.”

The Elder nodded casually.

“Alright, this incident ends here. Garen, regarding your matters, I’ll contact the other side as soon as possible. You can standby for more information. Don’t worry, you have a very great chance!”

Finishing his words, his gaze scanned Garen’s entire body from head to toe as if he was admiring an exceptional treasure. The longer he looked, the more satisfied he was.

“Thank you very much, Elder!” Garen replied with respect immediately.

Witnessing the conversation between the Elder and Garen, the other dragons looked as if they had seen aliens. They could not understand what had happened between the both of them that made the Elder ignored his favorite grandson’s critical injuries while openly favoring Garen instead!?

Boris hovered and stayed behind. Despite being the one who knew Third Elder’s personality the best, he was completely stupefied now. Third Elder, who had an extremely selfish and cold personality, had actually handled Garen so magnanimously even though the latter had challenged his dignity. This was more unbelievable than if White Dragon Mountain had instantly transformed into Black Dragon Mountain!!

Nonetheless, he could not deny it because the truth had happened right before his eyes.

However, none of the dragons knew that while Garen had breathed a sigh of relief, he was also secretly vigilant of Third Elder’s selfishness.

The true nature of White Dragons was that they were naturally selfish and cold, which could be vividly seen in Third Elder. If his own grandson was merely a bargaining chip that he could discard at any moment, outsiders would be worth even less.

He had already prepared in advance to display his powers in the clan. As long as he displayed his elite grade as an Adult White Dragon and leveraged on his age and talents, Wylow would be insignificant. In a clan where powerhouses were revered, no one would even dare to say anything if he killed Wylow.

However, it would be slightly risky depending on how much Third Elder valued familial attachments.

Therefore, Garen did not go to the extremes and merely tore off one of Wylow’s arms because broken limbs could be perfectly reattached within a short period of time by using Divine Art. His actions may seem brutal, but in reality, Wylow’s injuries would not be critical with the Elder’s help.

This was also a subtle action that he used to probe Third Elder.

The results, however, made him bitterly disappointed. Third Elder was indeed a ruthless character!

“These matters shall end here then.” Third Elder released white light from his staff while dragging Wylow up from the ground. He scanned through the area one last time before his gaze paused on the Adult Dragon Guard on the side, who was still holding the Level Seven scroll in his hand.

“You, come with me.”

That White Dragon’s body trembled before he frantically lowered his head respectfully.

“Yes.”

“Don’t disappoint me… Garen.” Third Elder looked at Garen one final time before turning around and flew away

Garen looked on while they left.

He stood at the same spot silently, his physique shrunk back to its original state again. He did not look any different from a normal Young Dragon. No one could have imagined that the tough atmosphere had actually burst forth from him.

He waited until the silhouettes of Third Elder and the other dragons had disappeared completely before he turned around and walked towards Boris.

“Are you alright?” He reached his hand out to support him.

“Still okay…” Boris struggled and tried to stand on his own but could not raise his body. “You shouldn’t have worried about me. Although Third Elder was smiling happily, he’s definitely harboring a grudge in his heart. Despite whatever methods you’re using to temporarily suppress his internal fury now, you will definitely face his worse retaliation the moment you make the slightest error.”

“Since doing this, I’d naturally know that these are the consequences of my actions. Don’t worry.” In his mind, Garen had a definite idea of what he was doing. “I’ll send you back to your cave first.”

“Thanks.”

“We were friends since the beginning, so you don’t have to say such things.”

Garen ignored the stares of the other dragons around him. He grabbed Boris and flapped both of his own wings before flying towards the snowy peak in the distance.

*******************

Shhh…

“That really hurts!!”

Inside a narrow little cave, Saszt was applying medicine on Boris’ wounds carefully. Leona, who was beside them, rushed over with the medicine from home.

This pitiful little girl was looking at Boris, worried.

Garen sat at the side and looked at Boris who was lying on the ground groaning.

“What are you guys planning to do now?”

“Plans? What other plans could we have?” It seemed as though Boris had matured greatly after experiencing the things that happened during this period of his life. “It’s impossible for us to leave this place because Third Elder would never release us. Thus, we can only live in the snowy peak. Due to this, we don’t stand a single chance of breaking free from his grasp.”

“I… I miss Grandfather…” Leona could not help but started crying again. Her delicate narrow dragon eyes were recently always slightly swollen. She was clearly crying often every day. The dragon scales that covered her body which was initially clean and beautiful now appeared somewhat dirty. There were obviously no specialists to help her clean them anymore.

Bang!

Saszt punched the cave wall.

“Wait for me to grow up! Wait for me to grow up! I’ll definitely put on a good show for that bastard!!” He gritted his teeth.

Garen looked at these three Dragon Whelps helplessly.

“Frankly, you cannot leave this snowy peak nor can you escape from the Elder’s supervision. If this persists, it will be completely meaningless even if you grow up. If you don’t leave the snowy peak and experience other things, you’ll never be able to grow and achieve the same Level Nine grade as the Elder.”

“Level Nine… Haha, the regular dragon race like ourselves could never even dream of reaching Level Nine in the beginning without seven or eight thousand years of intensive studying. However, there are only a few members of the dragon race who can live over seven or eight thousand years. There are the rarest beings in the dragon race.” Boris was realistic and calm. He glanced at Garen and said, “it might be possible for you but the rest of us aren’t prodigies. If we can’t break through to Level Seven by the time we reach five hundred years of age and are unable to extend our lifespans, it will be eternally impossible for us to even hope of achieving Level Nine.”

“Perhaps there’s a way that will allow us to break free from Elder’s control,” said Garen quietly.

“What way?!” Boris was suddenly shocked. His gaze was closely fixed on Garen.

Saszt and Leona were also surprised. They looked at Garen immediately. They were at a complete loss now and could not even see a sliver of hope.

“Eternal Contract,” said Garen lightly.

“Are you talking about the Eternal Contracts that are signed with the princes and princesses of the Deladia Empire?” Boris responded immediately.

“Once you’ve gained the protected statuses of the royal Contractors, you won’t merely be members of the White Dragon Clan as you’ll gain half of the status of the royalty of the Deladia Empire. Even Third Elder wouldn’t be brave enough to suppress your growth openly,” Garen explained briefly.

“But… our lifespans will be reduced by half!” Saszt was slightly hesitant.

“You can consider it, but this is the only way. Only by borrowing the strength of the Deladia Empire will you stand a chance of obtaining normal space for growth.” Garen stood up, “I’ll be leaving first. You can look for Safour and the rest and tell them to inform me if any matters arise. I might have to leave for a period of time so you need to be careful during this period.”

“Leave?”

“Yes, there’s a Summoned Battle…” Garen sensed the Summoner’s request in his mind. According to the contract, as long as the other party had provided sufficient remuneration, he could never reject their requests.

Garen’s heart stirred as he flew out of the cave. Translucent wavy ripples had suddenly extended in mid-air outside the cave at an unknown moment. Garen’s slender body charged through the ripples directly before he vanished without a trace.

This was his first Summoned Battle and he hoped that Kevin would not disappoint him.

Chapter 1288: Underground City 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the lush green, white pine forest on the border of Deladia.

The scorching, crackling flames of a great fire were currently burning in an explosive blaze. The red light soared into the sky while numerous red Giant Hawks hovered around.

Several black-skinned elves with pointed ears rode on the backs of these Giant Hawks. They held bows and arrows, and lances that were used for throwing while glaring menacingly at the area where the large fires were burning below. Dozens of red hawks circled and formed an enormous red whirlpool.

There was apparently a faint green semicircular shield that was currently being supported in the center of the great fire. Five or six people were standing scattered under the shield, they were dressed in Deladia Empire’s military uniforms. Three of them were Wizards. There were either three or four stars on their black wizard robes which indicated their ranks as either Level Three or Level Four Wizards.

Kevin and his daughter Maria huddled together closely. The shield was released by him.

“Never would I have expected that we would be captured by the Giant Hawk Elf Forces after we had just encountered our third battle…” There was a slightly pained look on Kevin’s face.

There were two Warriors and an Archer in this group. There was a total of six people here including the father and daughter duo who were both Level Four Wizards. They formed a standard match.

This was a battle group that was formed by the dragon race Contractor Kevin to obtain the Core. When they came out to proceed with their border hunt this time, they had never anticipated finishing their luck from the two previous times. They had encountered a large contingent of Giant Hawk Elf Forces this round. With the ability to fly at high altitudes and throw burning or exploding-type weapons and arrows, these Black Elves were the nightmares of all Wizards that were Level Five and below.

“Father, the captain of the group of Black Elves in the sky seems like he has silver stripes. He’s definitely a high leveled existence. If we kill him and take him back as proof, we’ll meet our quest quota for the next two months.” Unlike Kevin’s currently pained state of mind, his daughter Maria was brimming with confidence.

“My lord and lady, I have terrible news! Another two groups that are being led by Contractors have arrived. They’ve surely noticed the commotion here!” reported the only archer who was concurrently holding another post as a scout loudly.

“We must get to work immediately, or they’ll definitely steal the credit!” Maria urged her father.

“Don’t worry, we’re just slightly inexperienced.” Kevin exhaled firmly. The arrival of friendly forces would be the best-case scenario. Otherwise, it was uncertain whether he could get rid of the Giant Hawk Forces in the sky if he could not accurately grasp the little White Dragon that he had summoned.

“But…”

Roar!!

Suddenly, a long and muscular Young Blue Dragon flew over from the faraway sky. The cerulean Blue Dragon had smooth dragon scales while the length of its body was five to six whole meters long.

“Haha, the captain of the Black Elves with Silver-Striped one as well. My luck is actually pretty good today.”

“Houston, I discovered him first so don’t even dare of stealing my credit!”

Another Red Dragon with an even bigger physique flew over in the sky. Shrouds of red halos were lingering around this Red Dragon’s whole body. It was apparently a prodigious Red Dragon that naturally possessed scorching radiation.

“Mark, do you really think that your Contractor can win a fight against us?” It seemed that the Blue Dragon was unexpectedly not afraid of the other party. “Although I can’t beat you, I can still stall you temporarily. However, you Contractor is another story… haha.”

Both members of the dragon race surrounded the Black Elves in mid-air. However, they were not rushing to put their hands to the task but were arguing with each other instead.

Maria and the others below paced in circles frantically, unaware that Kevin had mentally sighed in relief vigorously.

They saw that another Young White Dragon was about to appear in the sky quickly before Kevin secretly cut off the connection of his contract passage while the faint light of his Contract Matrix extinguished itself on the ground naturally.

“Let’s go. There’s none of our business here anymore,” said Kevin softly.

“Father, you’ve acted too slowly. Otherwise, this credit would have been ours definitely,” grumbled Maria.

“It’s fine, we’ll find another place…”

Hum!

Suddenly, a deep distinct voice echoed throughout the minds of all the dragon race Contractors here.

“All Contractors, head towards the message transmission site immediately and gather there. All Contractors, head towards the message transmission site immediately and gather there. The location of the unique Underground City has been discovered, and the Pearl of the Hall may be hidden there. You must definitely fight to obtain it.”

The voice repeated itself in their heads three consecutive times.

“Pearl of the Hall…” Kevin’s mind stirred. The revolving core of the Black Streak Empire’s Underground City — Pearl of the Hall had numerous mystical effects.

Its most renown effect was its ability to improve aptitudes and forcibly modify souls to increase the probability of breakthroughs for numerous Professionals who were unable to break through their limits.

The Pearl of the Hall’s most valuable aspect was that it was a first-rate treasure that could sufficiently increase the probability of breaking through to Level Eight when it was used.

Furthermore, the Underground City was also the predecessor of the Black Streak Empire and the remains of the Black Elf Empire, hence there would definitely be an abundance of rare treasures inside it. Moreover, the Black Elf Empire was an infamously greedy empire that possessed a myriad of treasure and wealth.

“Must we go?” Kevin knew in his heart that he had no other choice. This question was undoubtedly insignificant. Military orders could not be defied and his misdemeanors would definitely be recorded if he did not go. Since he was currently wearing his badge now, there was no leeway for him to struggle at all. He was worried that the little White Dragon that he had contracted was not even at Level Five… if he rushed in like this, would it really be alright?

Unlike his fearful and dispirited self, Maria and the few other Warriors were enthusiastic now after Kevin had relayed this information to them.

“Underground City, huh. Although we certainly won’t be able to obtain the Pearl of the Temple, there is an abundance of treasures there. As long as we can get a few random antiques or good items, we will definitely earn a lot of money if we sell them!”

Maria was very knowledgeable and knew many rumors regarding the Underground City.

Wizards belonged to a profession that included huge expenditures. They only had the right to upgrade their own levels without having to consider about wastages or depletion once they had a sufficient amount of money.

“Let’s go then…” Kevin glanced at the few members of the dragon race in the sky one last time. The few dragons that arrived after that had already started to slaughter the large contingents of Black Elves that were escaping in the sky. Seeing the power and ferocity of these dragons that belonged to other people, he lost even more confidence in his own contracted dragon.

His dragon was already a member of the weakest White Dragon Clan. Moreover, he was also a Dragon Whelp… The average Dragon Whelps were mostly only at Level Four.

The surrounding flames weakened when Maria used her staff to release a Hydropower Spell. This Level Three Spell induced a small amount of rainwater that fully drenched the surrounding areas that were covered in flames earlier before the high temperatures were lowered by the water vapor immediately.

Kevin chanted a few sentences quietly and waved his hand to release a Level One Squall Spell that blew the water vapor away.

The group then rushed speedily towards the direction that Kevin was pointing at.

******************

White Dragon Clan Elder’s Peak

A shroud of ripples had instantly appeared in mid-air in the cave where Garen stayed. Garen charged out of the ripples in one go and appeared disorderly from head to toe.

“Damn Kevin!!” he cursed loudly and furiously. His expression was extremely contorted.

He was passing through space when the summoning of his contract was abruptly severed on the other side. This caused him to frenziedly crash head-first into the Spatial Barrier that had closed in front of him. Next, he rolled around and was dragged back like a tractor while being inflicted with vertigo along the way.

The inexperienced, useless Wizard over there was actually unaware that one-sidedly ending a contract without prior information would cause the Contractor on the other side to be seriously injured at any time because they could not react promptly?!!

If he had neither possessed exceptionally agile reflexes or qualities that were incomparable and far beyond that of the average Young Dragon, he would probably be completely and heavily wounded because of this. Regardless of one’s level, the slightest problem when passing through a space portal would surely be a major issue.

When he landed in his own clean ice cave, Garen panted hoarsely in an extremely indignant manner. He saw that his entire body was covered in dark blue bruises. These injuries were formed when he crashed around in the space passage. He was extremely furious.

“Don’t even think that I’ll put in any effort for you the next time you summon me!” Garen was furious. He was initially already impatient with that penniless good-for-nothing Summoner. He had never expected that the other party would actually still dare to pull this move.

He already had thoughts of instantly severing contact with him if he did not have to wait for the contract time to arrive as he could only be relieved after the battle ended.

*******************

Several days later…

At the edge of an enormous underground abyss on the border of Deladia.

More than ten battle units had gathered in a temporary campsite at the border.

The campsite was arranged in a circle while transparent floating Sentinel Eyes were installed in its surroundings. These were guarding devices that were created by the Wizards which could be repeatedly used for ten times.

More than ten units had their own large tents in the campsite. Hints of black patterns that were deeply engraved could be faintly seen on the edges of the largest tent.

Every single person at the campsite was currently standing outside their tents, while more than ten units of dragon race Contractors were all looking at a man in blue armor who was standing at a high place.

The man’s features were as beautiful as a woman while his short blue hair was raised up high like a blaze of fire. His body was slender and tall, and he wore exquisite dark gold crescent-shaped studded earrings on both of his ears.

The man crossed his arms at his chest and looked down from above at all of the other dragon race Contractors below him. He gave off an agile and brave but arrogant attitude.

“I’m Blue Void Reisman. I’ve temporarily gathered all of the nearby Contractors here. In the name of the royal family, I shall be the highest in command here. Honorable lords and ladies, are there any objections?” He said in a low and deep voice.

“No objections. If Master Blue Void is leading the group, I think that we won’t have to worry about any danger,” said a white and grey-haired elderly Wizard softly as he stepped forward. Although he had spoken quietly, his voice was amplified by his spells to the extent that it resounded through their surroundings.

“I don’t think that there’ll be any issues if we’re led by Master Blue Void of the White Knights who has been renowned for a long period of time,” agreed another voice.

“Rumor has it that Master Blue Void is about to advance to Level Seven. Being able to reach this stage at twenty-six years of age is worthy of…” the voice trailed off.

A middle-aged female Wizard stood forward.

“I was wondering if Master had a deeper understanding of the Underground City? Our sixteen Contractors here have gathered the strength of sixteen members of the dragon race. It’s unlikely that it will be dangerous in there. However, obtaining the greatest benefits and snatching them from those Black Ghosts will depend on the leadership strategies.”

Blue Void’s expression remained unchanged.

“I have a map relevant to the Underground City, and I’ve also prepared some methods to counter and get rid of some sections of certain organizations. I only need the assistance of your honorable selves in certain places to help me conserve strength in those areas.”

Kevin and his daughter were standing in their own unit while looking at Blue Void who was on the platform far away.

“Level Seven at twenty-six years old… Truly amazing.”

“It doesn’t matter because I won’t lose to him!” said Maria softly.

However, Kevin knew the difficulty of wanting to break through Level Four. For humans, breaking through Level Four meant crossing a threshold of qualitative changes. Even though numerous people had advanced to Level Four when they were only ten years of age or older, there are also those who were delayed at Level Five for over an entire decade and were still around. Moreover, they would need to exhaust even more resources, time, and energy when they reached Level Six after that, and almost a few times worth as well. Results such as achieving Level Seven at twenty-six years of age was an impossible stage to accomplish for the average Professional and even prodigy who did not possess the great forces, resources, and priceless support that the royals received.

Chapter 1289: Knowledge 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

“If nobody has any other objections, we can leave now,” Blue Void said loudly from the front.

There were no sounds from below, indicating that everyone was pleased and satisfied with his arrangements. Blue Void then started dividing everyone into several groups and the respective tasks each group would be in charge with.

As protected ones, all the Contractors were surrounded in the middle. After all, their safety was directly linked to the existence of the summoned dragon race.

As a Wizard, even if it was a Level Nine Great Wizard, without any special physical attributes or equipment or casting a spell shield upon oneself, even a Level One Warrior could easily kill him. However, once the Wizards were well prepared, the power they could erupt would be way horrifying than an entire troop of Warriors.

Therefore, the safety of the Wizards was at the top of their list.

After everything was settled, the groups slowly walked out of the camp site. Warriors were scattered everywhere whereas Archers were at the inner layer with the Wizards and Contractors right in the middle.

Kevin was the one who stayed in the innermost, grouped together with a Contractor and a Level-Four Wizard whereas his daughter, due to special relationships, was arranged to be by his side.

The team slowly descended along a small stone ladder at the edge of the abyss, and soon disappeared into the darkness of the abyss.

*******************

The mysterious snow mountain.

The pure white snow mountain and the azure lake were calm and peaceful, yet seemed remorselessly dead without any living creatures.

There was no sun over the blue lake, only white clouds that floated slowly but there was still a white light that was shining upon the surface below.

Whoosh!

A gigantic White Dragon glided across the lake, causing large ripples and waves.

The White Dragon had a slender snake neck and strong and powerful limbs, its slightly blue-ish wings on its back fluttered gently as if it had a weird yet natural frequency. It was well coordinated and natural.

Roar…

The White Dragon growled slowly as it darted in the direction of the snow mountain.

The instant it closed in the snow mountain, the White Dragon once again rushed and entered a translucent whirlpool, vanishing into thin air.

“You’re here?”

Everything went black, Garen suddenly felt that he had fallen directly into the bottom of the abyss.

The translucent light source was right in front of him, shimmering in a faint white light as Ann’s voice could be heard from inside.

“I came to fulfill the agreement.” Garen realized that he was standing in front of the light source, his mind calmed down.

“It seems that you’re still trustworthy, and punctual,” Ann spoke lightly, “my experiments are divided into two categories. The first one is the Soul Toxic Test. Please come with me.”

“?”

Garen did not understand how he was supposed to follow her. Ann’s presence was clearly locked within the light source.

But very quickly, he soon understood what Ann meant.

Poof.

A beautiful lady wearing a black tunic skirt walked out slowly from the light source. Her hair was silky smooth and her skin even delicate than the best jade.

This was a perfect lady.

This was Garen’s first thought when he saw Ann for the very first time. She was so perfect she did not even seem humane.

This kind of perfection was not just the perfection of Heaven and Earth, but the kind of perfection that no flaws could be found. Whether it was her temperament or her body, she was completely flawless in all aspects.

“Come with me,” the clear manly voice that came out from Ann’s mouth instantly destroyed her perfect temperament.

Seeing that she just made a turn into the side of the mountain wall, Garen quickly followed.

As the both of them walked towards the mountain wall slowly, Ann explained in a hushed tone.

“Don’t be surprised by my abnormality,” she glanced at Garen’s confused face. “Every hundred years, I’ll switch genders and voices. For this coming hundred years, I’ll have the body of a woman and the voice of a man. Then the next hundred years, the body of a man and the voice of a woman.”

“Uh…” Garen was a little speechless. It was still alright if Ann had the body of a woman and the voice of a man. If he just happened to meet Ann in the body of a man with the voice of a woman… that would be extremely hard for him to adjust to…

“Also, I’m not as what you think, sealed in this place.” Ann turned back and walked towards the stone wall. She reached out her hand and pressed on it lightly.

An arch door slowly and silently appeared on the stone wall, in the middle of the black door were two scarlet red bloodshot eyes.

Click.

The door opened, and Ann walked in.

Garen quickly followed.

Inside was a pitch black hollow space without a trace of light. But with the body of a White Dragon, Garen was born with the talent of Darkvision. Coupled with the faint, white light that was coming from the outside, he could vaguely make clear of his surroundings here.

A laboratory.

This was no doubt a laboratory.

Some unknown blood-stained creatures were bound onto the white experimental platform and in the corner were some wheat-like rings with blue, electric current flashing from time to time.

There were a lot of small grooves on one side of the wall with red candles placed in it. There were probably more than hundreds of them.

Swoosh.

All the hundred over red candles suddenly lit up and a bright yellow flame instantly illuminated the entire cave.

Ann walked to a corner where a lot of garbage and utensils were placed and searched around, finding a very sophisticated looking silver-white metal machine.

“Come here.”

She waved at Garen.

Garen hurried over. Although he did not know what she was up to actually, he did agree to cooperate with her experiment and so naturally, he had to keep his promise.

“Drink it.” Ann opened the silver-white metal machine. Inside the elliptical machine was a Light Ball full of tentacles. She held it up and passed it to Garen.

“Drink?”

Garen accepted the Light Ball, how do I drink this? He was stunned.

“Try to imagine, and use your Soul to touch it,” Ann explained.

Garen composed himself and looked at it. It did not seem harmful and his Soul Ring was not sending out any warning or whatsoever, so it should be alright…

He thought so in his mind.

His Soul Energy reached out and touched the object.

Swoosh!

The white ball of light vanished instantly as it seemed to have disappeared underneath the skin of Garen’s arm.

Before Garen could even react, he felt a cold and intense aura that emerged in his soul rushing straight for his Soul Ring.

Before it could reach his Soul Ring, boom!

The white ball of light exploded and a mass of green paste splattered all over the place, even the Soul Ring.

Garen suddenly felt a strong sense of nausea stirring up in his stomach. He had a strong urge to puke.

“This is…?”

“Do you feel anything?” Ann looked at him curiously, “This is my latest Soul Explosive Potion. It’s able to separate the parts on Alien Soul that is not pure enough.”

“I…” Garen felt more and more uncomfortable. His stomach felt as if there were a thousand roundworms wriggling around and the discomfort was unimaginable.

His body tensed up and he fell onto the ground. Wriggling on the ground, he bit his mouth shut. He had a feeling that once he gave in the urge to puke, his Soul might suffer an unimaginable harm.

“This potion lasts for two days so, in these two days, I’ll give you a lesson on the basic general knowledge of this world. Oh… It’s not that kind of general knowledge, but the more high-end part,” Ann said casually. “This shall serve as my reward to you for cooperating with this experiment.”

Garen was not able to speak anymore, he could only listen. He resisted the immense urge to vomit and listened to Ann’s words quietly.

Ann led Garen to a room’s door. The room appeared abruptly on the mountain wall as if she just used a chalk to draw out a door. With a push, one could enter the room.

Garen was then placed inside the room by Ann. The room was filled with books, bookshelves, and piles of books.

In the middle of the large heap of books was a gray-yellow translucent map that was floating in the air.

“This is the Main Plane. I don’t know where did you come from but,” Ann paused as she sat down before the translucent map that was floating.

“No matter what time or space it is in the Main Substance Plane, this will always be the core.”

At this moment, Garen felt slightly better and less nauseous.

“Core? So, it is the center of everything?” He asked reluctantly.

“Almost… every year, tens of thousands of creatures from different worlds wander into the Main Substance Plane and they’re always caught by researchers to be used for various experiments. These researchers, some are Great Arcanists, some are Holy Spirits. Some are scholars of the Abyss, but most of them are Gods.”

“Human Gods, Elf Gods, Dwarf Gods etc., there are many Gods in the Main Substance Plane and just an average God’s power is able to build up a small God so there were plenty branches of Gods, small and big. For example, the Great Human God, the symbiont of Light and Fire, the Almighty Fehra.”

“So we can call for the Gods here?” Garen was somewhat surprised. It was known that Fehra was the strongest God of the Human Gods and the most powerful God. Even calling out for a God in the isolated face was very likely to be discovered so after a period of time, Fehra could pay close attention to the situation here straight away without disguise.

“Yes,” Ann nodded. “I’ve made some preventive measures so no matter which God you call out to, it won’t be a problem.”

Garen understood and did not ask anymore but in his mind, he was starting to guess Ann’s identity.

Ann pointed to the floating transparent map.

“I’ve already helped you solve your body and soul coordination, but your soul is still far stronger than your body. This is unusual itself so no matter how you coordinate, you can’t cover this up. A strong soul that is formed naturally is always recorded down by the Gods hence,” Ann cast a glance towards Garen, “you still have to pay attention to some creatures, they can still see through your essence.”

“Oh?” Garen looked as if he was listening carefully.

“First of all, all the demigods, or other higher existences.” Ann came before a bookshelf where a book flew out automatically, floating right before her. It then began flipping the pages itself.

Soon enough, another book flew out automatically and floated beside her as it started flipping through the pages itself as well.

“Second, the Holy Spirits. They have a sense of divinity and most of the powerful Holy Spirits are even stronger than demigods,” Ann’s delicate index finger pressed onto a page in the book.

“And thirdly, the scholars and thanes of the Abyss. As long as they have divinity or they’re so powerful to a certain level of existence, they can notice your problem.”

“Then… when can I settle this once and for all?” Garen asked in a low voice.

“It’s very simple. Once your body is strong enough to be worthy of your soul, by then, you’ll have a perfectly coordinated existence,” Ann smiled. “Your talent seems to be extremely powerful but in reality, your body has a limit in the plane. The soul does not affect the limits of the body, that’s the iron law, that’s why no matter how strong a warrior is, he must truly understand divinity in order to break through the limits of his strength. But Wizards are different, they can choose to understand divinity or continue to study Arcane Techniques.”

Garen did not refute. The most special aspect of the Mother Stream System was that a soul could influence as well as determine the limits of the physical body. But for Ann, perhaps she had already taken that into consideration.

In his heart, Ann had become an omnipotent know-it-all.

“Some of the stronger existences of the Main Substance Plane lived on land, the Heavens, the Chaos Sea, the stars, the great kingdoms, the bottomless abyss and the purgatory. These are all places you have to pay close attention to. Once your soul enters these places, those existences that have a strong sense of smell toward souls would instantly find you. And once you’re captured, you’ll be destroyed.”

Ann explained slowly. From time to time, she would look at Garen with a weird stare. Her eyes glimmered with gold, silver, and even a little like a crystal-like Milky Way vortex. Her gaze upon Garen was as cold as the tip of a knife, cutting Garen to the point his scales ached.

But this was obviously part of the experiment, and so he could only bear with it.

“Really strange though, there are parts of your soul that I can’t understand,” Ann fondled her chin as she muttered, “It seems that the potion’s effect is running out… continue to drink.”

Just like performing magic, she pulled out another white mass of light that was full of tentacles.

Chapter 1290: Knowledge 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen received it conscientiously and continued absorbing it. Once again, the immense nauseous feeling re-emerged.

He could barely hold the urge to bend over and vomit but immediately resisted it again.

“Such strong willpower. Very persistent,” Ann nodded with satisfaction. “You are now qualified to become a Holy Spirit. If you are pious enough, that is.”

“Thank you… for the compliment…” Garen squeezed out the words. His entire body was shivering and coated with cold sweat as he crouched on the ground, too afraid to move as he feared he would vomit. He felt an excruciating pain in his abdomen as strong surges to puke washed over him.

Ann stared at Garen in awe.

“Your soul’s strength has dropped slightly. Seems like this soul toxin really does have a debilitating effect. Maybe it’s because your resistance is relatively high, that’s why I thought it wasn’t working at first…”

She bent her head seemingly in deep thought.

At the same time, the floating books around her would flip its pages occasionally. Text and symbols would appear from thin air, so obviously, she was recording notes.

As time passed by slowly, Garen finally got through the potion’s effect. He was so exhausted that he almost fell asleep.

Right then, Ann’s raitensed her head once more.

“Cooperate with me and do a set of movements. Your spirit should be coordinated.” Upon finishing her words, she began a set of dance-like movements that almost seemed like an awkward social dance, but there were also some weirdly difficult postures.

Garen did not know how he was supposed to keep up with her. He had the body of a dragon. But since Ann said so already, he used his four limbs as arms and legs and started moving slowly.

With just one move, he instantly heard a cracking sound from his Soul Ring followed by the sight of crack lines, causing his heart to jump.

“Don’t worry.”

Ann waved her arm and everything around them suddenly stopped.

Swoosh…

Garen’s movements began to move around in a rigid and automatic way as if time was moving in reverse. He repeated the movements in reverse, from the last part to the first part, until he fell back to the ground just as if he had never started.

Garen stared and the cracks on his Soul Ring instantly disappeared!

“This… is the power of time…!” This was not the first time he had encountered such a power. The last time his Soul Ring ruptured, it was this surge of energy that rescued him, and this time, again.

Everything was back to normal.

Garen was able to move once again.

“You must constantly practice this set of movements with this toxin. After one year, I’ll be back to see your results. Understand?” Ann asked calmly.

“Understand,” Garen replied conscientiously.

Seeing that he was so cooperative, Ann seemed to realize that her trading principles were not really met.

She pondered for a while.

“Why not this, I’ll mark a set of maps of the plane for you, indicating all the places that you shouldn’t get close to and I’ll send you a set of books. You can choose freely here.”

“Thank you very much,” Garen responded eagerly. What a joke. Being able to control time, an existence like Ann should have reached a certain terrifying extent. The knowledge accumulated by such a powerful existence was no doubt hard to find in the majority of other places!

What Garen yearned most was the overall understanding of this entire universe. He just simply had no clue what he should pay attention to in this world.

This was naturally the time not to be courteous.

He braced the nauseous feeling and quickly scanned the bookshelves around him.

Spellcraft books were all written in different languages that could not be understood at all. Moreover, they were clearly locked by mana and it would be impossible to read them if one was not a certain level or did not understand the decryption method.

Potion books, he was not fond of using potions so this was a book he was unfamiliar with.

Garen’s gaze soon landed on the History books.

The History of the Main Plane.

This book was just perfect for him.

“Are you done selecting?” Ann could sense that he had come to a decision. The book automatically flew out of the shelf and landed right before Garen.

“Thank you.”

“This book is really suitable for you, so you can adapt more easily,” Ann nodded in agreement with his selection. “Go now.”

She waved her hand and Garen could feel everything spinning. His whole field of vision turned upside down and together with the books, they disappeared from the study room immediately.

Ann fondled her chin. All the books around her closed together slowly and flew back to the shelves automatically.

“There’s actually something I can’t resolve. God of Potions is indeed worthy of praise,” she mumbled to herself.

She held out her index finger and drew a stroke in the air. In a flash, a crack appeared in front of her and Ann stepped inside it.

It was unsure what was on the other side of the crack, only white rolling hills could be seen below. The sky was blue and golden sunshine shimmered as Ann floated midair. Suddenly, her body expanded tremendously and rushed forward.

Roar!

Her body expanded and she transformed into a gigantic, ferocious black dragon.

The black dragon was almost a few hundred meters long and she looked just like a black battleship. She had three horns on the top of her head which had colorless current arcs flashing around them.

Hu…!

The Black Dragon’s enormous body suddenly disappeared on the spot and when it reappeared, it was already a couple of kilometers away.

The huge Black Dragon flew over the mountains, across the ocean, through a gold desert, and in just half an hour, she finally arrived at a black plain.

“Pasala.” Ann’s loud voice spread toward below, causing large groups of animals that looked like ants from above to panic and flee in fright. Some of the weaker ones were even scared to the point they peed or paralyzed on the ground, not even dare to move.

“Ann?”

A thick female voice rumbled from below, young yet majestic.

“Aren’t you still in meditation? Showing up so casually like that, the Shadow of Ampsey will not let you off that easily.”

Ann’s huge black dragon face showed a look of disdain.

“I’m meditating, not escaping. Do you really think that I’m afraid of him?”

“Alright, I believe that you don’t fear him. So why are you here?” Pasala’s female voice asked.

“I’ve discovered a way to improve my physique’s existence through talent,” Ann said shortly.

“So what? No matter how strong a body gets, when it faces the distortion of time-space, a Level-Nine spell can throw it right into the abyss of the sea of worms and you’d be completely devoured to death by the endless worms. Not understanding the laws, a stronger body doesn’t mean anything at all,” Pasala said truthfully.

“Of course I know that, but I’m just only interested in this kind of abilities. He was created by the God of Potion’s first accident,” Ann responded mindlessly.

“The God of Potions?” Pasala hesitated, “now this is something worth studying. So what do you want coming over here?”

“Give me a Death Crystal,” Ann said bluntly.

“No. I have only secreted this much over a hundred years, what’d I do if you take all of it away?” Pasala rejected immediately.

“Let’s trade then,” Ann said with a low tone. Pieces of her black dragon scales started falling off her gigantic body automatically and flew downward.

The dragon scales that were a meter long spun quickly and just like a falling meteor with flames, it crashed into the plains.

Boom!!!

A deep crater appeared on the ground. However, the ground surrounding it started wriggling like a living creature around the crater, and soon filled the hole up.

At this sight, a smile crept upon Ann’s face.

*******************

In the cave.

Garen quietly lingered in his own cave and right in front of him was the book about the history of the Main Plane.

Pages and pages of the book flipped slowly. The pages were not just symbols and text that he could not understand anymore, but in a twisted unexplainable way, the Information Stream could still be conveyed into Garen’s brain in distinct symbols.

This was quite similar to a Wizard’s reading technique, but slightly more advanced than that because this type of Information Stream was all automatically converted into Draconic Language and Garen only understood Draconic Language.

“Ninety-five thousand and three hundred years ago, three Supreme Gods suddenly rose up in the Main Plane and they were Fehra the God of Light and Fire, Ellafy the Mother of Nature, and Avon the Dragon of Eternity. After the invasion of the abyss, the Purgatory and Main Plane overlapped and war broke out… Demons and Inferno creatures trampled over the land of the Main Plane, the sky was shrouded in flames and poisonous gas, evil spirits bewitched the people and killing desires swept upon all beings.”

The content of the book flowed through Garen’s mind slowly.

“Human and all intelligent races were faced with a major crisis and so the three Supreme Gods each chose the heroes of the war and gave them divinity to become Gods. However, some of those who accidentally acquire the lives of the evil from the abyss had confused the boundaries of the war. The abyss has been raging for thousands of years and has finally been driven off…”

Garen read the pieces of history carefully.

“After the Battle of the Abyss, this book recorded the Battle of the Gods. The Dragon of Eternity and the two other Gods had a conflict and after being defeated by the two Supreme Gods, he disappeared. As for the God of Elves’ Mother of Nature, after helping Fehra the God of Light and Fire, they turned against each other. The Elves lost but Fehra suffered an immense loss as well. With that, they signed the Republican Treaty.”

He skimmed through most of the parts of the praise and proud descriptions of the Gods and skipped to the important parts straight away. But then, he found something strange.

After the Battle of the Abyss and the Battle of the Gods, there were still new Gods, demigods, and heroes that popped out constantly. According to his dragon race’s inherited memories, Garen realized that with those many Gods who had fallen in battle, the Main Plane was still showing faint signs of prosperity.

He suppressed this doubt but he failed to find any answers in the book. Theoretically, even if the war was victorious, there would usually be ‘ ten thousands deaths of the enemy and eight thousand deaths of one own ^1 ‘ but there was no sign of this here.

With a general understanding of the Main Plane’s history, Garen analyzed the entire world’s geographical environment through the book.

Numerous planes rose and fell, surrounded by a cosmic ocean called the Chaos Sea. Among all the planes, there were the main three that stood absolutely upon the Main Plane.

The positions of those three planes from the top to bottom were:

The highest one on top was the Heavens, which was the main land of peace for the kingdom started by the all the Gods. Most of the kingdoms were connected, creating network branches between the Gods in order to cooperate and defeat the loss of the Chaos Sea. It was heard that the three Supreme Gods were the founder fathers.

The middle one was the Main Substance Plane, which was where humans lived.

Right below at the bottom was the endless abyss.

As for the Purgatory Plane, the Shadow Plane, the Main Elements Plane, the Ether Plane, and so on, were all attached in between three of the Main Planes. There were also many other strong Planes that were privately established and those were attached to the edges, and those other planes that were chaotic and messy were too many to enumerate like fishes in the sea. Nobody would ever know how many planes were there exactly.

But Garen only roughly knew as much, he would have to find a more detailed geographical plan to analyze carefully next time.

Chapter 1291: Survival 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

To be able to obtain such detailed information from Ann had already exceeded his expectations.

There was a lot of content recorded, even the dragon race inherited memory was not as detailed as this. Garen planned to bring back more goodies the next time he goes over.

Heavens, the Main Plane, and the Abyss.

The names of the three places flashed into his mind. This was the most fundamental core of this universe.

It was unknown how big exactly was the Main Substance Plane, it was like a gigantic sphere. He recalled the scene he saw when he just arrived, everything on the plane was yellow-brown. It was unclear what those cotton wool-like objects were, just that they were attached to the surface of the Main Substance Plane.

“Too bad this book’s not about the plane’s geography…” He shook his head and closed the book completely.

The main purpose of him coming here was to find the root of the Depletion of Mother Stream, but until now, he still had no clue.

Instead, he witnessed the absolute power of the strong ones here. The laws and restrictions here were at least able to suppress their strength by several levels.

His peak strength, while he was in Mech World, was on Planetary Level which was able to destroy planets, but here, Planetary Level was so suppressed to a completely horrifying extent. From what was mightily recorded in the books, it was approximately equivalent to a demigod level here. Even if he restored his various abilities at his peak, it was still impossible for him to destroy an entire planet, but destructing the plane was still possible.

Garen squatted inside the cave. The small range of White Dragon Clan no longer limited his vision, and so he projected his sight to other places far away.

After reviewing his current situation, Garen was extremely satisfied with the progress of his body growth.

Although the improvement of attributes has been raised to the requirement of three potential points in order to improve a little bit, he still managed to reach a whopping sixty points. This level of flesh was almost the highest level even for an Adult Dragon, and almost close to the apex of a White Dragon.

The most powerful warrior of the White Dragon race, the Adult Dragon Phosphorus, if other external forces were not included, was probably not able to surpass this level. Only his other aspects were above him, causing his flesh to exceed this certain level.

There was no doubt that Phosphorus’ Draconic Aura was definitely a Level Nine.

Garen then remembered the King Gus incident. He did not want to just simply conclude an Eternal Contract with King Gus just like that. It would be hard to determine whether this kind of relationship built on without trust would be a good thing or a bad thing in the future.

“Garen! Garen!!” Suddenly, Safour’s voice came from outside.

“What is it?”

Garen stood up and Safour came running in.

“Leona, Leona they just signed the Eternal Contract with the Deladia royals!!” Safour exclaimed frantically, “hurry, let’s go see! Many dragons have left already.” He was not aware of the discussion between Garen and Leona and rushed over with a look of incomprehensible shock.

It should be known that an Eternal Contract meant that one would give up half of his life to an ordinary mortal!

For example, if an ordinary person was to live up to eighty years old, let him give half of his life away to another dead person, he would then only live up to forty years old. To pass away at a time of one’s prime was no doubt a big deal for any White Dragons.

“Let’s go.”

Garen was not surprised, he just did not expect them to act so quickly.

He followed Safour and flew out the cave. They crossed a small snowy peak and they could see the snowy ground below, ten or so White Dragons were gathered together. Some were Adult Dragons, some were Young Dragons, but most of them were Young Whelps and a few young people dressed in royal assembles.

Garen and Safour landed and spotted Leona and Boris among the crowd. Both dragons had a look of determination, clearly, they had already thought through this beforehand.

Upon seeing Garen’s arrival, both dragons nodded slightly to him and continued standing beside two young people. One of the young people was a male and the other, a female. Their looks seemed beautifully crafted and they looked extremely tender and cute, but the guards around them were merely Level-Three ordinary elites. It was obvious that they were not the most valued ones in the royal family.

Several Adult Dragons had their mouths closed, but there was a subtle soundwave transmission in the air. Evidently, they were using a spell similar to ventriloquism and were currently communicating with Boris and Leona.

Garen recognized one of the Adult Dragons to be Leona’s father who was a weak White Dragon. When his daughter was bullied, he shrank into the crowd and did not dare to come out. Facing his strong and determined daughter now, he still had a sad look on his face.

Leona’s sister, Mehsa, was present as well. Standing on one side quietly, her expression was down and upset.

As for Boris, his uncle, an ordinary White Dragon, was there with a cool expression.

“Seems like you’re already sure about this no matter what I say.”

“Yes.”

Boris nodded.

“Alright then,” His uncle said indifferently. Back then when Boris was bullied, he did not step out and help either. The dragons who really cared about Boris and Leona were already arrested along with the Great Elders.

The rest of them were not exactly close to them and their relationship was weak.

Garen stood by the side and looked for a while. He did not squeeze in and greet the both of them. This was their own decision. Third Elder could only rely on such means to temporarily resist it.

“Come on, let’s go back,” Garen shook his head. Knowing that the situation had been set, Leona and Boris might soon leave them and who knew if they would ever meet each other again. They had to follow the Contractors back to the Deladia Empire to live. For them, this was just a place of sorrow, perhaps one day when they return with sufficient powers, they would be able to avenge their ancestors and save them from being arrested. But that day was too far away.

“But…!?” Safour wanted to say something but then realized that Garen had already flown off.

Garen was not worried that those two guys would get into trouble, even Third Elder did not see that those two tots would create problems or whatsoever. Level Nine was not just easily achieved by any dragon, what more, a wasted one that had lost half of its life.

Sure enough, not long after returning to the cave, Garen heard the news of Boris and Leona leaving with the group back to the Deladia Empire. A total of five White Dragons of the entire White Dragon Clan had signed an Eternal Contract, two of which were them.

With two fewer acquaintances, Garen’s life was even duller.

Safour, Sathree, and Satwo were always nowhere to be seen. If they were not participating in hunting activities, they were playing around with the Young Whelps. Soon, they forgot about the separation and the feeling of sadness that came with it. After all, they were still kids.

Garen sat still in the cave and meditated.

He had plenty of experience in martial arts but he had not been able to make full use of it. In addition to the understanding of the various laws of several worlds, after transmigrating between so many worlds, he had his own understanding of the laws of the world.

He gradually understood some limitations and unknowns clearly, he began to recall all the systems he had been in contact with so far.

Secret Technique system, Totem Light, Witches and the power of Blood Breed, Holy Phoenix Scriptures, and the strongest of all, Mech World’s Willpower system and Energy Machinist’s system.

“Even though this world is extremely repressive, its degree of inclusiveness is very strong. All these systems are usable, but some of the powerful forces are suppressed several levels below the original level. This way, the only things that can be used in all ways are the Secret Technique system and the Energy Machinist system.”

“Willpower requires a variety of techniques of a Mech, and this will not work. Many of the materials here are different from those there and to rebuild the study of materials would be very troublesome and it’d take too much time. The Totem Light mainly has the power of evolving and degrading and finding the most powerful part of a creature’s gene fragment. But this is considered as a knowledge system, and it’s very likely that once leaked, it’ll attract plenty of attention. If possible, it just shouldn’t be used. So, what remains is the Witches and the power of Blood Breed which is mainly a technique used for Dream Weaving through dimensional worlds. I’m still not very clear about this and it feels very vast, perhaps I can try using it some other time.”

Garen sorted out all the powers he had witnessed and listened to them one by one to see which ones were helpful to him now.

Now that his body had reached a certain level of change, it needed to be upgraded. That would take a lot of time and his strength was probably unable to be greatly enhanced in just a short period of time. Therefore, he had to think of another way.

“My Energy Machinist Willpower needs to be practiced again and it’s not urgent at the moment but my Void Confinement Essence can be activated by the power of dreams. Let’s see if I can make use of it here.”

Void Creatures and Warlocks were all masters of controlling dreams. Garen had never understood that, but now that his Soul Ring had really reached the Middle Demon Lord Level, he could faintly sense that the concept of dreams had slightly surpassed the essence of time-space. It was just a very weird yet mysterious existence.

Even though the restrictions here were wide, a weak trace of Soul Energy was not even able to escape the body. His understanding of the Void Confinement Essence was probably not applicable to foreign objects right away. However, it may be different if he was in a dream.

Garen pondered for a moment and looked at his accumulate potential points.

‘Safive — Strength 57, agility 57, physique 50, intelligence 19. Potential points 723%. Soul Limit 170, Level Five Draconic Aura. Level One Arcane Art Basics.’

His intelligence had only improved a little all this time whereas his potential points were only left with seven points. His Draconic Aura had reached Level Five, meanwhile, his Arcane Art Basics was still a mere Level One as he did not put much effort in it and he just did not have the interest of improving it at the moment. This combat force was taking too much time.

“Seven points attributes… it should be enough. To quickly recover to your peak strength, it’s worth the try,” Garen remembered the Wizard’s way of practice. Slowly crouching down on the ground with his eyes closed, Garen slowly drifted to sleep.

If Void Creatures were born with the ability to control dreams, then Warlocks and Witches were post-natal and they had to practice to acquire this ability.

Garen’s soul belonged to the Demon Lord so naturally, controlling dreams was as simple as drinking water.

He quickly fell asleep in a minute.

Ever since he came to this world, this was the very first time he had a dream, the others were just simply a rest.

After his brain blurred for a bit, Garen suddenly found himself floating in the sky above a barren land. He no longer had the body of a White Dragon and Garen’s human face and body was floating in the sky.

Above him, gray clouds loomed the sky and besides that, nothing could be seen anymore except the gray-brownish piece of wasted land with centipede-like tracks scattered all over the ground. There were no trees, there were no lives, just dead silence.

“This is strange, why would I dream about a place like this?” Garen muttered and began to look for something weird about the dream.

A dream was divided into several levels. The first level of dreams was the retrospective and illusion influenced by the biological instinct memory but most often, dreams of this level had some hidden meanings.

When the living body was in a state of sleep, they were able to receive clearer information and capabilities than in the awake state. Under normal circumstances, they were able to discover other worlds that ordinary creatures could not perceive.

Dark Energy and the Dark Substance World were just a part of it. Under such circumstances, the creatures could only come into contact with beings that were inaccessible under a blur state and they would able to sense different mysterious symbols as well.

As for those signals, they would all turn into stimuli and be reflected in the dream. Due to the brain’s lack of ability to think, they would turn into illogical parts of a dream.

Chapter 1292: Survival 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Dreams could reflect all stimulation of an organism, both spiritually and physically. This was a special state amplified by an organism’s Sensing Ability.

Therefore, dreams often reflect reality. For example, if one’s stomach was pressed in an uncomfortable way, one would dream of being kicked at the stomach. Even dreaming about finding a toilet to pee or something along the lines was the stimulation of one’s body presented in a dream.

There were big dream stimulations, and naturally, there were the small ones.

Garen soon found what was wrong with this dream.

He held his finger in the air.

“How can there be paper scraps flying at such a high altitude?” A white piece of scrap gently dropped on his finger.

He smiled softly, and the paper scrap instantly enlarged into an endless white slate that wrapped him up.

Everything around him turned white straight away, it was a blank white space. Opposite Garen stood a white swan dressed in a gentleman’s costume. Standing upright like a human, it was wearing a black high-top hat and was motionless just like a sculpture. A wind from God-knows-where was blowing gently, ruffling its white feathers.

Garen frowned slightly.

He had been on this layer once when he was back in Mech World.

“This should be the second level,” he muttered.

Mr. White Swan did not move at all as if it did not notice him.

Garen made his way over and circled the white swan that was still like a statue.

His purpose of entering the dream was to test out whether his Confinement Essence was usable. Other than that, he wanted to check out the differences between this world’s dream and the previous worlds’.

But from the looks of it now, this world’s dream was not much different from the other worlds.

Gurgle gurgle…

Suddenly, a rumbling sound of wheels could be heard from a distance.

Garen turned around and saw a brown snail that was almost a meter tall slowly moving toward himself.

The snail’s shell slowly moved to his front and stopped. The sorrowful face of a man peeped out from the shell’s mouth.

“It’s been a long time since I’ve seen a new buddy.”

Garen raised his eyebrow.

“You are?”

“I’m His Majesty, Indo Demon Lord’s Thirteenth Demon General,” the man said. “Seems like you have also discovered this world here.”

“What do you mean?” Garen was stunned for a bit as his brows scrunched up even tighter.

“This is the second level. There are plenty of gaps between time-space and dimensional conscience. It’s not very quiet here so we need a safer place,” the snail man whispered.

“Follow me.” Garen turned and looked at the swan gentleman behind him. He reached out and lifted the hat and suddenly, he shrunk and entered from the bottom of the hat.

The snail man followed suit and swiftly entered as well. The hat was then once again held up by the swan gentleman as he proceeded to place it back on his head. Then, he resumed his original posture.

The third level of dreams.

Viscous liquid-like colored lights were flowing all around them.

Garen and the snail man floated right in the middle.

“Alright, there’s definitely no interference here. This is a temporary space that I just built. Speak, since I’ve already entered by accident, I’m sure the other beings have realized this, no?”

He did not expect himself to encounter an existence who was also from Mother Stream system during the very first time he entered a dream, and it was still a general too.

He could faintly sense a thick conspiratorial aura.

The snail man squirmed as he settled into another posture and face Garen up front.

“Most respected Demon Lord Master, you’ve guessed it. We have indeed discovered this world for a long time.”

“Discovered this place for a long time?” Garen frowned.

“Yes…” The snail man’s already sorrowful expression got worse. “Because of Mother Stream’s depletion, we have been looking for the cause everywhere. In an accidental situation, a Demon Lord Master came to this world and unexpectedly survived. When we found this place, the timing was just chaotic.”

“What do you mean by chaotic?” Garen felt that something was wrong. Clearly, he had just received the news regarding the Depletion of Mother Stream.

“It means that the two Demon Generals that we’ve sent out later on did arrive safely, but then we found out that the two Demon Generals were seven hundred years apart!”

“Seven hundred years? You mean, both of them who came in at the same time actually landed at different times?” Garen understood this time.

“It’s like this. The time we enter this world is not fixed. I don’t know if it’s our problem or the world’s problem itself. We won’t know. May I ask you when did you enter this place?” The snail man looked at Garen with sincerity in his eyes.

“Me?” He was uncertain himself either. If time had changed randomly, who knew when did he actually reach this place.

“Talk about the situation when you just came,” he had some reservations towards the snail man.

“Yes, master.” The snail man began to talk about the series of happenings before he actually came.

The more Garen listened, the more stunned he got. He had already expected that the flow rate of time he encountered when he entered the Black Hole may have been abnormal, but he did not expect it to reach this extent of abnormality!!

Mother Stream was about to be completely depleted, all the branches were reducing rapidly. Many of the Void Creatures and the Warlock Powerhouses had nowhere to rely on and they could not see their paths ahead. True Souls finally appeared and together with the Void Demon Masters, they lifted the Mother Stream’s Oath, eliminate the enemy’s camp, and worked together to find out the root of Mother Stream’s Depletion.

Garen carefully asked about the situation that he knew of and the current status, and after comparing both stories, he discovered that two hundred years have passed since he left.

In other words, in the process of entering this world, he had wasted a total of two hundred years!

“… Mother Stream is withering more and more, lots of tyrannical beings are already getting ready to enter this world. But so far, only a dozen was able to stand firm here,” the snail man whispered. “The Gods of this world also noticed something was not right and began a wide screening.”

“Why? Why such a big move and enter this world?” Garen was still curious. “Did you guys discover something?”

“The source of Mother Stream is directly connected to this world.” The snail man forced a smile. “All the True Souls and Void Demon Masters had carefully observed that our world is positive, which means this world is negative. If we’re negative, then they’re positive. We’re two endless dimensions, like two ends of an hourglass. When one side has more sand, the other side would have lesser sand.”

“You’re saying that the Depletion of Mother Stream is caused by the absorption of this world over here?” Garen was shocked.

“The specific time is more than ninety thousand years ago. I don’t know what happened back in that era that started causing Mother Stream to slowly deplete. Up until we found out about it, most of the hourglass had leaked to this side already… we suspect that perhaps it’s because this other world is absorbing.”

Garen suddenly remembered something he had previously come across as he was reading up the history. Ninety thousand years ago, three Supreme Gods appeared in this world, and those three Gods were the three top powerhouses who just suddenly rose without warning.

If they saw it that way…

“The Supreme Void Demon Master once said that this is the Battle of Survival. There is no compromise and we have no choice,” the snail man revealed a face of sadness.

“The Battle of Survival…” Garen’s heart sank. This war was not like before, how he was able to transmigrate to another universe if he died. This was an actual Battle of Survival that life and death actually mattered.

“Only if the number of strong enough powerhouses who die here was enough and we grab them and convert them into nutrients, then only can we turn the hourglass around. Mother Stream will be able to rejuvenate…”

“No wonder… no wonder those Gods would die without hesitation even when they haven’t started fighting, all Alien Souls weren’t exempted…” Garen recalled the scene some time ago in which he was almost killed.

The Void Creatures and Warlocks actually united… this was something he did not expect at all, but this also really proved that the entire Mother Stream was facing a moment of life and death.

“Then why did you come and look for me?!” From that moment, Garen’s stare toward the snail man immediately became fierce. In the third layer of dreams, one could only rely on the nature of one’s soul to communicate. No holding back, no lies, and no deception. That was because beings below the Demon Lord Level could only rely on their core subconscious to communicate, and the subconscious would never deceive.

“It seems like you’ve already established a foothold here, I hope you can start a massacre as soon as possible. The more True Souls that die in our hands, the more likely we’re able to save Mother Stream.”

The snail man said in a hushed tone.

“Also, is it alright for me to disclose your location?”

“You’re still able to keep contact with other existences?” Garen raised his brow.

“Yes… I’ve given up on all my powers and strength, only being able to survive in a dream. My only role is acting as the messenger to convey messages,” the snail man explained.

“How many beings were there the last time they entered and of what mechanism?” After pondering for a while, Garen asked.

“Fifteen Middle Demon Lords, twenty one Lower Demon Lords, seven thousand and above Demon Generals, a large number of Willpower Void Creatures and even the lowest leveled ones were in the group as well. The number’s probably at least tens of millions,” the snail man answered softly. “But they were scattered around so they landed at different planes of this world, not really many planes either. Although the Willpower Void Creatures were strong, being wisdomless was only put in as a cover to enter. As for the Main Substance Plane, I know there were two of them who survived, and you are the third one. The others are all in different planes.”

“So what’s intercepting us?” After hearing such a huge number but only so much survived, Garen’s heart skipped a beat. There were fifteen Middle Demon Lords, which meant that there were fifteen beings who were at his same level.

“Gods… all of the Gods!”

Garen went silent. He remembered the ceremony he had seen earlier and the few beings who were detected, perhaps they were also forced to land.

Unfortunately, to the Demon Lords, they had a long period of growth ahead of them after they arrive. Although short, it was still the period where they were the weakest. Once discovered by any of the Gods, they would face death.

So what about Ann? Garen suddenly thought of Ann. She knew he was an Alien Soul, so why did she still save him?

Chapter 1293: Probe and Patrol 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The white stairs, the tall and sharp cathedral exuded a soft, gentle white light. From far away, it looked just like an ordinary cathedral. Apart from being slightly more magnificent, there was nothing peculiar about it. But if compared to the surrounding objects, then only was the horror of the cathedral revealed.

Nearby, a huge white airship that was carrying at least a few hundred people was slowly flying towards the cathedral. This airship that was almost a thousand meters big was just like a small fish, slowly coming in through a small hole above the cathedral and soon disappeared.

From far, small spots that resembled specks of dust under the sun could still be vaguely seen walking out of the cathedral door. They were actually Divine Officers dressed in white robes!

Small gray dots were densely packed on the stairs and they squirmed like water tides as they moved upwards.

Dressed in gray robes, these people took one step and one bow as part of their prayers. Slowly but surely, they gradually made their way toward the cathedral on the mountain peak that was shimmering in prayer light.

Blood splatters were scattered all over the stairs, but it all slowly absorbed into the white-jade material and disappeared, restoring the stairs to its original white innocent texture.

From time to time, two bright angels with long swords appeared by the sides of the stairs. On the left were angels with white wings, while on the right were angels with black wings. Together, they maintained the order of the crowd.

“This is the Main Plane’s center empire. This is Fehra’s Cathedral, which is also known as the Temple of Light and Fire. It is ten thousand meters tall, standing like a huge mountain right in the middle of the entire empire.”

Far away in midair, a large white airship was slowly flying towards Fehra’s Cathedral.

Visitors that seemed to be there for the first time gathered together in the airship as they listened to the tour guide introducing the place.

“Fehra’s Cathedral is surrounded by dozens of urban villages of different sizes and they all form the safety region sheltered by the Light and Fire Church. It is said that Fehra’s Cathedral was once built on a gigantic crater, and that is why this place is also known as Meteor City.” The tour guide had five, white tentacle-like limbs that were dangling about like soft noodles. The other features were no different from a human other than its arm.

“Praise Gloria, this is really a cathedral?!” A mermaid exclaimed, her hand covering her small mouth as her lower body was soaked in water-like mist.

“It’s even bigger than the average mountain… really, it’s so straight and tall!!”

“The power of Fehra’s Light and Fire is infinite, and this is only one of such miracles,” a traveler exclaimed. “I’m been here once thirty years ago, also for a trip. At that time, there were still many Sky Temple Knights patrolling around the sky. But now, even the Sky Knights are no longer wanted anymore.”

“Nobody dares to challenge Fehra’s authority, even light and fire burns and ignites in the endless abyss,” a devoted traveler said softly.

“Even the most powerful army formed by the entire Holy Spirit group, Sky Knights, who are stronger than the group known as the strongest, Golden Knights, are only just a little something compared to Fehra’s authority,” the tour guide praised.

“Praise Fehra,” all of them suddenly bent their heads and pressed their right palm on their heart. Calling the name of the Gods would actually attract the Gods so nobody dared to be disrespectful.

“Such a magnificent cathedral… really amazing…” Suddenly, a woman’s voice rose lightly from the back of the crowd. “Unfortunately…today, such a great miracle will be completely destroyed…”

“You…!” The tour guide and the group of tourists, as well as the passengers around, were stunned as they stared open-mouthed at the lady who just spoke. At a place where Fehra’s Holy Aura was shrouded, someone actually dared to say this!! Did she want to die!?? No, this was already not a question of life. Committing blasphemy at such a sacred place, that would cause one’s soul to burn for a thousand years by the Holy Fire!!

“Catch this psychopath!” A priest on the airship shouted.

“Up! Left, right, together!” The Church Soldiers stationed around quickly reacted and rushed toward the woman as they pulled out their swords.

The one who spoke was a lady dressed in a black shirt and skirt. Her face was beautiful and she had delicate skin. From the looks of it, she resembled more of a rich lady.

But what was most eye-catching was the little boy who was holding on to her left hand. The boy had one finger in his mouth, and he was sucking on the finger hard. Both of them looked like an ordinary lady and child, traveling and dressed wealthily.

The lady smiled gently and suddenly, a black mist started spreading everywhere and instantly covered the soldiers.

“A blasphemer!!” The surrounding Church Soldiers immediately pounced on both of them. As they shouted the Holy name of Fehra, white flames ignited on their bodies and all of them attacked the two from all directions.

The woman’s bright blond hair floated in the wind and she suddenly smiled.

“Agale, go… go destroy everything that you see…”

She let go of the little boy gently and pushed him forward.

“Can I eat everything, mommy?” The little boy took two steps forward and turned around with a vile smile.

“Of course…” the woman grinned. Her small cherry-like mouth seemed to be torn apart all of a sudden, both corners of her lips reached her ears. A scarlet red tongue popped out between her blood-red lips.

Suddenly, the little boy rushed forward.

Oh…!!!

His body expanded in an instant and his clothes were ripped apart exposing the black skin underneath. His whole body expanded as if it was a balloon being blown as it grew bigger and wider!!

In a blink of an eye, the body had already flown out into the air and transformed into a terrifying giant with had over thousands of arms.

Roar!!

He growled. The size of this giant was almost several times bigger than the whole Fehra’s Cathedral. His skin was a dark shade of black and the most conspicuous part was his abdomen where there was a gigantic black door engraved with many symbols and patterns.

If someone could identify the meaning of those words, they would know the creature’s true identity and origin.

On the airship, all the creatures exploded from the roar. Mists of blood slowly dissipated in the air. Traces of translucent thread-like objects flew out from where the creatures died and entered the mouth of the lady who was the only one left standing.

She once again showed a faint smile.

“Thousand-Armed Giant Agale, unleash all your powers completely…”

Roar!!!

Agale waved his thousand arms and grabbed the top of Fehra’s Cathedral.

Immediately, the entire cathedral reacted.

White light glinted and flames rose as the cathedral began to shake violently. Sings and praises of countless people rang at the same time, buzzing like the bees as they shook heavens and earth.

“Eternal Fehra! You are the judge of life and death, you are the one who shines light and warmth, you are the master of justice and ignition!!…”

Chants sounded and endless praises transformed into more white flower petals that descended from the sky, slowly falling onto Thousand-Armed Giant.

What was even more bizarre was that the worshippers on the stairs seemed to be completely unaffected. They were protected by the white light. Although they were frantic, they gave their all and sang, more devout than ever. There was no sign of them escaping in fright.

Roar!!

Agale screamed and flung out his thousand arms, both his feet trampled on thousands of worshippers.

But more white flower petals fluttered down. Suddenly, black-winged angels and white-winged angels flashed beside him and started attacking him with all their might.

But it was useless. Whether it was the petals or their attacks, nothing harmed the Thousand-Armed Giant. Even the angels were polluted by the dark splotches on the giant’s body and fell like dumplings.

“Combustion is eternal.” Suddenly, a man in a white robe with three eyes rose up from the cathedral. He only said one sentence.

Boom.

The multiple layers of clouds instantly spread out in the sky. The golden sun brightened countless times, and an immense golden light descended from the sky instantly weaving into a golden figure which darted in the direction of the man’s body.

He was suddenly lit up and his entire body was ignited with golden flames.

“It’s you again, you petty Alien Soul!!” Though there was no sight of him opening his mouth, a mighty voice sounded which rumbled the surroundings.

“Eat! Eat it all!” Agale did not understand what he meant. It was one of the strongest soul of Mother Stream, with a bottomless stomach and was the guardian of the Door of Dimensions. There was nothing it could not eat in the world!

At the sight of the golden flames, his face revealed an even more greedy expression. Both his arms grabbed the black doors on his abdomen at the same time and pulled it open.

Bang!

The doors opened roughly.

Whoosh!

Black magma-like substance spurted out from the doors and surged towards the cathedral and the figure burning in golden flames.

The black magma actually suppressed the projection of Fehra’s transformation that was arriving and wrapped the golden flames tightly.

In the midst of the buzzing sound, a large number of different creatures swarmed out of the doors like flood waters. Some were face-less black monsters, some had figures like squids, some were deformed grotesque creatures that were like demons. Pure elements that formed flames of life, water flow of life, and elements of the earth. Gigantic monsters like headless bodies swarmed out, almost a hundred thousands of them. They exploded in the air and scattered all over Fehra’s Cathedral like raindrops, dropping all over the ground.

The massacre had begun.

A mass number of angels also swarmed out of the cathedral, but their speed was far comparable to the speed of those swarming out of the black gates.

The monsters and angels fought against each other. These angels were the most loyal and powerful heroes turned from mortal elite warriors. Under the attack of these monsters, their supposedly undefeatable bodies actually showed symptoms of pain, weakness, and powerlessness. Their vitality no longer maintained at an eternal state but was rapidly consumed by those monsters.

A large number of worshippers were also slaughtered by the monsters. Some were able to resist but their number was too small, it did nothing to help.

“Heavenly Fire.”

All of a sudden, a troop of golden knights arrived from a distant in the air. They rode on white Unicorn Creatures and every member had a burning phantom floating behind them. That was a virtual silhouette that burnt in white flames.

All the knights yelled at the same time and golden flames suddenly flared up from their backs. All the virtual silhouettes suddenly boiled and formed an enormous golden figure in the air. The figure had no face, only a white whirlpool that constantly moved on its face. It had a pair of wings, one was black and the other white. It was only slightly smaller than the Thousand-Armed Giant. It then leaped forward and slammed a punch right into Thousand-Armed Giant.

Bang!!

The fist was blocked by one of Thousand-Armed Giant’s arm. Both behemoths shook at the same time.

Right then, Agale made a jaw-dropping move.

In the midst of everyone’s angry roars, he bowed his head and bit the peak of Fehra’s Cathedral — the statue of Fehra!

Chapter 1294: Probe and Patrol 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Ka-chak!

Countless cracks appeared and spread across the statue.

Boom!!

Rays of golden light pierced through the black mud and the hoard of monsters, and a golden figure shot into the air from the black tide.

Countless divine runes surrounded him like silk ribbons, floating around him. Many fresh flowers carvings, mountains and oceans, precious stones and metals– all of these scenes flashed past him at high speeds, as though he was being wrapped up in an endless translucent screen.

“Blasphemer!!”

There was a stern roar of fury.

Psst!! Roar!!

Golden flames seemed to envelop the person, and like a sword, both pierced into the Thousand-Armed Giant’s forehead at lightning speed.

Agare roared out in pain.

The golden flames on the surface of the silhouette abruptly formed a human face.

A white pillar of light fell from the sky abruptly, and amidst the ceaseless golden sunlight, the white pillar looked particularly conspicuous, just nicely covering the face made of golden flames.

All of a sudden, the human face turned around and faced the airship levitating in mid-air. This airship was very close to it, and yet it had, quite eerily, taken no damage whatsoever.

“Fehra… So this is the authority of the Three Great Major Gods? It’s truly impressive…” On the airship, a woman grinned and looked at the face of golden flames from afar.

“Then we’ll end it here for now…”

Swoosh.

She instantly vanished from the spot, as though she had never been there.

There was a barroom, and the airship simply exploded. Within a few blinks of the eye, it had turned into white ash that scattered and rain down.

***************************

On the lush green plains, there stood many giant white-grey stones that looked like Ganoderma* (TN: a precious and expensive fungus shaped like an upside-down umbrella known in traditional Chinese medicine for its powerful medicinal properties).

These stones were narrow at the bottom and thick at the top, and looked like so many grey-white ganodermic staffs* (TN: lingzhi ruyi, an ornament originating from a fancy backscratcher shaped like a Ganoderma herb), growing up from the ground.

The blurry grey rain continued to fall endlessly over the sky and the earth.

On one of these giant Ganoderma, several Young White Dragons flew down abreast and landed on the stone surface. Pulling back their wings, they all looked at the White Dragon at the front of the line in unison.

“We’ve arrived at the Jumo Plains.” The Young White Dragon at the helm looked at his surroundings through the curtain of rain. Since he was standing on a grey-white rock almost a thousand meters tall, he could clearly see into the far distance across the plains.

“Garen, this is our first time on a quest, so if we get caught in a battle, you have to be careful.” The young dragon leader turned around and looked at a white dragon in the team whose scales were much cleaner and brighter than the rest.

This wd seemed to be about the same size as the Young Dragons, but his dragon horns were just some very short stubble, so he was clearly still a Dragon Whelp. Yet, here he was, out on a quest with the Young Dragons. There was only one Dragon Whelp that powerful among the entire Deladia White Dragon Clan, and that was Garen.

Garen nodded calmly.

“Don’t worry, Gamu, I’m here to train, not to make mischief.”

It had been more than five years since the last time he received news from the Mother Stream.

To the dragons, a mere five years was equivalent to one human year, and they passed in the blink of an eye.

But to Garen, he had changed rather considerably in these past five years.

Five years. His growth rate had already been obviously abnormal, to the point that he could be resistant to Level Seven Spellcraft even though he was just a Dragon Whelp. Such a terrifying physical body was so much stronger than even Black Dragons of the same age and level. That was why, in order to attract less attention from the gods, he chose to temporarily store his Potential Points, and grew only according to what was natural of his body in the past five years. At the same time, he would occasionally use some of the Potential Points on his Draconic Aura and Arcane Art.

He had as many as three hundred Potential Points, and only used about a hundred on his Draconic Aura and Arcane Art, until he had reached the upgrade limit for his Draconic Aura and Arcane Art.

After Garen found an extremely hot place, he had quickly increased his Draconic Aura up to Level Seven, and then it refused to go any higher. The Potential Points needed to progress from Level Six to Level Seven also greatly exceeded the total number of points he had spent on the prior levels, causing Garen considerable heartache. And it seemed that Level Eight required even more Potential Points. Garen had yet to encounter any bottlenecks in his understanding of this power, so maybe he needed to fulfill another special condition to progress.

Since no dragon was guiding Garen, he also did not dare to ask what special conditions Level Eight might need, lest he created too many shockwaves within the community.

His physical fitness could be attributed to unnatural talent, but that would not be able to explain away his Draconic Aura and Arcane Art. For example, to reach Level Six Draconic Aura, one would need to have truly experienced the aura of a battlefield. Garen understood it without ever stepping into a battlefield, wouldn’t that be proof enough to the other creatures that he was a soul from another world?

As for Ann, he tried asking once, but Ann ignored him completely, saying that he would reach it when he reached it.

So Garen resisted. He left two hundred more points available and threw the rest onto the Arcane Art. Or rather, onto Intelligence and Arcane Art.

Arcane Art required a lot from one’s Intelligence, and the actual progressing of one’s Arcane Art can be accomplished through the accumulative training of one’s meditation and spirit power to increase one’s Intelligence. Simultaneously, the increase in Intelligence would play a crucial part in affecting the most critical areas of the Arcane Art. Out of these, the most prominent was Spell Slots.

Garen had increased his Arcane Art to Level Five, and even that took up a hundred points from what he had left. He had also consecutively borrowed a few standardized Weave archives about Necromancy Spells from Ann.

The fact that he could reach Level Five Arcane Art only proved to show that he could use his hand gestures, chants, and materials to unleash all of the Spells they had learned in Level Five.

Of course, the precondition was that he knew them, meaning that he had learned them before.

Once you reached Level Five and above, however, some crucial level-ups would require a special environment and some special research.

After Garen familiarized himself with the Spellcraft information, he ended up rather disinterested in further research. All he was interested in was the research Undead Masters had done into the soul. As for those Spells?

Those skeletons, zombies, or vampires that they summoned? One dragon’s breath could wipe off so many of them. As for those so-called negative state Spells, he would simply use a Level Seven Immunity Spell. Only Level Eight fighters would be able to cause him some damage, so to him, these Spells were not particularly useful.

The only exception would be if he reached Level Eight and managed to learn the most critical Spell in Necromancy, Deathfinger. Although the chances of an instant death move like that working on him were extremely minuscule, that still depended on what level the powerhouse who unleashed it.

That was why he had only learned a handful of Spells in case of any emergencies. Everything else, he poured into the structure of his power system.

Although he did not take the weakness of the low-level Necromancy Spells seriously, Garen placed great importance in the research of the soul and the body.

It would also be extremely helpful to the usage and training of his training wheels as well.

At the very least, he had discovered a way for him to absorb the core of the Suffering Knight into his Soul Rings.

This was what he had been doing all this time, and the remaining two hundred points were to be put aside for now.

Be it his Arcane Art or his Draconic Aura, both had reached a bottleneck, and his physical fitness could not be too powerful either, so he chose to go out on quests in order to understand the general situation of this world better. At first, he wanted to go out through a summon quest, but something seemed to up with the Wizard over there. After he summoned Garen last time, he never called him again, almost as though he had forgotten about Garen. If it were not for the fact that the Wizard would still contact him occasionally through long-distance communication with their wills, Garen would have assumed that this guy had already died in battle.

After some applications, Garen received a patrol quest.

Led by the captain of the Young Dragon Team, Gamu, they patrolled the borders of the Deladia Empire’s southern plains, vigilant of the Central Empire’s movements.

The rain seemed to be growing heavier.

Gamu looked around.

“There is a patrol supply point nearby, let’s go rest there for now and stock up on some food before we get going again.”

“Captain, this is already a border city very close to the Central Empire, so there will probably be many priests from the Church. How should we deal with that?” asked one White Dragon softly.

Outside of the Deladia Empire, the White Dragon Clan was not welcome in any other territory by the races there. Part of this was because the reputation of White Dragon Mountain was too bad, and part of it was due to the White Dragons’ selfish nature, so there were always rumors about them betraying their other comrades in battle. They even tended to attack human trader convoys in order to steal their riches.

Another point was their disgustingly powerful breeding powers. To the other Dragon Clans, the White Dragons bred exceptionally easily, but at the same time, this put a large burden on the clan. Each of them took up a lot of supplies, and once there were too many of them, without a self-sustained source of food, all they could do was migrate after a certain amount of time. When they moved, all they left behind in their wake were patches of destroyed natural habitats and ecosystems. So it was not surprising that they were known as the representatives of Evil Dragons.

“The churches of both Mother Nature and Lord of Light and Fire have ordered our exile, but right now, we have a different identity now, we are the Deladia Empire’s patrol warrior. Now that we have this identity, they probably would not be so quick to attack…”

Gamu said softly.

“If they dare challenge us, we’ll kill them!” said a White Dragon angrily.

“They’re just a bunch of ants. As long we don’t meet a Silver-Striped Knight or higher, seeing how strong this team is, what else is there to fear?” The White Dragons clearly were not worried.

Garen stood among them, slowly resting and readjusting his breath. He now had Level Seven Draconic Aura and Level Seven physical fitness, so he was already a proper Level Seven apex creature. Even if they did encounter a Silver-Striped Knight, he was not afraid.

Closing his eyes slowly, he began to gradually bring out some of the Soul Energy from the Suffering Knight’s core.

He had already absorbed more than half of the core and only needed to absorb another third or so before he would have drained it completely. But even so, Garen could already clearly see that his Soul Ring had fully perfected the fourth Soul Seed and was beginning to condense the fifth.

The Soul Rings had five levels and leveled up once with every five Seeds.

According to Garen’s estimates, once he finished absorbing the Suffering Core, he would be able to enter the Second Color Phase.

The levels of a Demon Lord were divided into seven color phases, and entering the Second Color meant that he was truly making his way toward becoming an upper-grade Demon Lord.

When he reached the peak of the Seven Color Levels, that would be when he achieved True Soul status.

And the way he saw it, judging by how he had progressed so far in this world, Garen felt that it was quite likely he could achieve True Soul. This world had far too many resources…

After resting for some time, the White Dragons began to fly toward supply point Gamu had mentioned as well.

As he flew, Garen organized his corresponding level boundaries.

Not long later, two groups of humans, fighting against each other, suddenly appeared in the distance ahead of them.

One side was dressed in an array of colors and came from an unknown faction, whereas the other was dressed completely in white robes embroidered with a detailed red fire emblem. Some of these even wore silver helmets and shoulder armor that were carved with complicated divine runes. It was the Priests and Holy Warriors of the Light and Fire Church raiding another unknown group.

“We sure are lucky…” Gamu said helplessly. “We just said that we might encounter Priests, and then we bump into them straight away.”

The five dragons stopped advancing, flying slowly in the air as they watched the battle from afar.

“Just let me eat them!” said a Young Dragon nonchalantly. “They’re just a group of Level Two and Three ants.”

“It’ll be easy to eat them, but the trouble we’d attract later won’t be so simple.” Gamu shook his head. “Let’s just fly over them, ignore them.”

“I’m really hungry now.” That Young Dragon was not very pleased.

“Gedd, now’s not the time to be stubborn,” warned Gamu. His expression grew stern, and the Young Dragon named Gedd quickly hid away his displeasure.

He looked around at the other dragons as well and noticed that another White Dragon was staring wide-eyed at the bright, sparkling things those humans had.

“O Dragon Goddess above, my eyes aren’t deceiving me, right? Those are Soul Gems! How could they be Soul Gems??” This White Dragon kept muttering. As though he realized Gedd was staring at him, he lowered his head quickly, but his expression grew greedier and greedier.

The two dragons exchanged a glance, and read the same intention in each other’s eyes.

This was in the middle of nowhere, so if they acted fast enough, even if they killed these Priests and took away their stuff, those weaklings would not be able to contact the Church in time at their level, so no one would be any the wiser as long as they got rid of the evidence.

Only those who are Level Nine and above would be able to use a Time Reversal Spell, but who would use such a resource-intensive Level Nine Spell on a couple of Level Two and Three Priests?

Garen watched all of this unfold before him.

Chapter 1295: Comrade 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The group of White Dragons flew quickly past the sky on the right side of the battleground.

Gedd and the greedy White Dragon’s eyes casually landed on a Priest wearing a silver helmet who was fighting below them. The glow and aura of the Soul Gem came from him.

“White Dragons?!” There was a gasp from below and the fighting slowed on both sides. There were five Dragons in total, and every one of them was a Level Five Young Dragon. If even one of them descended here, it would be able to decimate everyone present.

After all, Level Five among the dragons and Level Five for regular occupations were not the same. To the humans, Level Five meant that they could use skills with Level Five power, whereas to the dragons, Level Five meant that they could be immune to Level Five Spells and other attacks of the same magnitude. That was the most terrifying part.

In other words, if any one of these Young Dragons landed among them, it could just stand there and nobody there would be able to harm it.

Everyone held their breaths, terrified that one of the White Dragons up there would decide that it was in a bad mood and so swoop down to eat every single one of them.

“The Evil Dragon Clan!” said the leader of the Priests, the one who wore that silver helmet, in a deep voice as he looked up at the sky. Hidden underneath the gem, his eyes shone with a deep-set hatred.

“Orelei!” warned an old Priest next to him sternly.

Silver Helmet harrumphed coldly, and said no more.

“The quest is more important,” said the old Priest.

“If we weren’t here to exterminate these heretics…” said another Priest in a low and contemptuous voice. However, he was immediately hushed.

Soon enough, the group of White Dragons flew past them.

Everyone heaved a sigh of relief.

The Priests turned their gaze back to the group they had surrounded.

“Kill!” Silver Helmet roared in his deep voice.

The people who were surrounded instantly wore expressions of despair, tightening their grip on their weapons and preparing for battle.

All of a sudden, Silver Helmet abruptly noticed that a gigantic shadow was flashing over the top of his head.

He raised his head hurriedly and saw a White Dragon with the body of a horse pounce down on him mercilessly.

“Protect the lord!!”

Two Warriors beside him drew their swords and dashed forward, standing in front of him.

Two Priests began to sing hymns in praise of their god, their hands lighting up with damage-inflicting white rays.

“Gedd!!”

At the same time, yet another dragon pounced down from the side.

The two White Dragons surrounded the most important member of the Priests’ party.

Psst psst psst! Many weak debuffing spells landed on their bodies, but they were completely ineffective. The dragons were fully immune to any spells lower than Level Five.

Bam!

Gedd smashed his head into Silver Helmet, and there was an explosion of bright light between the two of them, white light! The white light exploded between him and Silver Helmet like a sphere of light.

“Dammit!!” Gedd yelled loudly. He seemed to have been injured by something, and was crying out in pain.

The sudden attack and change in the situation had messed up the Priests’ and Warriors’ plan to surround and attack the group. Everyone was trying desperately to retreat, attempting to stop the White Dragons’ attacks.

The Evil Dragons and most of the human Priests had always stood on two ends of a divide, so attacks like these were not rare. The unexpected part, however, was that Priests were usually the ones to initiate a battle. This time, there were actually White Dragons who dared to initiate an attack on the Priests of god, so this was a challenge against the dignity of their god.

The two White Dragons stood among the Priests and Warriors, knocking away a few Warriors easily with a swipe of their claw or a shake of their head. Low-level spells were ineffective against them, but the Priests switched to using holy spells to buff up their Warriors. Rays of green and red light lit up on the Warrior’s bodies. They instantly rose the Warriors’ abilities by one level, and the strongest one even reached Level Four.

“Give us the Soul Gem! And we’ll go immediately!” After Gedd knocked away Silver Helmet, he stood on the spot and roared loudly.

“Two Evil Dragons! How dare you attack…!” Before the voice could complete the sentence, there was a tremor, and the whole earth seemed to sink abruptly.

Bam! An even larger and stronger White Dragon descended upon them from the sky, landing behind Gedd and the other dragon. This one had even cleaner, brighter scales, and its body was more evenly and gracefully proportioned. It was Garen, who had already noticed that something was fishy about the two dragons.

He had noticed it, and the captain Gamu even more so. The captain just happened to silently permit it, because the Priests from the Church of Fehra had killed White Dragons more than once or twice, so it was normal to get revenge once.

On the other hand, Garen had followed the two White Dragons who had slipped away during break time in order to earn some side income.

He had heard every word of their conversation just now using his peak-level physical abilities, and so he knew about the Soul Gem. As long as it had anything to do with the soul, he would be extremely interested in it.

“You two! What are you planning to do, sneaking back here?” Garen’s movements made both White Dragons jolt, but when they realized it was him, both of them heaved a sigh of relief. Anything was fine as long as it was not the captain.

“Don’t tell Captain, and we’ll give you a share!” said Gedd hurriedly.

Garen grinned.

“Sure!”

The Priests and the people they were surrounding gathered together. When they were being chased by dragons on plains like these, trying to escape was futile. Their only sliver of hope was to put up a fight.

“We’re from the Holy Tribunal! We’re currently representing the Church on a heretic extermination mission, are you sure the White Dragon Clan wants to get involved in this?” Just as the Priests were beginning to despair, an old Priest stepped up and said loudly.

“Heretic? I don’t care about any heretics, just hand over anything valuable! Or else you don’t even have to think about leaving here!” Relieved, Gedd and the other White Dragon looked at these Priests with a cold smile, as well as the other group who was being surrounded.

“You dare get in the way of Fehra’s all-encompassing light!?” Silver Helmet crawled up from the ground, blood seeping out through his priest’s robes at the chest.

“Sadly, the only got we believe in is Tiamat.” Gedd flew and pounced at the two guardians again, knocking them away harshly and then pressing the leader underneath his claw. He then began to search his body.

On the other side, Garen was slightly confused as he noticed something about the group of people who were being surrounded.

He sensed that within this group, there seemed to be something with a Soul Aura rather similar to his.

His gaze terrified these Warriors who were only at Level Two, and all they could think of was what if this Evil Dragon just accidentally ate them up. It was not unheard of for White Dragons to eat humans.

While the other two were in the midst of looting, Garen paid attention to their side while he walked over to question the other group.

“You guys are the heretics pursued by the Church?”

In his eyes, these people were just a random assortment of normal Warriors, and they did not even have the basic combat training to stand in a defensive formation. They were clearly just a group of ragtag soldiers.

“No! We’re not heretics!”

“We don’t really know what’s happening here either, Lord White Dragon. The Church suddenly rushed into our houses and just started killing us without even giving us a chance to explain.”

“They stole our possessions and defiled our wives and daughters! The great Fehra would never condone their violent existence!”

But Garen did not care about what they were saying about all, his gaze was trained on one of the members among them.

“Gerbera here, pleased to meet you, Your Majesty.” A voice resounded directly in his head.

“You are…?” Garen immediately recognized that he was using a method unique to Void Creatures to communicate information through the Dream Space. But this was extremely difficult to accomplish in real life.

Garen glanced at the White Dragons who were looting the other side, and waved his claw.

“Tell me, why are you guys suddenly heretics now? Wasn’t the Central Empire perfectly fine before?” The information he received when he started patrolling was that the Central Empire was still as peaceful and calm as before, and there were no signs of any heretic extermination operations at all.

“No, the Empire’s Meteor City has been attacked by an unknown entity! The Church is furious, so they’ve started searching for heretics. We were just caught in the crossfire.”

The member who had been possessed by a Void Creature stepped out and said loudly.

“Meteor City?” Garen was slightly stunned. Meteor City was the home base of the God of Light and Fire, Fehra, and now someone actually dared to attack that place?

“Do you know who or what it is?”

He transmitted a question through the Void Creatures’ special method.

“Sir, it’s a Thousand-Armed Giant. Other than the Void Demon Masters already known to our alliance, the Mother Stream is simply too big, and it has spawned innumerable powerful existences too. This attack was not factored into our plan at all, it was probably a stray Demon Master who participated in the probe.”

“How could it be? Isn’t there a fixed number of True Souls and Demon Masters?” Garen frowned.

“No, we don’t really know just how many powerful beings there are in the Mother Stream either, we just know that there are extremely many, more than you could imagine. Our alliance only represents one part of this power,” the being called Gerbera replied quietly.

“The Mother Stream is like an ocean, and the power that we know of is just a tiny bay. We just happen to be more united, there are many other stronger creatures who are simply unable to work together. They don’t give a damn about the alliance, and instead they have all sorts of mysterious and strange abilities. We don’t know just how many they have either.

“A Thousand-Armed Giant…” Garen had heard of this type of creature. In this Ancient Endor legends, this creature came from a race called the Hundred-Armed Giants and was the strongest among them. It was a terrifying creature capable of destroying entire civilizations.

“What happened in the end?” he continued asking.

“The Thousand-Armed Giant was ripped to shreds, and the God of Light and Fire’s Incarnation was projected into the mortal realm as well. The Projection was killed, but the Incarnation was doing okay, and was only slightly injured in the end. I believe the attacking Demon Master knows just how strong Fehra is now.” Gerbera said somewhat regrettably, “What a waste, they abandoned such a powerful Thousand-Armed Giant just like that, just to probe their powers. That’s a powerful existence that can rival an upper-level Demon Lord!”

“The Projection only has a few one-thousandths of Fehra’s strength, but the Incarnation would have at least one per cent. As a Major God, one percent of Fehra’s power could already kill off an upper-level Demon Lord and only sustain some light injuries…”

Garen was inwardly impressed.

“Then how did they break through the Barrier and maintain their original powers without having to reincarnate?”

“We’re not really sure about that… But I heard that on the other end of the Mother Stream, there’s an even larger Chaotic Territory. The Void Races there have something called a Distortion Door. It can distort everything and penetrate Barriers. They are parasites, so as long as the host allows them to stay, they can travel through worlds uninhibited while also maintaining their original powers. It’s just we haven’t seen it before.”

Gerbera explained softly.

Garen asked a few more questions. Gerbera answered them all, one by one, so Garen decided to just have him stay back, releasing everyone else.

On the other side, the Priests had also been completely wiped out by the two White Dragons. These White Dragons did not care about Fehra’s Church at all, and killed them just like they said they would. They had obtained five whole Soul Gems and an assortment of enchanted equipment, as well as two high-quality Holy Spell Scrolls. Everything was Level Five.

“I want all the gems!” Garen walked over and glanced at the Soul Gems, his heart giving a heavy jolt. These things were just like the Soul Crystals from the previous world, he could condense them into a Soul Seed once he got enough of them!

“No! The gems are mine! You can choose something else! Seeing as you don’t plan to spill the beans on us…”

Bam!!

Before he finished talking, Garen swiped his tail at Gedd, who wanted to continue speaking, without any hesitation whatsoever.

Gedd’s body was sent rolling away by the tail swipe, and he left a long clear mark on the ground. There were drops of white blood seeping out from underneath his scales.

“Do you have any other opinion?” Garen looked at the other White Dragon.

This White Dragon gave a shudder and hastily nodded, then he realized something was wrong and started shaking his head instead.

“No! I have no other opinion!”

Chapter 1296: Comrade 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen nodded, satisfied, and walked up to the White Dragon, Gedd. He grabbed a Space Ring that belonged to that Silver Helmet from the ground in front of Gedd, and used the ring to keep away the five Soul Gems.

These things were called gems, but in truth they looked just like sweet potatoes, dusty grey on the outside, but a lot harder. If it was not for the fact that Garen could clearly feel how different the forces were, he would not have known that these were the so-called Soul Gems.

“Five Soul Gems? That’s a pretty impressive deal. Looks like these Priests have already imprisoned five heretic souls, each of them at least Level Three.” The only function Soul Gems had was to imprison souls, a gem without a soul inside was not called a Soul Gem. In other words, these five Soul Gems each had a soul trapped inside.

These souls had had their memories wiped clean, until all that remained were their most basic combat understanding and knowledge. These were maintained in order to become materials for the creation of more Holy Angels in the future.

On the other side, Gedd was crawling up, a hint of resentment and fury in his eyes as he looked at Garen. Then he hurriedly lowered his head and did not dare say anything else.

Garen’s power had reached Level Seven a long time ago, and Gedd had heard before that, as the strongest prodigy in the clan, the Third Elder had many hopes of Garen. Apparently, he might even sign an Eternal Contract with King Gus. A being like this was not something Gedd could offend easily.

“Alright, let’s go. We’ve been out for a tad too long,” Garen said casually.

The two White Dragons hastily packed up the treasures.

Garen turned around and glanced at Gerbera. His appearance looked just like a normal young teenage Warrior. He had wounds and blood on his face as a result of battle, and so he looked somewhat worse for the wear.

Gerbera blinked.

“Um, Your Majesty, this area is under the governance of the Black Fish King, so if you wish to obtain more information about our fellows here, you can contact him.”

“Black Fish King?” Garen was slightly stunned. “There are different territories under different managers?”

“Yeah, we’ve secretly infiltrated many places, and there are different beings in charge of managing each different place so that they can report large amounts of data back at any time. The one in charge here is the Black Fish King, and if he knew that there was a Demon Lord Level here, he would be extremely happy,” Gerbera replied hurriedly.

“Alright, I’ll go meet him.” Garen nodded. “You get going, it’s not safe here.”

“Yes.”

Garen left Gerbera alone, and brought the two White Dragons back toward the direction of the captain, flapping their wings and flying there. Soon enough, they caught up to Captain Gamu, who was pretending to rest.

Garen glanced at Gedd behind him and gave him a look.

Looking depressed, Gedd handed a part of the treasures he had obtained to the captain, passing it over to him quietly.

Gamu received it inconspicuously. The other White Dragons pretended not to see it.

“Alright, let’s continue on. We need to finish patrolling the entire border within a month, and then we’ll return to the clan as soon as we complete our quest.”

“Yes.”

All the White Dragons replied in their low voices.

“First, let’s find a supply point.”

The row of White Dragons flew into the sky again slowly, shooting away into the distance.

*******************

They soon completed their patrol quest, though that was putting aside the many dragons who also began to rob any creatures they met on the way, having seen how Gedd and the others struck it rich.

Garen waited for the dragons to go their separate ways, heading back in the direction of the clan. Along the way, he had found a location that was closest to the Central Empire, and used Dream Communication to meet the Black Fish King that Gerbera had mentioned.

In the limitless black ocean, there was no end in sight, the seawater rising and falling.

The sky was completely dark, but there was actually a white fog floating between the sky and the sea.

Garen stood on the seawater and saw precisely such a scene.

He had already reached the third grade of Dreamland and met the person in charge of this area, Black Fish King, directly. It was the owner of this pair of dead-fish eyes.

If they were in the real world, each of these eyes would be as big as a house and unnaturally terrifying.

“A new comrade?” The Black Fish King spoke in the Void language, his words reaching Garen.

“Black Fish King?” Garen asked.

“Are you here to ask me about the Thousand-Armed Giant?” The Black Fish King seemed to have been asked about this a lot already. “Agare, the Thousand-Armed Giant Agare. That was the name I heard from afar. He bit off the statue on top of the Church of Fehra, it was a statue of Fehra, so the Lord of Light and Fire lost his temper.”

He laughed, contemptuously and proudly.

“He deserves it. He actually oppressed me for a thousand years, and this time, even his incarnation was injured.”

This guy…

Wordlessly, Garen listened to the Black Fish King roar in laughter.

“Alright, I also want to know, has the Mother Stream taken any new actions recently?”

By ‘Mother Stream’, he meant the Mother Stream Alliance, an immense faction that put aside their previous differences in order to survive, thus achieving unprecedented unity.

“Actions? What actions would we need to take??” The Black Fish King continued to laugh. “The Mother Stream is beginning to retaliate instinctively, hahaha! Countless Void creatures and Ancient Endor beings have already been released into this universe. Into the deep Abyss, the Inferno, the Mortal World, the Heavenly World, and countless other dimensions. We are just pushing the waves along from behind the scenes.”

“You don’t seem to be worried at all?” Garen frowned.

“Worried? The Underworld River of this world is no match for the Mother Stream either. Be it the Will of the Abyss, or the many gods in the Heavenly World, this war cannot be decided by any one party. What’s the point of worrying?” The Black Fish King was completely unconcerned.

“Tell me, how many other Demon Lord Level existences are there around here?” Garen continued to ask.

“How many?” The Black Fish King looked at him strangely.

“Most of the Lord Levels have gone to the Abyss, those’re the best soul hunting grounds. In Blood Wars, the demons in the tower don’t care if you come from another world or not. They just want to win the wars. Nothing else matters!”

“Blood Wars, huh?” Garen was thoughtful.

“If you want to go, you can go through the Soaring Wing King, he’s a Level Twelve Great Arcanist hiding in that Snow City near your side. If you can’t find him there, you can go look for the Snake Princess in the Green Oak Forest. She’ll give you a Blood War Stone for free, and all you have to do is transmit your power into the Abyss. The demons there will help you pay the transmission price needed for battle,” suggested the Black Fish King. “On the precondition that you don’t mind dying for nothing, of course.”

“I got it, many thanks.” Garen nodded. He knew about the location of the Abyss’ Blood Wars. The place was called the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains, and had a poisonous dark red sun scorching down on many fortresses of steel. Even the greatest river of this world, the Underworld River, flowed from there.

The Ten Thousand Abyss Plains were the highest level of the Abyss, and had many bottomless abysses there. These abysses could reach each of the different levels of the Abyss at any time.

The conversation ended just like that.

Garen bid farewell to the Black Fish King and the two of them exchanged Dream Communication methods. To the Demon Lords, as long as they had a marker, it would not be difficult for them to directly project communication. It was the same principle as Nadia’s long-distance projected attack back then.

By now, Garen could freely use his Confinement Essence in the Dream World. Although his middle-level Demon Lord Soul Rings were weaker than the Black Fish King’s, his understanding of this Essence made up for the difference in ability. Even if he could not defeat the Black Fish King, he would not be confined and trapped in the latter’s Dream World.

That was why, in truth, he was not very afraid of upper-level Demon Lords either. If it were not for the fact that the restrictions in this world were too strong, and the pure power of his soul had been weakened too much to the point that it could not leave his physical body and could only affect it, he would have already returned to the peak of his powers from the previous life by now.

He did not encounter any more accidents after the patrol quest. After flying eventlessly in the sky for a few days, Garen returned safely to the clan. Where he continued to train.

Every year, he went to Ann and underwent the experiment.

Just like Ann said, not only did her experiments not weaken him, they even vaguely strengthened him.

Garen would also occasionally go out for a stroll. After understanding that there were fellow Demon Lords scattered around managing different territories, he visited the Snake Princess Demon Lord in Green Oak Forest and the Soaring Wing King nearby, in another direction.

Snake Princess was a small silver snake as long as an arm, and she looked very weak, but she belied extremely terrifying power. She was definitely Level Ten or higher.

On the other hand, the Soaring Wing King was slightly weaker. He only had a Level Nine physical body, but he actually held in his hand a Semi-Divine Weapon that directly increased his power to an unfathomable level.

Garen created a communication channel with the Back Fish King and these other two, allowing them to exchange intel.

Garen’s advantage in intel was in the Deladia Empire. King Gus was a Level Fifteen peak existence, and there were plenty of powerhouses within the Empire. There were eighteen whole beings who were Level Ten and above, so they dominated this area, keeping all the other powers here silent.

And the Black Fish King was a powerful noble inside the Central Empire, so he had an advantage in gathering intel about the Church of Fehra.

The area around here was almost completely taken by Mother Nature’s and Fehra’s churches, so naturally, any intelligence about these two Major Gods was extremely valuable.

Meanwhile, the Soaring Wing King was a Great Arcanist, acting as a member of the Snow City’s Arcane Organization Grey Shadow Parliament. It was independent and stood against the Deladia Empire. However, he asked Garen for information more often than the other way around. His intelligence channels seemed to more obstructed than the others.

Snake Princess was a Great Druid who believed in Mother Nature, and she also had the most variety of random resources and materials. She seemed to have many connections, and could obtain all sorts of materials.

The Black Fish King and the Soaring Wing King also bought materials from her quite often, and now there was Garen as well.

They called Garen the White Dragon King. Although this was the title of the White Dragon Mountain’s Dragon King, no one cared.

As time passed, the situation grew more chaotic.

More and more Interdimensional Passages opened up mysteriously, and there was clearly an instability in space. A space-time crevice even opened up near the White Dragon Clan, swallowing up two Adult White Dragons that had gone out hunting and scaring the Third Elder into hurriedly sending his elites to draw out boundaries in case any other dragons wandered in.

A few more years passed in the blink of an eye.

Garen gathered two hundred more Potential Points. Add that to the two hundred from before, and he had four hundred now. He had always resisted from using them for fear of growing too overpowered and attracting the attention of the gods.

And he finally received news from King Gus, who signed an Eternal Contract with a princess from the Red Dragon Clan.

Only then did Garen heave a sigh of relief. He had it all planned out, if he were to be chosen as a contractor, he would go straight to the Abyss for the Blood Wars.

Right now, there were no outside eyes paying particular attention to him, so he finally started to secretly use all the Potential Points on his own attributes.

But he did not add them evenly. Instead…

Chapter 1297: Conclusion 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation  Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He did not add them evenly.

Instead, he firstly increased one aspect to an extreme.

When it came to increasing his attributes, Garen had always been used to directly increasing them to extremes. Now that he had collected so many Potential Points, he prepared to do the same thing.

Since King Gus’ contract had been canceled, he did not have so much attention trained on him anymore. That way, there would not be too many variables and concerns even if he drastically increases his powers.

Inside the White Dragon Clan, Garen lay in his cave, surrounded by many books he borrowed from the other White Dragons, as well as the ones he got from Ann.

He had generally calculated the general situation within the Clan, and once he added that to some of Ann’s top-secret information, he obtained the truest of real-world statistics. Statistics about the physical fitness of the dragons.

Converted into the Attribute System that he used, it meant that as a member of the dragon race, the limit of his power in this world would be about ninety points on average. Theoretically, this was the limit that the bodies of those Ancient Dragons could reach. Any beings with these statistics would basically be demigods that were almost a thousand meters long and understood divinity. Once they reached this limit, the dragons would also slowly weaken due to the lengths of their lives.

This was the necessary rhythm of things.

The White Dragons were among the weaker members of the dragon race, so their limit was at eighty attribute points or so. However, they could use their Draconic Aura, Arcane Art, and other abilities to increase their actual power.

“Eighty points is the limit for all White Dragons, and I’m already at sixty points…” Over the years, Garen’s natural growth and development had already broken past the sixty-point mark. His Strength was at 61, Agility 62, and his Vitality was slightly weaker, but even that was at 53. Because he put too much into it, his Intelligence had increased directly to 49.

And he could still add four hundred whole Potential Points to this.

“Let me increase them to their limits first.” Although Garen was confident in his Soul Limit, he was still slightly worried. The restrictions of this world were a tad too strong.

Right now, he needed three Potential Points to raise his attributes by one point.

Garen stared at his Strength attribute, and his Potential Points instantly took a nosedive plunge.

61… 62… 65… 70… 80… When it reached the eighty, the increase stopped abruptly.

Garen frowned slightly.

He could still feel some space for improvement, but it seemed to be slightly harder to increase Strength just by itself. It felt as though something was restricting the increase of his Strength attribute.

He moved his body slightly and felt as though it was unbalanced…

By increasing his Strength to eighty points, he had used up as many as 57 Potential Points. He still had 343 remaining.

“It’s probably a result of the imbalance from the other attributes. Perhaps I should increase them evenly. As expected, extremism won’t work…”

When his thoughts reached that, Garen began to increase his Agility and Vitality as well.

His Agility had been at 62 points, and he increased it by 18 points, using up 54 Potential Points. And his Vitality was at 53 points, and he used five points to increase it to 58 before it started requiring three Potential Points for one attribute point. He used another 66 Potential Points before he could reach 80.

The last was Intelligence. All in all, Garen used up 257 whole Potential Points before he could have all attributes reach 80 points.

Lying down in his cave, Garen’s body was completely curled up. His body had already expanded rapidly until it was as large as an Adult White Dragon’s, and it was still slowly growing. Large amounts of transparent energy flowed under his scales, it was the energy from his Potential Points.

At the end of the day, Potential Points were actually a source of pure energy that could be freely distributed to the different parts and functions of his body.

This energy was now rapidly strengthening Garen’s body to an incomprehensible extent.

Garen’s scales were growing whiter and whiter, becoming more crystalline, glowing with neon light. His body was approaching the standards of utmost perfection. Small stabs of pain surged up endlessly from all over his body, and Garen resisted that pain, an indescribable feeling in his heart.

As though his body was a rubber ball, and the constant release of Potential Point energy was inflating his body quickly.

“Looks like this is a compulsory process when powering up. The stronger the laws, the more natural adaptation and adjustment time would be needed for attribute changes.” Garen glanced at his current status.

‘Garen — Strength 80, Agility 80, Vitality 80, Intelligence 80. Potential 14363%. Soul Limit 170.

‘Level 7 Draconic Aura. Level 5 Arcane Art.’

“I still have some Potential Points left.” He tried to continue increasing his attributes, but it seemed as though they could not be increased anymore for the time being, because his body had already reached its limit. This was already the limit for a single adjustment session.

Garen sensed that if he continued to increase his attributes, his body might be in danger of exploding, so he instantly squashed down that notion. Instead, he placed his attention on the thing that he had been researching for some time now.

The fusion of the knowledge and systems from the many major universes.

He had once used created the Ten Thousand True Technique while in a human body, and this could be used in most universe systems. Although he was in a dragon body now, the Ten Thousand True Technique was still usable, he just needed to adjust the basic training paths slightly.

And after joining the Young Dragons these past few years, Garen still used most of his efforts to figure out how he could incorporate what he had learned previously into the power system of this world.

No, that was not the best way to phrase. More precisely, he was trying to connect his understanding of the power system in this world with those of all the other universes, in order to form a system that could be used in all the worlds.

Garen had traveled through so many universes, and, especially in the Transmigators’ Lighthouse, he had encountered so many different civilizations and systems. He had learned and seen so much, far more than even Ann.

In these past few years, he had mostly been focusing his attention on this.

In the Mech World, he had once obtained two extremely overpowered martial arts techniques, namely the Nine-Level Tempered Body Technique and the Destructive Impact Fist.

He had once reached an extremely high realm in the former, but as for the latter, even Garen himself never reached the limit of the Destructive Impact Fist.

“In the end, I relied on the Crystal Confinement and understood the Shadow Dragon’s Void Confinement Essence, only then could I reach the pinnacle. This was a stroke of luck, but since I could not reach the limit in the previous world, maybe I can try walking this sort of straightforward path for once in this world.”

He had always sensed that the true essence of the Destructive Impact was extremely terrifying, and at the very end, it seemed to be able to understand a Conceptual Essence that went beyond Confinement.

The restrictions of this world were very powerful, so he could not use the Destructive Impact Fist. But since White Dragons were part of the dragon race, their natural fitness far surpassed that of humans.

Hence, Garen’s foundations were very powerful as well, and it would not be impossible for him to try fusing this brutally powerful martial arts completely.

He organized the different system and finally came up with a set that contained the essence of everything he had learned.

He used the Ten Thousand True Technique as the main body, the Destructive Impact Fist as the skeleton, and all the other system contents as the blood and flesh to fill it up.

A powerful form of martial arts that belonged fully to him slowly began to take shape.

This conclusive system no longer originated from the Mother Stream. Instead, it was usable in all the universes, or at the very least, it could be used unrestrictedly in all the universes Garen had experienced up until now. It was practically adapted to all of the universes’ original systems.

Hence, he gave this power system a simple name — Void Original Opus. Because be it the Mother Stream or anything else, everything originated in the endless universal void. That was also the origin of that name.

The Void Original Opus that he first arranged contained next to everything. All of the martial arts he had ever learned, the secret techniques, skills, and even the essences, he could use all of them through the Original Opus.

Be it secret techniques, or Willpower, or any other system.

The difference between this and other systems was that the Void Original Opus’ roots did not lie in any form of power. Instead, it used the practitioner’s body and soul directly.

The energy produced was something Garen called Original Energy. This Original Energy was unnaturally pure and clean and could be used in any universe.

Right now, his physical fitness had been increased to its limit, and Garen had also checked his Void Original Opus once more to make sure there were no loopholes. This Original Opus even included this world’s Arcane Art system and Draconic Aura system. It could naturally tap into the strongest genes in the deepest part of the body, and this Original Energy came from his research in the Totem World.

Once he was sure there were no problems with the Original Opus, Garen finally became to practice this personalized system that he had created.

In truth, he had already sensed that the Void Original Opus was vaguely similar to the Living Secret Techniques he used to practice, and was a terrifying weapon that could truly last through the ages.

If he randomly created a Living Secret Technique Seed and released it, perhaps another shocking battle to snatch it would occur again in some ruins ten thousand years later.

The days passed, one by one, and Garen continued to stay in his cave training. Satwo, Sathree and the others brought him food and water. He practically ignored everything else happening in the world outside.

As time passed, his body grew larger and larger, rapidly expanding from the size of a normal Adult Dragon until it was more than twenty meters long and ten meters tall. He had directly become an enormous giant, comparable to some Ancient Dragons, but immediately afterward, he began to shrink quickly as well, returning to the size of a Dragon Whelp within three days. And then he grew again and shrank again.

This cycle ended and began once more, for several dozen times consecutively.

The aura around Garen grew more and more fearsome. It was not Draconic Aura, but a special type of suppressed aura.

In the blink of an eye, more than several dozen days had passed.

*******************

“I wonder what Garen is doing recently? He hasn’t come out to eat for more than ten days now.”

Satwo had grown slightly as well. Although he still looked like a Dragon Whelp, he was one size larger than a regular Dragon Whelp. This was also a result of Garen’s influence, since he obtained a larger share of the resources, it allowed him to grow faster than others as well.

“Perhaps he’s cultivating his Draconic Aura, so that he can prepare to break through to the next level?” said Sathree softly. “What about Safour?”

“Out on a quest.”

“To the Black Horn Mountain Range again?”

“We’re Dragon Whelps, not Young Dragons. The last time we went to the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range, we sustained heavy casualties, so the higher-ups lowered the standard and changed the location. It’s only natural.” Satwo pouted. “What, did you think that anyone could do like Garen did, and just join the Young Dragons on patrol like that?”

Inside the ice cave, the two Dragon Whelps chatted idly in low voices. With Garen’s protection, they did not have to worry about being sent off to any quests that were too dangerous. In fact, if any of the dragons in the clan were even slightly impolite to them, they would be dragged off by the Third Elder’s Dragon Guards for a talk.

Now that the Third Elder had separated on bad terms with the leader of the Dragon Guards, Phosphorus, he was placing all of his expectations on Garen. He was raising and helping Garen however he could, hoping that Garen could replace Phosphorus and become the new strongest Dragon Guard leader that was also on the Third Elder’s side.

That was why Garen and the dragons around him got the biggest slice of the pie for many matters within the clan.

Ever since Leona and Boris left, Garen no longer wanted to raise any conflicts against the Third Elder. Since he no longer had to worry about King Gus’ Eternal Contract, he was also more than happy to enjoy the power and position given to him by the Third Elder.

Boom!!

Suddenly, there was the sound of a huge explosion coming from the cave Garen was in.

Sathree and Satwo were jolted and nearly felt onto the surface of the ice.

“What sound was that!?”

“It came from Garen’s cave, let’s go look!!”

The two Dragon Whelps reacted immediately and rushed straight to the cave Garen was in.

After a few turns and dashes, going through a long and narrow ice tunnel, the two Dragon Whelps quickly rushed into Garen’s cave.

There was a mist of white steam inside, so they could not see anything inside at all.

“Garen?! Are you okay!?” Satwo yelled loudly.

Chapter 1298: Conclusion 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Sathree was a female dragon, and she followed behind him carefully, blowing out her breath and flapping her wings hard so that she could scatter the large clouds of white fog.

“Garen??” Sathree started yelling as well.

The fog spun slowly in a clockwise rotation, like a whirlwind, with the most central area of the cave acting as the eye of the storm.

At the center of the fog, Garen was looking at a wall of ice in front of him, calmly. The mirror-like wall reflected his current appearance clearly.

On the surface, he clearly looked just like a normal Adult White Dragon. But there was a vague overlapping image in the mirror, and that image showed a completely different Garen.

In the overlapping image, his right claw was ablaze with golden flames, and the cries of a phoenix emanated from those flames. His left claw emitted a pale blue chill that vaguely rang out with the deep calls of a phoenix.

His left wing sparkled with seven black dead stars, and a creepy ice-cold trident appeared in front of his right wing.

His long and slender dragon tail waved slowly, and he could actually see the illusion of nine fearsome dragon heads at the tip.

And in front of his chest, in the very center of his torso, there was a shapeless black whirlpool. Specks of starlight twinkled in the whirlpool, blinking in and out of sight.

Phew…

He opened his mouth and blew out a breath. It was a faint cloud-like Dragon Breath, but he did not blow it out of his own accord. Instead, every breath he exhaled naturally had that special power.

This was a result of the Divine Statue Technique and Hellfrost Scarlet Snow Technique that he used to practice.

The truth was that every power Garen carefully cultivated to a certain point had left an indelible mark deep within his soul. And these marks had fully manifested now that he had successfully invented his Void Original Opus.

Everything he had ever learned had naturally manifested on his dragon body.

“The Void Original Opus is a conclusion of everything I had ever learned over time, and it also perfectly embodies the imprints on my soul from the beginning until now.”

Garen raised his claws. The left claw had an illusion of golden flames, representing the Holy Phoenix Demonic Book. The right claw had a pale blue chill, symbolizing the Hellfrost Peacock Mother.

And each of the other parts represented another part of his life’s conclusions and experiences.

“This is that so-called True Body that only forms at the peak of the Demon Lord level, right?” He had heard of this form before, when some upper-level Demon Lords wanted to reach the True Soul form, they needed to condense everything they had into one, and fuse that into one body. This would then force the body to evolve to its highest level, and from there, it would advance to the True Soul.

“This is an early form of the True Soul…?” Lastly, Garen glanced at himself in the mirror, pulling back the Soul Rings all around this body and storing away all of the illusions, keeping them inside his body.

At the same time, his body shrunk rapidly as well, returning to his original Young Dragon form.

This was a secret technique similar to the Bone Shrinking Technique that he used to hide himself.

The Void Original Opus did not have grades, only a percentage. Garen had tossed all of his remaining Potential Points into it, hence resulting in his current progress in change. His Original Opus had risen from 0% to 14%, in other words, more than 140 Potential Points could only raise his power by 14%.

The truth was, if it were not for the fact that Garen tried increasing his attributes again and found that they still would not increase, he would not have put all his Potential Points into the Void Original Opus like that so decisively, no matter how useless the Potential Points were.

The invention of the Void Original Opus gave him plenty of inspiration, and he vaguely knew that the reason his attributes could no longer increase was not because they had reached their limit. His Soul Limit was far beyond that of a normal dragon, so there was no way he could have been blocked. And the way his body was now meant that he had to evolve to a higher level, only then would he fulfill the rules of this world, and only then would he be able to continue accepting more energy and materials. According to the laws, this was practically a required evolution process.

There were no abnormal changes or increases in his physical attributes, but because of that, he had a feeling that his body could still evolve further.

Waving his hand and scattering the fog, Garen looked at Satwo and Sathree, who were walking in.

“I’m fine, there’s no need to worry. I was just practicing my Draconic Aura and created some force waves because I got careless.”

“Are you sure you’re really fine?” Satwo asked carefully.

“I’m fine. You guys can leave now, I still plan to continue training,” Garen replied with a smile.

“Alright, then…” Satwo and Sathree did not dare to say too much either, and they left in a hurry. If at first they still considered Garen their brother, the Garen they saw right now had long since left their reach. They already thought of Garen as their protector, someone like an older brother or a father.

Garen waited for the siblings to leave the cave before he started considering his current level.

“I must be at least Level Eight, perhaps Level Nine. But until I cross swords with a true Level Nine existence from this world, I won’t know their level either.” Garen was confident that he had already reached the highest level of physical fitness that the body of a White Dragon could achieve, only powerful Ancient Dragons who have lived for several thousand years could match up to him.

Eighty attribute points on average were enough to go against a giant warship in the Mech World, but the restrictions here were too harsh, so there was no telling how much power it could result in here.

Garen sensed that his body was still evolving and changing slowly, and this required time. He had a feeling that once he finished evolving, he could still continue increasing his body’s attributes and elements.

As for Level Nine, he was not particularly afraid of it. With just his body alone, he might already be immune to regular Level Nine spells. This was a privilege only enjoyed by the very highest-level Black Dragons.

He suddenly remembered the Suffering Knight core he had devoured earlier. Before he knew it, he had subconsciously finished digesting it. That thing had probably contributed to his evolution earlier as well.

He looked at his current Soul Rings.

Five Soul Seeds were fully complete and had already been raised to the Pale Red Color. It had risen from its original Colorless Level to Pale Red.

All five Soul Rings sank, leaving their initial position open. The silhouette of a new Soul Ring appeared where they used to be, and this glowed with a faint orange light.

“The second level, the second level of the Seven Colors Phase, needs me to find five more Soul Seeds and condense them into orange Soul Seeds. If I was still very young and weak, this would probably be harder than walking in air, but right now, well… After all, the Soul Seeds for the second level should require Soul Seeds of a higher quality than the first level. And more Soul Energy as well.”

He remembered the Suffering Knight core that he had devoured earlier. The Soul Energy contained inside that thing was definitely enough. Perhaps it could become a second level Soul Seed after purification.

There was also the grudge from before when he was hunted down. It was about time to cash in that debt.

“Perfect, I can test my abilities and see where I stand now.”

Garen grinned.

******************

Fiery Blaze Mountain Range

Whoosh!

A white shadow instantly shot past the sky and flashed across the snowy peaks, leaving a long white line of air.

It was a long and slender White Dragon.

The White Dragon flew straight toward the depths of the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range. He did not linger for even a second.

The cold clean sunlight shone down on his body, glowing with a light that was as bright as a mirror.

There were only a few Hellfrost Giant Iguanas hunting around for food in the mountain range during the daytime. Some of the Elder Giant Iguanas sent their auras shooting into the air, drawing the boundaries of their own territory.

Garen swept past at a high speed and descended from the sky abruptly, pouncing mercilessly at an Elder Giant Iguana.

Bam!

The white shadow landed, and the Elder Giant Iguana roared madly as it covered its entire body with ice armor. At the same time, a gigantic rolling ice ball appeared, floating above its head.

But the white shadow crashed straight down at it, and the ball of ice shattered. The Elder Giant Iguana was smashed hard into the snowy ground, and its entire large body actually sank into the ground. The impact instantly knocked it unconscious.

Garen lifted the Elder Giant Iguana. This Giant Iguana was already at Level Six, but to him as he was right now, it was basically a massacre.

Garen dug the Demon Core out of the Elder Giant Iguana’s head and wiped it on the snowy ground. Once he made sure it was clean, he tossed it straight into his mouth. There was a cracking sound, and he actually managed to chew and swallow the sturdiest Demon Core in one go, just like that. The pieces of the Demon Core, as sharp as glass shards, were actually unable to scratch or pierce the membranes and skin inside his mouth.

“Its Soul Energy is so weak…” Garen frowned slightly. A Level Six Demon Core like this only gave him two Potential Points.

What was the difference between this and the Level Five Demon Core he risked his life to obtain back then?

But this was also the disadvantage of having unnaturally exceptional talent. The longer he trained and the higher he reached, the harder it would be to simply rely on this to power up. That was because the energy requirements were too high, so the regular Potential Point sources naturally appeared insignificant when it came to higher level upgrades.

It was just like how a drop of water was more than what an ant could drink in an entire lifetime, but at the same time, it could barely wet the lips of a person.

“It’s better than nothing.”

Garen looked around him. Everything was covered in white snow, black stone and yellow earth revealed in some places.

“This should be the heart of the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range.”

He walked around the area casually. Since he did not know just where the Suffering Knight came from, he planned to reveal himself in advance and lure them out.

On the snowy ground, his heavy body meant that every step he took made crunching noises in the snow.

He emitted his powerful Draconic Aura. Although it was only Level Seven, it was already an extremely horrifying presence to the strongest creature here, the Level Six Elder Giant Iguanas.

All the Elder Giant Iguanas ran and hid.

Garen wandered around for half a day, and still did not encounter a second Elder Giant Iguana.

However, it seemed that there were many ruins in the Fiery Blaze Mountain Range. Slightly interested, he wandered around inside, but he did not discover anything interesting. Evidently, they had already been cleared out by others who came before.

The flying snow began to come down again, slowly.

Garen walked toward the area where the snowstorm was at its strongest.

Before he knew it, he had walked up to the front of an abandoned white palace that looked like a garden.

The palace was constructed out of large white stone bricks, and it was also being supported by tall and large stone pillars, each so wide they required several people to hug it completely. It was almost a hundred meters tall, so it looked imposing and majestic, but it was damaged in all sorts of places.

The ceilings had caved in on the internal structures, and the previously closed-up building had turned into something that looked rather like an open-air garden.

Garen flapped his wings and took flight, turning one circle in the air above the palace area.

The palace stood all alone in a valley, and he could barely see it at all from the sky.

There were many white stairs, concentrated in one area at the door to the hall, but many of the steps had been damaged. The two fire pillars guarding either side of the door had been snapped in half and fallen to the ground, while some of the beautiful and intricate carvings had been defaced beyond recognition.

Garen did not notice anything of value and was just about to leave this area.

Suddenly, his eyes glimpsed a strange statue outside the palace.

It was a grey-white statue standing in the midst of the snowstorm, and it looked just like a large hand with three fingers sticking out of the ground, reaching toward the sky.

There was nothing at all between the three fingers.

But Garen frowned slightly, because he knew this statue. He had always gotten his information from an assortment of sources, so he had practically forgotten which world he had gotten that information from. But one thing was for certain, this information did not come from this world.

A Projection Summoning Ritual?” The functions of this statue flashed past Garen’s heart.

“It’s clearly an object from another world, but it’s somehow here as well?” He landed down there curiously and stopped right in front of the statue.

Chapter 1299: Power 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Reaching out his claw and touching the statue, Garen felt a hairy, fleshy sensation on his claws.

The area in the middle of the sculpture seemed to have some type of strong electromagnetic field. It was a powerful energy field, separating the area in the middle into an isolated zone.

“More than 700 years ago, Caswell created the Universal Codex, which opened up the passage between the Void and this world.”

Suddenly, an aged, low voice sounded from behind Garen.

Garen turned around and saw a tall silhouette in a green robe standing in the snowy plains a distance away. The voice came from him.

The silhouette was in a cloak with a hood, concealing his face.

“Then, all of you Alien Souls also came here through the passage.” The silhouette raised his head slowly, revealing a fleshless skull beneath the cloak.

Two green flames burned in the place of the skull’s eyes, and a dark, red blood colored symbol was carved on his brow area, giving a strong religious aura.

More than a dozen black Suffering Knights were coming out slowly from the snow plains around. They were all wielding various types of weapons, some of them were armed with swords, some with long spears, and some even had a combination of sword and shield.

Two of the Suffering Knights had silver striation etched faintly on the edges of their armor.

“Silver-Striped Knights?” Garen raised his eyebrows.

Silver-Striped Knights were at the very least at Level Seven, and if an Undead Silver-Striped Knight was well nourished, it could easily turn into a Level-Eight creature.

“This time, for you to come over on your own accord, what’s your goal?” The skull asked in a low voice. “After killing three of my Suffering Knights, your soul is something that I will definitely capture and keep in a gem.”

It seems that this was a very cautious lich. Garen recognizes the identity of the skull figure standing in front of him, it was the Great Undead Wizard. It looked like he had transformed himself into a lich, an immortal existence.

He did not attack immediately just because Garen came here alone. He would also definitely have his other reinforcements around this area. To think that his opponent would still be so vigilant against him.

“If that’s the case, what else is there left to say?” Garen grinned. “There can only be one reason I came.”

“What?” The Lich started to be even more alert.

Garen sighed, releasing a puff of white air.

“To negotiate of course.”

He originally thought Garen was about to make his move, but he did not expect it to be this. The lich was obviously a little stunned by his proposal.

Boom!!

Suddenly, the white silhouette flashed in front of him. In just a blink of an eye, the body of the White Dragon expanded, reaching the size of a mature White Dragon as it charged straight towards him. At the next instant, Garen had already appeared right in front of him. It was almost like a teleport!

Roar!!!

In a burst, the Level Seven Dragonic Aura instantly condensed onto the Lich’s body.

The white dragon claws slammed on the Lich with tremendous force.

There was no sound. A transparent barrier had blocked Garen’s claws, with large amounts of transparent sparks spilling out at the point of contact.

The barrier blocked his attack for a full second, but that was already enough for the Lich to react.

He raised his hand, revealing a black bracelet on his wrist embedded with five different colored gems, one of it started glowing red.

“Loss of Reason.”

The sorcerer raised his voice to a high pitch.

A large, red net suddenly appeared in the air, it shrunk and wrapped Garen tightly with it.

This was a Level Eight spell, a unique spell formed by combining several different Psychic-type Manipulation spells 1 . Although it was only Level Eight, the practical effect was comparable to a Level Nine. It had been fixed onto the Lich’s bracelet and was released instantly.

To other powerful people, the Psychic influence might have required a bit more time for them to react to it. However, it was useless against Garen with his thoroughly trained will. Even Ann had praised that his willpower was comparable to Holy Spirits.

The red net disappeared without any reaction on Garen’s scales. There was absolutely no effect at all.

The green flames in the eye sockets of the Lich started burning more intensely as his bracelet released another spell once more. It was a shroud, black mist, engulfing Garen and his surroundings.

Its form changed so fast that even the surrounding Suffering Knights barely reacted in time. Two Silver-Striped Knights leaped a few meters in a blink of an eye, their two giant swords striking powerfully on the roots of Garen’s dragon wings.

“Death Spirit Energy?” Garen was shrouded in the black fog. He felt that this black fog was not some simple spell, but one that added some sort of unique potion. The potion could rapidly erode his scales’ resistance, minimizing his ability to resist magic.

He increased his alertness.

His wings flapped furiously as the two Silver-Striped Knights rushed over. In two flaps with a frightful eighty points of strength, the two Suffering Knights were flung away like a couple of chicks,

Although an undead Silver-Striped Knight was equivalent to a Level Eight, even when they were the same level they all had different specializations, some leaned towards strength and some leaned towards speed. In addition, at the same level, no one could compare against The Dragon Clan’s power when it came to direct confrontations. This was the law of the world!

The Level Eights of human and humanoid races are more dependent on techniques and special abilities, such as special equipment and so on.

Just as Garen smacked away the two Silver-Striped Knights, he heard the rest of the Suffering Knights roaring in unison.

“Final Death Match!!”

Bang!!

The red area instantly covered the entire space around him and Garen had once again found himself in a strange special space like last time.

The surrounding Suffering Knights all pulled out scrolls at the same time. They were ancient, yellow scrolls just like the last time, each of them tied with a red string.

“In the name of death!”

Their chants rippled through space.

The scrolls started to open up one by one. Amidst the black mist, various types of creatures slowly revealed itself.

Roar!!

There were actually gigantic-sized beasts hidden within the scrolls!

Amongst them were Level Eight Earth Dragon Beasts and even Level Nine Bone Dragons! There were also some weird and powerful species that he did not recognize.

In an instant, his enemies had nearly doubled their force.

Garen also felt a special threat could erupt at any moment, giving him a chilling and numb sensation.

He was no longer clueless about spells now, thus he immediately identified the origin of this feeling.

“Deathfinger!”

The Lich’s voice rang out suddenly.

Whoosh!

A light green ray suddenly pierced through the red space from some part within the inner wall, targeting Garen directly at his chest.

Garen instantly fell a chill shooting down his spine.

I have the body of the strongest white dragon at its peak performance level, I don’t believe that you can kill me just with one shot of that Deathfinger!!

Whoa!

Amidst a loud roar, Garen spread his wings out and released a terrifying ripple of energy waves from throughout his body. It is not an effect of a spell, but the energy ripples that was purely a result of him just exerting his power.

The muscles on his whole body started tensing up to its limit.

Galleon lunged up into the air. Without any intentions of retreating, he headed straight towards the light green ray.

The body of an Ancient Dragon-level creature was definitely enough to directly confront any Level Nine existences without any disadvantage.

The light green ray hit Garen’s body, turning his entire dragon body in a shade of green for a brief moment. Then, nothing happened, as if the attack had never happened at all.

“Level Nine!! Within such a short time, you!!” The Lich’s furious voice came from outside the red space.

At that moment, Garrn’s dragon body started to expand. His huge body that was comparable to an elephant crashed straight onto the inner wall of the red space.

The rest of the Suffering Knights behind him were trying to keep up with his speed, attacking him from the back when they finally did so. The Bone Dragons, the Earth Dragons, and the different weapons of the knights all slashed from different angles towards Garen’s dragon wings on his back.

Clank clank clank!!

Sounds of successive explosions were like clashing metal. Garen’s scales on his skin started to emit a white-gold glow.

Not only his wings but his entire body’s scales were pale white-gold.

Divine Statue Technique!!

This was the strongest Body Hardening Technique that Garen had learned back in the first world. Now, this technique had automatically activated as a self-defense mechanism.

Using the Divine Statue Technique with the body of a Colossal Dragon as a foundation, it had reached a terrifyingly extreme level. His level of defense had reached an absurdly overpowered level.

Initially, Garen’s average attribute points were not even close to ten points, but with the Divine Statue Technique, he was able to block bullets even with just his eyelids. It was the epitome of Body Hardening Techniques! It was invincible!

Now the Void Original Opus had been raised to 14%. The first restoration that was revealed turned out to this amazing secret technique from his first world.

The greatest use of the Void Original Opus was to be able to use all the worlds that Garen had experienced and all the abilities that he attained as a foundation, and then, fuse them together, ultimately forming the body of the True Soul!

Despite the countless weapons slashing on the Garen’s back, it had only left some faint white marks. It could not pierce through the skin even the slightest.

On the other hand, a few Bone Dragons used their huge body mass to try and knock Garen down but instead, he only moved forward slightly and the knocks served to add on to his momentum.

Garen concentrated his entire body’s strength and with a loud crash, slammed into the inner wall of the red space.

With a crack, the inner wall of the red space broke into pieces.

As the pieces came crumbling down, it revealed the Lich with a look of disbelief plastered all over his face.

The dragon claw lunged to grab the head of the Lich with an exploding force. It was so fast that even the afterimages could barely be seen, crashing onto the countless barrier spells in front of the Lich.

The black runes flowing in the air tried to block Garen’s claw but was instantly disintegrated. Immediately after that, a black locust-like smoke started flowing out, only to be dissipated even before coming into contact with Garen due to the immense shockwave from his claw.

The dragon’s claws were closing on to the Lich’s head. The threat of imminent death alarmed him.

The blood-colored symbols on his brow suddenly brightened up.

Ahh!!!

A huge and ferocious green succubus’s face appeared behind him. As the Lich’s mouth opened, a violent and sharp screech erupted in front of Garen.

“Succubus’ Wail!?” Garen’s heart tightened, “and it’s a full appearance of a succubus!!”

If the previous Deathfinger was a Level Seven spell upgraded into a Level Nine, then this Succubus’ Wail was definitely a real Level Nine spell. That would mean that the Lich in front of him right now had the gene of a banshee in his body before he turned into an Undead. Otherwise, it would be impossible to visualize the Void Shadow of a real banshee, and the Void Shadow would at least half the power of that skill!

The sound waves turned into a violent ripple of shockwaves, scraping through Garen’s body. Even his white-gold Divine Statue Technique started to show faint signs of damage.

The huge body shrunk. Garen shrunk from being an elephant size to that of an average human, in an attempt to minimize the ripples’ contact from the Succubus’ Wail.

Chapter 1300: Power 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It was not only affecting him, but even the Suffering Knights and summoned creatures behind him were injured heavily from the Level Nine spell. The Succubus’ Wail is basically a large-scale area-of-effect spell with friendly fire. If the Lich had not been forced into a corner, he would have never used this spell welded on his brow as the last resort.

“The Touch of Despair!”

Taking advantage while Garen was still under the effects of the Succubus’ Wail, the Lich’s body fluttered upwards, his hands started making a lot of complicated gestures at lightning speeds, sprinkling large amounts of mixed and messy powder of an unknown material.

A purple matrix emerged from below on the huge snowy plains.

The snow was quickly dyed dark purple, and huge purple tentacles that were a few meters in diameter sprouted out from the purple ground, wiggling straight towards Garen.

These tentacles were like an octopus’ tentacles. At the tip of the tentacles, it was densely packed with countless tiny suckers, whilst the suckers were covered with fine, sharp teeth.

A large number of tentacles tangled itself onto Garen, quickly weaving him into a giant purple meatball held high up in midair.

“I originally wanted to turn you into one of my undead! Unfortunately, you no longer have this opportunity! Now die for me!!” The green flames in the Lich’s eye sockets burned intensely. Just an instant earlier, he felt that he was about to be killed. That strong, intense feeling of a lethal threat was something he had not experienced for many years.

Just a genius of the White Dragon Clan? That was enough to damage him?

His hand, still holding up a gesture, moved down.

The purple meatball began to sink down swiftly. The snowy plains were no longer covered in snow. Everywhere the purple light touches had already connected to a different dimension. Once something was pulled in, it would directly enter the torrential dimension storm that was the habitat of countless monsters. The countless powerful and terrifying high-leveled monsters aside, even if one were to survive the monsters’ pursuits, without any specific landmarks or coordinates, he would only be left there to starve to death.

This was a spell that the Lich created himself. There were no other existences that could imitate it, and no existences could manage to find a countermeasure to it in such a short period of time. The only option for anyone caught in this was to keep on resisting and dodging.

Unfortunately, Garen’s spell power was far from reaching this level.

“How unfortunate, such a powerful Alien Soul…” The Lich looked at the purple meatball as it was slowly pulled down towards the purple ground. He had calmed down, albeit feeling sorry that he had to resort to this solution.

“These purple tentacles are from a huge creature called the Ruins Monster. Even the Dragon Clan’s Level Nine powerhouses won’t be able to escape. No matter how much of a genius you are, you’re still just a White Dragon!” The Lich grinned.

At this moment, the huge meatball began to slowly expand, getting bigger and bigger, and then contracting rapidly.

The green flames in the Lich’s eye sockets flickered wildly.

“No, it’s impossible to escape!”

However, the power of this spell completely repels any other external forces. He could only watch anxiously as the purple meatball stopped in mid-air, contracting big and small swiftly.

The green flames in the Lich’s eyes flickered faster. This spell was already his most powerful one. If his opponent managed to break free even under his most powerful spell, and he had already exhausted his arsenal of spells and half of his spell slots for the last two continuous Quicken effects, he had no way of fighting anymore again.

The white, bone finger gently touched the last black jewel on his bracelet. After a slight hesitation, the Lich still could not decide.

“Retreat!!”

He finally made up his mind, barking out loud.

Swiftly, all the Suffering Knights, summoned creatures and two Silver-Striped Knights who were still moving instantly grouped to protect the Lich. A cloud of dark smoke suddenly enveloped everyone. As the dark smoke dissipated, the Lich and all the Suffering Knights had disappeared completely.

Poof!!

The purple meatball burst from the inside, and Garen was covered all over with fine, small wounds. The white-gold scales cracking into what looked like countless glass shards.

Streaks of white blood dripped down slowly through the scales.

He burst out of the meatball and shot up into the sky. The enormous force ripped off the purple tentacles pulling onto him from underneath.

Roar!!!

He howled loudly as his wounds healed itself under the naked eye. This is the powerful effect of having an 80 point vitality attribute.

The power of this spell was horrifying. It was impossible for any other White Dragon to escape even at their peak performance. If not for the Divine Statue Technique, Garen knew he would not have been able to escape with only these light injuries.

The spell was strong enough to trap even the strongest Black Dragon at its peak!

“Lich…!” Just within this short fight, Garen had already understood the Lich’s power.

The Lich was definitely above him in terms of powers, he was no mere Level Nine. To be able to utilize and show the full Void Shadow potency of the Succubus’ Wail, he was very likely to be a Level Ten.

“If it was a formal fight, I wouldn’t even have stood a chance against him, but his insistence on wanting to kill me caused him to pay a hefty price. No wonder he retreated voluntarily.” Garen understood what was going on in his opponent’s mind after pondering about it.

If he could not kill a creature like a Lich from the roots of his soul, it would just cause him even more trouble in the future. As long as the Lich’s Phylactery was still there, the Lich will continuously reborn.

The purple matrix on the ground dimmed gradually. The huge monster roared to show its unwillingness to be defeated as its tentacles sank slowly back into the matrix.

“Unwilling to admit defeat?” Garon sneered as he looked down at the monster that is now only revealing its tentacles.

He took a deep breath.

Roar!!!

Roaring furiously downwards, the terrifyingly strong shockwaves slammed onto the tentacles. The entire matrix trembled slightly, and the rate of subsidence slowed down.

However, this was not the most crucial thing, but rather the fact that Garen’s body had once again started to grow. It went from the size of a horse to the size of two elephants in an instant. He was now twice as big as the average fully-matured White Dragon! Thick tubes of his Meridian system could be seen clearly, his muscles were twitching like running water.

“Die!”

Bam!

He stretched out a huge dragon claw, grabbed hardly onto a large clump of large purple tentacles, and pulled it up with all his might.

A shriek of pain screamed from within the matrix, which sounded like a combination of a lion and a tiger but also mixed with the cries of a mountain goat.

The serrated teeth on the tentacles sawed onto Garen’s dragon scales in a mad frenzy, but it could not hurt him except to barely leave a thin white mark on them.

Roar!!

Garen roared into the sky menacingly once more, shattering the layers of cloud. He grabbed madly on to the tentacles and pulled it upwards.

It was a competition of strength between these two huge forces. Garen’s strength was not as powerful as this monster, but he had effectively delayed the tentacles sinking down into the matrix. However, the purple light of the matrix was fading away at a higher speed than the sinking.

That was what Garen had hoped to achieve.

” Silibala, guyiee… 1 ” Suddenly a string of gibberish accompanied with the cries of an angry mountain goat rang out from the matrix.

It seemed to be a language, but it was not one that Garen understood. He ignored it and continued to pull on the tentacles so that they could not sink down instantly.

The voice suddenly changed to a different language, and in a span of tens of seconds, alternated into a dozen more languages.

Quickly, it managed to change to the Dragon language.

“You’re an Ancient Dragon!! Bloody hell, only an Ancient Dragon at its absolute peak could have such tremendous strength!! Let me go and I will compensate you!!” The sound of the mountain goat rang out in urgency.

Garen’s strength had far exceeded his expectations, and Garen was not afraid of his all-devouring sucker teeth. This was an outright miracle. He was just an ordinary White Dragon, but he had the strongest defense that only the Black Dragon Ancient Dragon at its peak could attain. If he knew this, he would have sent out his main tentacles to respond to the summon. That damned summoner Lich. Screw the dimensional agreement. If he could not retrieve his tentacles this time, his actual body’s will would directly be severed at the root of the dimensional link due to the Spacetime Dimensional Fissure. That would injure him fatally.

The Ruins Monster even wanted to devour the Lich’s heart at this point.

“Compensation?”

Garen laughed coldly. Suddenly, he realized something, the Ruins Monster’s strength had already become incapable of stopping him, seems like he was no longer an ordinary existence.

“So, you’re actually an intelligent species. Alright, I want you to sign a summoning agreement!! When I require aid, I can summon you for help!”

“The power required for the summoning agreement is not something you can afford,” the Ruins Monster said hurriedly. “You need 50 grams of Level Eight Soul Crystal powder, a power crystal of a creature that is at least Level Eleven! You can summon only my tentacles like the Lich. That way only Level Seven materials are needed.”

“No! I just want the summoning agreement! You deal with the materials!” Garen’s tone was firm. As the purple light of the matrix below started to fade away more and more, the Ruins Monster also started to panic more.

“Okay okay okay!! But only once! I have to pay a hundred times more materials than you and I can only afford it once! Any more than that and I’ll rather sacrifice this part of my will!” The Ruins Monster was pissed.

“Deal!”

Garen rapidly concussed his soul as a preparation to sign the agreement. A summoning agreement was no stranger to him as a Level Five Arcane Level. After a few lines of simple chants, he exchanged coordinate information with the Ruins Monster.

From the matrix, a black and purple bracelet flew out and automatically attached to Garen’s right claw.

The agreement was established, and the bracelet was the tool to summon the Ruins Monster.

This time, Garen was slightly wounded to the point where he spilled blood. If he did not get something out of it, he would have felt that it was not worth it.

Finally, he released the tentacles. With a whoosh, all the tentacles retreated swiftly into the matrix, and the purple light disappeared completely a moment later. The ground returned to its the original, snowy state.

Although he now had a one-time summoning agreement with the Ruins Monster, Garen did not intend to pursue the Lich to continue their bout.

Now, unless he wasted his one-time Ruins Monster summon, otherwise in a direct confrontation against the Lich, the two sides will be quite evenly matched. Furthermore, if he could not find the other’s Phylactery, even if he managed to critically damage or kill the Lich, his opponent can still reborn again in the future hence making no difference.

Speaking of which, the Lich may be stronger, but he also did not want to sacrifice too much as it was not worth the candle. Garen’s power was not as strong as the opponent. The two have reached a stalemate.

Staying in the snowy plains for a little longer, Garen rested until his body was completely recovered before flapping his wings and flying away.

With this attempt of testing the waters, he had also managed to preliminarily gauge his power. He had definitely surpassed the peak of Level Nine. With the Divine Statue Technique enhancing his dragon body, he was not even fazed by the confrontation of a Level Ten Lich.

Even within the clan, he no longer had to fear the Third Elders. With Garen’s current power, he could easily inflict critical damage to the Third Elders at any moment. After all, he was not a real Level Ten, but rather, he relied on the Divine Staff to reach this level, which was equivalent to the pseudo-Level-Ten.

Since he finally gained the power of self-protection, Garen had to start planning his next move.

In this war between the Mother River and this world, only by becoming a True Soul as soon as possible could he have the greatest chance of survival.

Thus, the first thing to do to reach a True Soul is to raise the Void Original Opus, and in turn, gain more Potential Points.

Chapter 1301: Leaving 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The only two ways to gain Potential Points were to either hunt for Demon Cores, or to absorb souls.

Garen took the previously obtained Soul Crystal out from the Space Ring he wore on his nail. After deliberating briefly, he did not absorb the crystal directly. Even if he absorbed a few of these crystals, he would only get more than a dozen Potential Points. Compared with this small amount, he had better use for them.

Unlike the Demon Cores, this type of Soul Crystals had actual souls imprisoned within them.

He quickly checked through the fatally injured Suffering Knights and summoned creatures sent by the Lich.

“These guys, even though they were in such a rush, they still didn’t forget to take back the cores. How stingy!” Garen silently checked though once more and found that these Suffering Knights and summoned creatures’ cores were ripped away, only leaving its empty, body shells.

He dragged the two corpses of the Suffering Knights away and looted the most expensive and valuable parts of the other summoned creatures.

In this fierce battle, the Space Ring on his body was already on the verge of breaking. Although the Space Equipment was hailed as the toughest item discovered, it still could not withstand the strength of such a Level Nine or Ten battle. To be able to survive through the entire fight was already an astounding feat.

Carrying a pile of loot, Garen spread his wings and flew towards the direction of the whereabouts of the clan.

******

Within the endless Void, there was a huge floating distorted palace.

The black color palace was constantly twisting around in shapes. Sometimes it seemed to be circular, sometimes square, and sometimes an extremely complex shape.

A white ring was slowly rotating around the palace. It was made up of countless white ants with wings. They all had human faces and sang while they orbited the palace.

The song they sang did not have any hint of rhythm, but it gave off a sense of mesmerizing illusory.

Inside the palace, on the edge of a green vortex, there were three tall stone pillars. Each of the pillars had one wide open eye, a bloodshot yet pale white eye.

They were staring at the center of the green vortex in front of them.

“Distortion Demon Master, our mission has been completed, now it’s all up to you guys.” A calm, male voice said from one of the eyes of the three stone pillars.

“Our Void Army is not something free for you to sacrifice without any reason.” The green whirlpool let out a plain, female voice. They were using the standard Void Language.

“You people are in the Mother River, so you can manipulate and control more creatures near the Mother River. Thus, you should be the one in charge. Furthermore, I had already sent an Upper-Level Demon King to test out the waters.”

“This is not the time for bargaining, if we don’t go all-out, our entire existence will soon be annihilated.” Another stone pillar urged on. The stone pillar’s eye was shining in a hazy light.

“The Demon Masters we know is barely a fraction out of the Void. The Void is an endless abyss. There are still a lot of terrifying Demon Masters that we can’t even hope to make contact. There are more of them than there is sand in the sea. We’ll just have to deal with it as it comes.” The voice of another man sounded from the vortex.

“No matter how good your True Souls or our Demon Masters are, we’re still actually not the real main force. When the time comes to take action, it is not up to us but the Void and the Mother River.” A child’s voice rang out from the vortex.

“The Dimensional Crevice had already passed through the Crystal Wall System. A large number of the vanguard squad had already entered the Primary Plane and other planes.”

“The best channel of infiltration should be in the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains. That place is already chaotic enough with all the Demon Essence so they wouldn’t care if we enter.”

“I think we should go for Purgatory, the creatures there are sly and cunning. Perhaps we can persuade them to join us. The Void and the Mother River are incomparably great, that universe can never beat us.”

“How to deal with the Gods? That is the key.”

“Gods?”

One of the True Souls sank down.

“I checked it out once. They are almost omnipotent and invincible in the Divine Kingdom. It’s still doable if we were up against a Lower God, but a Middle God and the Upper God are going to be really difficult to handle.”

“The foundations of the Gods lies in the power of faith. We can initiate a war of faith to weaken them.”

“That’s too slow. We can’t afford to wait that long. The best solution is to lure out their Incarnations and Projections to exhaust their Divine Power.”

“How can we lure them out?”

“There are a few ways… The simplest one is to get a blasphemous Divine Soul with power that can overwhelm even the strongest of mortal existences.”

“To find an existence like that, I might have a good idea.”

For a moment, everyone fell silent.

******

Heavens

God of Light and Fire’s Divine Kingdom.

The Central Divine Kingdom was situated at the peak of the Mountain of Heavens. The whole Divine Kingdom was simply just a huge burning white flame on the top of the mountain.

The flames were eternal, constantly releasing a fearsome amount of light and heat. It was nearly half as large as the entire Primary Plane.

At the core of the flame, a huge crystal ball wobbled up and down slowly in the air.

There were rivers and hills within the crystal ball, countless creatures laboring in farms, angels with white and black wings patrolling in the sky, and even various Elemental lifeforms residing there.

Inside the crystal ball, at the center of it all was a huge and luxurious, pure white temple.

In the temple, all the Gods of Light and Gods of Fire were gathered there at this time.

The Major God Fehra sat on a golden-white throne at the top of the room, overlooking the projections of dozens of different Gods below.

“Welcome to the Throne of the Gods.”

A huge and majestic voice resoundingly rang out from Fehra.

His current attire was a White-Gold armor set. Wielding a sword and shield on each arm, he wore a green garland symbolizing peace in front of his chest.

This attire represented both offense and defense, signaling a desire to maintain peace.

Fehra’s face shined with a white light, concealing his face. The perennial imagination of idealistic perfection by his countless believers made his Godhead to have a fixed appearance. In different people’s minds, he will appear in the perfect, aesthetic form conforming the ideals of a person’s heart.

Hence, Fehra had another God name, and that is the Thousand-Faced God.

Below the temple, the two sides were filled with seats of different sizes, some looked fancy, some plain, some horribly complicated, some simple and elegant.

The Gods with concealed or exposed faces were all seated on the seats. Some of them were surrounded by faint colored halos, some were wearing flowing snake-like sashes, and the God of Knowledge had countless books behind him fading in and out of existence. There was also Shar who looked like an enchanting woman shrouded in darkness, and so on.

Fehra looked down at the gods.

The Goddess of Darkness and Shadow Weaves Shar, the Goddess of Magic and Weaves Mystra. There was also the War God, the Thunder God, the God of the Storm, and the Lord of Darkness and Death.

These six Gods were all Higher Gods, each with their own independent Divine System and huge forces. They allied with Fehra and were of near equal standing.

The rest of the gods were Middle or Lower Gods, and could only be dismissed as side characters.

“Major God Fehra, why have you called upon us?” Mystra was the youngest of all the Upper Gods. Her appointment was due to an excessively ignorant Arcanist that got demoted into a Lower God. Thus, she only had a mere few thousand years of experience as the Goddess of Magic and Weave.

“Goddess Mystra, in the areas you are involved in, have you noticed that there are more and more dimensional crevices recently? The alien creatures entering the space of our universe getting denser and denser?” Fehra asked in a low voice.

“Naturally I’ve noticed,” Mystra replied in affirmation. “This is a very strange phenomenon. In the last Centennial Conference, we found that the universe is starting to show very serious signs of rapid growth. This is not a good sign, despite the growth is very strong.”

“That’s right, we are pursuing absolute stability and balance. If we grow too fast, it will inevitably bring about a very rapid decline. It’s a law that what goes up must come down.” The God of Knowledge who was an old man with white hair and a beard answered calmly.

“The Weaves I manage are getting more and more energy. After checking the statistics, I’ve noticed that the source of these energies originated from the alien creatures that entered our universe,” Mystra continued. “I presume Miss Shadow feels the same?”

Shar was standing directly opposite her. She nodded slightly but did not make a sound. She was a charming woman in a black skirt and black veil. Similar to the Lord of Light and Fire, no one could see her face as it was only a black blur.

“Rumor has it that the Divine Statue of the Major Gods in the Primary Plane was vandalized by alien creatures some time ago?” The War God asked. Clad in golden armor, this Divine Soul with his eyes under the helmet constantly emitted golden light. He was blunt and straight to the point.

“This was also the other reason I have summoned you to this Conference of the Gods,” Fehra nodded. “Mother Nature had refused to meet with me. There might still be some trauma and suffering that she still feels from the last Holy War. The Dragon of Eternity had disappeared, his whereabouts have yet to be found. The Dragon Gods are all fighting each other, splitting into different factions. Now, the only ones who can deal with this the situation are just us.”

“What do you mean?” The mustached Thunder God asked, lightning surging throughout his body at all times. “Even when we’re at our strongest, there are alien creatures who dared to actively provoke us and destroy the Divine statues? This… was not an accident?”

“Perhaps it’s a warning,” Fehra nodded. “Let us tally up the amount of Dimensional Crevices for now. As for large crevices, it is still best to send some God-Favored to observe and monitor them.”

“We’ll act according to your will.”

The Gods responded in unison.

******

Deladia Empire.

White Dragon Clan

“You want to apply leave?” The Third Elder frowned, looked at Garen in front of him. He was a talented genius and the best hope the clan had. Now he wanted to apply for a long-term leave for an external mission, hoping to leave the clan to go elsewhere.

“Yes,” Garen responded softly in the cave.

“The clan can no longer satisfy my desire to improve, I want to go to the outside world to train myself.”

This clan is indeed too barren. The White Dragons have little access to general knowledge and lacked anyone to interact with. If it were not for Ann’s books, he might not have any understanding about the entire plane now.

Without support from the Deladia Empire, it is estimated that the clan would have to start controlling their population.

Holding his staff, The Third Elder turned around and took a few steps. He seemed to be very hesitant.

“Regarding your request, I can understand where you’re coming from… So, where are you planning to go?” He was actually very reluctant to let Garen leave, but he also knew that Garen was the only remaining hope in the clan with a chance to become the White Dragon King. All hopes of returning to White Dragon Mountain and regain power laid on him.

This was also the key reason for his tolerance of Garen to the point of ignoring even his own flesh and blood.

“Within the Four Great Territories of the Primary Plane, except for the neutral domain, all of them are the territories of various Gods. Even the largest Neutral Domain, it is still split up into territories of the various Gods of the Mother Nature Divine System. What the Gods are pursuing is peace, but I hope to kill to prove my courage and strength.” Garen had long decided on where to go, but he still had to explain his reasoning.

“If that’s the case, that narrows down your choices,” The Third Elder now understood his intent.

“I will first go to Snow City and participate in the war,” Garen succinctly said.

“Snow City… That’s a gathering ground for the Arcanists. The Arcanists don’t even care about Mystra and Shar. They brag about being the true center of the universe. It is too dangerous for you to go there,” The Third Elder warned.

“Wait till you’ve reached Level Eight, then at least you’d be safer.”

Chapter 1302: Leaving 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen’s actual combat power was already at Level Ten, but naturally, he had no way of knowing that. But no matter what, the Third Elder’s words right now was sincere with care, he was truly worried for Garen. There was not even a hint of self-interest in his intentions. That was because he was the clan’s only hope right now.

When Garen said Snow City, he was actually referring to the Ten Thousand Abyss Plains and participating in the Blood Wars there. At the same time, he could also absorb more souls to improve himself. He was much more efficient than the demons. If he can quickly gain a foothold in the Blood Wars, then he would be able to acquire a large number of souls in a very short time, then transform them into Potential Points, rapidly upgrading the Void Original Opus.

Moreover, there was another reason he wanted to go to Snow City, which is to build a Wizard Tower.

Garen needed a Wizard Tower to conduct his own spell research. Only the Arcanists who did not rely on Weaves could complete the construction of a Wizard Tower fitting a dragon. There were too many complicated issues that he can never resolve on his own. There was the issue of a large number of materials needed, various matrices of runes, spells and enchantments, Tower Souls and etc.

The Wizard Tower that he wanted must be able to block out the power of Divine Souls completely, creating a safe place just for himself. These things require at least a hundred years of academic research, and before that, you would have to have something to research on. There were countless mysteries and knowledge accumulated by countless wizards and scholars in the past. The average wizard had no way of learning or even coming into contact with all these.

Regrettably, Ann did not have knowledge in this area. Therefore, Garen could only set his eyes on the Snow City.

If he had his own Wizard Tower, his spell level will quickly break through the bottleneck and break through the limits of the plane. Even if he enters the abyss, he would be able to deal with it. This way, he would be able to resist the effects of space-time spells. After all, in this world, no matter how strong a body was, it still could not withstand space-time distortion. Even if you were unparalleled in strength, a direct Teleportation Spell would just send you into a very distant place, or a Banishment Spell would just expel you into the Astral Space. That was essentially the dumping grounds for the Eternal Gods. There was no food or drinks, just a hunting ground for Astral Space Monsters.

These may still be considered as good outcomes, but the most troublesome outcome was forced into some layers of the Abyss. The endless Abyss had certain layers that one could only enter but never exit, it had an even stronger gravitational pull than a black hole. Once one was sent inside, one can only remain in there forever, with no hopes of escaping.

Therefore, for any dragon, the early physical training was only for self-protection. After ensuring their ability of self-protection, they will start plundering wealth and knowledge, then eventually starting to pursue arcane and wisdom.

That was the reason why the White Dragon Clan would always send their geniuses to participate in the Dragon Clan’s Gifted Camp, where any dragon would be able to attain a large amount of knowledge.

Unfortunately, due to a series of radical moves such as the alliance with the Deladia Empire, the White Dragon Clan had lost the right to send a participant. They were completely isolated by White Dragon Mountain and the other Dragon Clans.

“Since you’ve already decided, then maybe I can give you some help for your journey.” The Third Elder sighed as he said reluctantly.

With a wave of his staff, a book with a thick, amber cover appeared in the air. The book was very heavy, looking no different from a piece of brick.

“This is the spell book I used when I was young. There are some useful spells recorded inside, but it’s all simple low-level spells, but you may be able to use it at a critical time.”

Garen accepted the book and opened it. Scanning through it, there were a lot of identification spells, enchanting spells, memory falsifications, human charming, and invisibility spells.

The spells were all non-lethal, but they were surely very practical in real life.

Furthermore, Garen noticed that the material of this spellbook was of a high quality.

“This book can record up to Level Nine spells, it should be enough for you to use for many years. When you pass Level Nine, you would naturally have enough time and strength to make an even better spellbook yourself.” The Third Elder said quietly.

“Thank you, Elder.” Garen thanked, and bowed slightly as a sign of gratitude.

“This is a space earring, you can store items you don’t need in there.” The Third Elder continued to give him stuff.

After a bunch of different things was given to Garen, he gave his final advice.

“As for your brothers and sisters, the clan will take care of them. In addition, we have news that your mother – your birth mother, Iris, is currently somewhere near Snow City. If you want, you can go find her. I heard that she had settled down with a Red Dragon over there.”

“Iris…” Garen frowned without saying anything.

He had no lasting memories of that dragon mother he had in this lifetime. Not long after he was born, she had already abandoned him.

“Lastly,” The Third Elder had an expression of sincerity. “For the clan, I hope you can promise me one thing before you leave.”

Garen had never seen this side of him and was lightly shocked by it.

“Please, tell me.”

” Please leave some descendants for the clan 1 .”

“…”

*******

Mating, that was an issue that every clan could not afford to avoid or underestimate.

If it was human mating, Garen might still be interested, but if his partner is going to be a female dragon…

That was a bit too much…

However, since it was the final favor from the Third Elder, he could not reject him. As the most talented genius of the clan, passing down the best genes for the clan was the duty that everyone in the Dragon Clans would do.

Garen agreed to do it, his original intention was to use a spell to charm some of them and get it over with. However, he did not expect all these female dragons to be wearing the Immunity Necklace distributed by the Third Elder. It was able to block spells including all charm spells that were below Level Eight.

Fifteen young dragons were chosen from the clan. Just like the emperor selecting his concubine, they were all available for Garen to pick from to mate with. Of course, it was called an interaction session on the surface…

“I feel that I’m still not mentally prepared yet…” Garen looked at the row of young female dragons standing side by side in his cave. Some were slender, some voluptuous, some muscular, some thin, there were even some that were long or petite. There were all kinds of body types.

A larger amount of dragon whelps had grown to become young dragons in the past few years, and this has given the Third Elder more selection options.

“Never mind, the elder said you can have us any time you want, as long as you want it,” A female dragon grinned seductively.

“Yeah yeah, we’re all ready for you. We’ll stay here for ten days. The Elder already said you can’t afford to rest these ten days.” Another small female dragon urged on.

“Ten days…” Garen had mixed feelings as he glanced at Satwo and the other dragons standing at the side looking at him in envy. That’s the thing with different tastes and preferences.

If only they could use the Ultimate Transforming Spell and turn into humans.

He thought helplessly, but he knew that was impossible. If an average dragon could turn into humans like Ann, there would not even be any need for him to pick. However, that kind of powerhouse would be at least Level Nine or Ten.

“Above Level Nine or Ten?” Thinking of this, Garen was even more motivated to increase his Arcane level. Once he reaches Level Nine or even Level Ten, he would be able to use the Ultimate Transformation Technique to take a human form. Then, he could use his dragon form purely as a battle form and transform as necessary.

The Ultimate Transformation Spell was a powerful Level Nine spell. To turn someone from the Dragon Clan to take a human form, it would at least require the power of the Level Nine peak. Furthermore, in the transformation process, the one being transformed will have everything about them exposed to the spellcaster’s eyes. There would be nothing they could hide so there might not be any creatures who would want someone else to help them use the Ultimate Transformation Spell.

“Lord Garen, are you going to pick one of use, or are we just gonna have an orgy?” A female dragon with weirdly white scales openly said.

“Since you’re so strong, I wonder if I would be able to take it?”

“Yeah yeah, when I think about how massive your **** is and how **** 2 , my heart can’t stop thumping.”

“I’m scared, but I want it so bad…”

These bunch of female dragons was shameless enough to say anything. Even Satwo and the other dragon whelps at the side could not take it anymore, escaping the cave with blushed faces.

“Alright alright! Everyone shut up!!” Garen was in a daze from the commotion and roared.

He strode towards his own cave. With a bang, a huge boulder blocked the cave’s entrance.

“One by one! Enter one by one! All of you, queue up!”

His impatient voice rang out from the cave.

Being forced into a corner, he could only use that move…

The group of female dragons looked at each other.

Everyone was silent for a brief moment.

“Me first! Me first!!”

“Me!”

“No, I’m first!!”

The female dragons all started to sign up.

“How open…” The Third Elder let out a sigh outside the cave. There was a hint of envy in his eyes as he looked at the group of young female dragons all signing up voluntarily.

“I’m getting old… Old…”

He turned around and spread his wings, flying back to his own cave.

******

Ten days later…

Garen flew away from the Clan, leaving behind a completely limp young female dragon. Forcefully resisting his uncomfortableness, he used a method that was the best of both worlds.

Waiting after the elder had left, he knocked out one of the White Dragon Guards and picked one of the female dragons. He then enjoyed himself for ten days, telling the remaining young female dragons that he liked that young female dragon and that the rest can leave.

Under Garen’s manipulation, the two unconscious dragons enjoyed ten days of purely hedonistic life. Every day, they ate while unconscious, slept while unconscious, and fucked while unconscious…

Without a hitch, the young female dragon got pregnant.

Garen put up an exhausted expression as he left the cave. The young female dragon he coincidentally picked was quite a beautiful one, but she was also obviously the type with a shady private life.

This way, even if it was not his seed that impregnated her, everyone would just chalk it up to bad luck. After all, this young female dragon had had too many partners, so given the circumstances, it was still understandable.

After resolving this issue, he hurriedly escaped from the clan and headed towards Snow City.

He was not alone, there were also two Dragon Guards assigned as his bodyguards.

The two Dragon Guards were assigned to Garen by Phosphorus in good faith. Both of the dragon guards were Phosphorus’ children and were full-fledged Level Eight White Dragons who were abnormally strong.

However, with that, Garen had no way of bidding farewell to Ann. He could only just continue on towards Snow City.

Chapter 1303: Underground 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Along the way, there were no accidents, let alone bandits and other obstacles. Facing a line of three White Dragons, the creature from the legends, even Golden Knights would not dare to stop them. Currently, in the Deladia Empire, White Dragons were equivalent to royalty because the Eternal Contract was largely reached due to the White Dragons. The Red Dragons and the other Dragon Clans were only there in name, only the White Dragons were the ones who fully supported it.

The clan was a long distance from the Snow City. After flying for more than ten days with a few pitstops in between, Garen finally saw the border of the Snow City. The border towers were lit up with lights, serving both as a guiding light and a warning. It illuminated the passing roads at night like a lighthouse.

The three White Dragons landed slowly on the edge of the tower, and the soldiers there had already run out to give warnings.

The border tower in the sea of forests was obviously just there as a warning. The ones that came out were just average Level Two elite warriors. It was most likely because this place was facing the dragon clan’s habitat that they only had stationed a Level Two elite at this place.

“Three lords, what are you planning to go to Snow City for?” The stationed soldier at the tower shouted loudly.

The distance between the two sides was more than ten meters, hence he had to raise his voice.

“Yes, please report the situation.” Garen knew the rules. One of the Dragon Guards around him flashed a white-gold shield-shaped badge. That was a special symbol issued by the Deladia Empire to the clan.

The border tower immediately emitted a force. Almost as if a magic spell, the force immediately transmitted far and faded away. The speed was amazing.

Soon, Garen sensed faintly that they were being spied on.

“Who’s there spying on me!” Garen narrowed his eyes. His dragon eyes instantly looking up towards the sky above him. There seemed to be a patch of dark clouds that made the area look like nighttime. Instantly, a transparent distortion flashed up.

“Sorry sorry, it might have been the Snow City Wizard Guard Lords coming over to check on things. Please calm your anger, Lord White Dragons!” The warrior at the border tower urgently explained.

Garen nodded, seemingly relieved. Both the Dragon Guards were a little shocked. They had felt something was slightly off earlier, but they did not expect it to be a wizard snooping on them.

“It was a Prophecy-type Wizard, they specialize in such spells. I’ve encountered them on the battlefield before,” one of the Dragon Guards said with a disgusted face.

“These damned Prophecy Wizards. The stronger ones could even investigate the exact time that you went to the toilet.”

Garon chuckled and said nothing.

Very soon, the wizards’ check was completed. Another force was transmitted back from a distance away.

“Three lords, you may enter the borders now.” The border tower warriors respectfully saluted.

Finally, Garen and company spread their wings and flew off. As White Dragons, they are considered very well-tempered out of the Dragon Clans. They calmly awaited the human’s border check to get permission to enter. They fully complied with the visiting procedure without a complaint.

If you go to other countries, these actions were considered very rare. However, in the face of Snow City, the Arcane Center of the Northlands, this was the gathering grounds of the top Arcanists of the entire Northlands. Even if it were the Dragon Clans, they would still have to have at least some etiquette.

The three dragons glided through the sky, effortlessly moving with the wind.

“Speaking of which, why are you guys, Dragon Guards, willing to stay in the clan to work? Why not go out and live alone?”

Feeling excessively bored, Garen asked the two Dragons Guards.

The two Dragon Guards were called Ken and Annie. One was male and the other female.

“Living alone? You mean those stupid dragons who sneaked out, then got cut up by humans and other races and have its entire body made into materials?” Ken laughed. “We, as White Dragons, have a bad reputation. We would probably get ganged up on in most places we go to. Even in the current region where everywhere is filled with chaos, Dimensional Cracks can still swallow even the strongest Dragon Clans whole. There are even a bunch of them who got captured and turned into pets for others to ride on!”

“That’s right, Lord Garen, you need to be very careful of one person when you get to Snow City,” Annie was calmer in her warnings.

“Who’s that?”

“Dragon Wizard Asilia,” Annie said a name that Garen seemed to have heard of.

“Dragon Wizard? The guy who specializes in capturing the dragons and forcing them to sign master-servant contracts?” Garen recalled of this character now. He was one of the figures that the Third Elder warned him about before he left.

“Yes, Dragon Wizard likes to force all the special and powerful dragons to sign contracts with her, and it’s always master-servant contracts. She has an irregular passion towards talented dragons. You should be careful not to be targeted by her,” Annie warned.

Garen smiled, not paying much heed to their warnings. With his hidden strength, as long as the Level Ten Great Arcanists of the Snow City Joint Council did not take action, the rest of the existences, even at their peak, would have no chance against him. No one would be able to do anything about him. Moreover, his growth rate had already far exceeded the imagination of these people. It would not take long before he would leave them in the dust.

“My goal is to build a Wizard Tower, break through my own bottleneck. I’ll try to stay low-key as much as possible.” That was the plan he decided on.

“I heard that there are five Dragon Clans under the Dragon Wizard: the Red Dragons, the Black Dragons, the Brass Dragons, and the Purple Dragon 1 s. Although it was a master-servant contract, due to her generous summoning rewards and an extremely powerful backer supporting her, all the Dragon Clans are extremely tolerant of her,” Annie whispered.

“Backer huh?” Garon got a bit of a headache thinking about that. He hoped that this Dragon Wizard would not set her sights on him. He was just some average genius in the White Dragon Clan. The Dragon Wizard’s backer was actually the biggest and most powerful existence of Snow City, the owner of the Silver Tower, the Speaker of the Joint Council, the boss of Snow City, and the one known as the strongest wizard of the Northlands – Urvac Dragon. He was a peak Level Fifteen Great Arcanist.

This guy had already reached Level Fifteen three hundred years ago. Who knows what level he was actually at right now. In the Deladia Empire, for Snow City to be able to stand on equal footing with the Royal Families, it was all due to his efforts.

Not only did Snow City have Arcanists and Wizards, but it also has churches of various Gods stationed here. Although they were oddly unpopular and did not have the respect of a lot of Wizards, these forces still made the situation in Snow City even more complicated.

Garen did not want to think too much about it. He had two main purposes for going to Snow City. First, build a Wizard Tower. Second, find the Soaring Wing King and go to the Abyss to participate in the Blood War. Only through the Blood War could he collect Potential Points at the fastest rate.

Entering the borders of the Snow City, Garen and company started to put their guard up. The closer they were to the place with the most amount of Deladia Wizards, the more nervous they got. The number of powerhouses who could threaten them was too high. After these people got to Level Five, they could easily increase their lifespan. Hence, there were many old guys who have lived for hundreds of years hidden in this ancient city, or maybe in the Snow Mountain Library, the Balloon Planetarium, the Silver Tower, or even in an inconspicuous corner of the city.

There were too many strong wizards staying in this place.

Some of their Wizard Levels were probably not that high, but under dire circumstances, they would definitely have some sort of trump card, and would still be able to defeat a Level Eight White Dragon.

As the sun set, Garen and company started to land to take a short break.

Taking this opportunity to pretend to sleep, Garen entered the Dream World to contact the Soaring Wing King. After all, Garen had just arrived in his territory, it was only appropriate to give him a greeting. Garen might even require help in the future.

Luckily, in the past, he had exchanged a lot of information about the empire to the Soaring Wing King, so both parties were quite satisfied with their cooperative relationship. Some of his knowledge from Ann and his understanding of the entire Plane Universe had also helped the Soaring Wing King a lot.

At the halfway point of a cliff of a mountain, the three White Dragons entered an abandoned cave and started to rest.

His consciousness sank into the depths.

In a black villa covered with bright concave windows, one could see the white but overcast sky through the glass.

When Garen woke up, this was the scene he saw.

He stood up in the room with a human body. The room only had a set of white sofas and nothing else. They were old and worn out leather sofas. The walls around the room were a gloomy gray.

Whoosh!

A huge black shadow flashed by the window. It seemed to be a huge black crow, flying around the villa. Other than the sound of its wings flapping, nothing else could be heard.

The shadows continue to flash by the windows, over and over, seemingly with a rhythm.

Every 13.56 seconds, it would pass by the window very punctually.

As Garen observed the black shadow outside the window, unbeknownst to him, an old man in a white robe was already seated on the sofa.

“I just received the news that you’re about to arrive.” The old man looked kind and gentle. He had a bit of a widow’s peak, and his hair and beard were pure white.

“You really never give up on your tendency of flying freely at all times,” Garen replied cheekily.

The old man laughed.

“That’s why I’m called the Soaring Wing King.”

“Alright, let’s skip the talk of your life motto. The reason I came to your territory this time is that I want to build a Wizard Tower. A Wizard Tower appropriate for a dragon. At the same time, I hope you can send me out to the Blood War,” Garen said bluntly. Looking at the old man’s stunned expression, he continued, “I know that a Wizard Tower for a dragon requires far more resources as compared to an average human, but name a price, I’ll find a way.”

“Price? It needs to be something of equal value to your request.” Soaring Wing King shook his head as he frowned. “What Level do you want it to be, and where do you want it built? What about the Level of the Tower Souls? To block out Divine Power you’ll need enchantment and reinforcement by at least a Level Nine Wizard. Furthermore, the cost of using it would also be high, your spiritual energy may also be downgraded. Are you sure you can afford it?”

Garen had already readied himself for this.

“Of course I know that, but I will still need an estimated quotation, then only will I be able to prepare what’s required. I want the best Upper-Level Wizard Tower. It needs to have an Elemental Pond, a Dimensional Anchor, and all the essential facilities.”

Soaring Wing King glanced at him oddly. “Why don’t you wait till you get a human body, then build an even better Wizard Tower? A dragon’s body is too big, the number of resources you’re going to need would be more than fifty times of what an average Wizard Tower of the same level would require.”

“Hmm… That’s actually not a bad idea.” Garen already knew that the expenses would be very high. “Unfortunately, I can’t afford to find a stranger to cast the Ultimate Transformation Spell on me. Well, just give me an estimated quotation for the time being, the location doesn’t matter.”

“The expenses for the highest level Wizard Tower with all standard facilities will roughly be above one billion gold coins, and that’s not including all the rare materials you need to prepare yourself. For you, the standard would be around five to ten times higher so you can estimate the costs for yourself. As for a permanent enchantment to block off Divine Power, the cost of that Level Nine spell would at least require you to give up some rare and precious treasure in exchange for it…”

Chapter 1304: Underground 2

Chapter 1304: Underground 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Although Garen was mentally prepared for it, he was still shocked by this figure. On one hand, gold coins were not worth very much at all in Snow City. Given the high cost of living, the buying power of one gold coin was equivalent to ten dollars back on Earth. But even if it was only ten dollars, more than one billion gold coins would still amount to more than ten billion in cost, and this was excluding the many rare materials that he needed to prepare himself. He also needed to exchange a treasure for that Eternal Divine Power Insulation Enchantment.

“What do I say? As expected of peak-level Wizard Tower equipment…” Garen sighed.

“As long as you get it.” The Soaring Wing King laughed. “I’ll give you a list of the materials you need to prepare on your own. I can help you with the basic construction fees, but my hands are tied with the materials. Many of those things are extinct now, the highest-level Wizard Towers now were all constructed thousands of years ago. That’s why you need to prepare them yourself.”

He was a higher-up in Snow City, and a billion gold coins were nothing to him, seeing as his current net worth was at least several tens of billions. Still, he naturally would not fork out that sum for nothing.

“What do you want in return?” Of course, Garen knew that there was no such thing as a free lunch.

The Soaring Wing King smiled mysteriously.

“Do me a big favor…”

*******************

Once he retreated from the Dream World, Garen sank into deep thought. The requirement the Soaring Wing King wanted in return was slightly too high up the danger scale.

But he had no other choice than to borrow the Soaring Wing King’s power in order to build the Wizard Tower. That was why he had to consider the pros and cons on both sides.

The shadow of the Mother Stream Alliance was peeking out slightly from behind the Soaring Wing King’s back.

The Soaring Wing King seemed to be a direct subordinate of the Mother Stream Alliance. In fact, Garen had received an invitation from the Mother Stream Alliance back then as well, but sadly he did not manage to reply to it before he was accidentally swept into this World.

“I still don’t have enough information, and there’s only so much I can do on my own…” Garen sighed. If he had a strong enough influence, he would be able to save a great deal of energy in terms of collecting money and materials, and then he would not have to ask such a big favor of the Soaring Wing King. And without enough information, he might accidentally be dragged by the Mother Stream Alliance into becoming cannon fodder at the front lines. Now, that would be a tragedy.

Even an upper-level Demon Lord Level Thousand-Armed Giant could be tossed out as cannon fodder, what was more a middle-level Demon Lord like him.

Although the dragons were rich, several billion gold coins… was still a staggering sum to give away… Most Adult Colossal Dragons had about ten million gold coins, and that was already rather considerable. Those who had a hundred million were impressive indeed.

He fretted over it overnight and continued on his way the next day. When he was just about to reach Snow City, for some reason, the summoning forces that he had not seen for a while suddenly rang out again in Garen’s brain.

He had almost forgotten that he still had an impromptu Summoning Contract.

This was a mandatory contract, so he had no choice but to go. Helpless, he ordered the two Dragon Guards to find a crevice and stay there for now, awaiting his return. The duration of the summon was very short, a few days at most, so he could return quickly after he solved the problem.

*******************

In the dark Underground City

It had been a very, very long time since Kevin entered the ruins.

The tunnel had been sealed off, and Blue Void led everyone further into the depths, as though he wanted to reach the core of the earth. They encountered too many troubles along the way, and the Contractors even summoned almost a half of their dragons. Even so, they just managed to hang in there, losing a great many of their team members on the way.

But after he exchanged information with the Empire for the last time, Blue Void continued to lead everyone into the deepest parts of the Underground City without a hint of hesitation.

The entire Underground City was filled with abandoned houses, empty and dim grey-black abandoned buildings. There were no living creatures, no movement whatsoever, and the dust was piled up on the ground and inside the house. If they knocked down a door by accident, they would send dust flying up in the air for a very long time.

Thankfully, they had all brought more than enough food and water, so all of them managed to hang in there and could continue to hang in there for several years. They encountered many traps as they went, but Blue Void’s men dismantled every single one of them.

There was no sun nor light in the Underground City, only the undead.

There were zombies, skeletons, corpses, and ghosts, each without wills, wandering around aimlessly.

Kevin sat in his own tent, looking at the pitch-black arc above the Underground City. Other than the tiny bit of light from their own campsite, there was no sign of light at all outside, and they could not see anything.

His tent was surrounded by the many tents of the other Contractors, and outside the rings of Contractors, there were more than ten dragons curled up on the ground, resting. Most of them were Red, Blue, Green, and White Dragons. There was only one Black Dragon.

Even beyond that, there was the campsite’s campfire.

There was nothing else any further than that, at the very outside. There was only a sea of dark, dusty abandoned buildings.

“If only we could live inside those abandoned buildings,” said his daughter Maria softly as she walked to the entrance of her recently-illuminated tent.

“How long are we going to stay here?” said Ice Orchid, a friend she had just made along the way, helplessly. This female Wizard, dressed in blue robes, was not a Contractor, but she had become good friends with Maria, so they lived in Kevin’s tent together. These tents looked quite small, but in truth they could be divided into several rooms inside, so they were actually quite large. There were many items and furniture in there. The Wizards could use spells to produce water, and although it was not much, it was still enough to drink. On the other hand, it was unfortunate but the water was not enough for them to bathe.

That was also the problem that troubled everyone the most.

“It should be soon,” Kevin replied in a low voice. “Master Blue Void is already picking up the pace, apparently the scouts at the front discovered something big.”

“Yeah, I noticed it too. All of the Wizards specializing in Necromancy have been summoned over for a discussion, so clearly the next obstacle ahead of us is a result of Necromancy again.” Ice Orchid clearly had her own plans throughout the journey. This pretty female Wizard had a very clear goal, and that was to find and stick to a Contractor, so that she could rely on the power of the dragons to obtain better treatment while also keeping herself safe.

Maria was a simple-minded person, so she did not notice, but Kevin realized it a long time ago. However, he thought that perhaps another Wizard would keep them that much safer, so he tolerated her.

Kevin walked out of the tent. Half of the Contractors around him had already summoned their dragon companion, but he still refused to. The excuse he gave his daughter was that the price was too high.

“At such a critical moment, should you summon your companion, Master Kevin? If you can’t contribute when the time comes, we won’t get a share of the goods,” Ice Orchid suggested softly, walking up to Ice Orchid.

She did not attempt to hide her voice at all, and some curious gazes instantly peeped out of the few tents around theirs. Along the way, Kevin had also had his share of conflicts with the other Wizards. Even though he tried to tolerate whatever he could, there was still no avoiding the voices of dissent at how he was always at the center of protection even though he did not contribute all this time. There was even a Level Six Great Wizard who publicly said that he wanted Kevin’s daughter, Maria, to become his Subordinate Wizard, serving him. The man clearly had his eye on his daughter’s talent, as well as Maria’s beauty.

Although Maria was not as pretty as Ice Orchid, she was better in that she had a pure and innocent aura, plus she was extremely talented. More than one Great Wizard had already expressed such a notion.

These greedy people wanted to use him to force his daughter to obey. They wanted to corner the two of them, making their situation even harder, so that Kevin and Maria had to beg for their help of their own accord. Faced with such people, Kevin tried his best to maintain his image as a powerful Contractor.

Even though this image was fading and seeming more unlikely by the day, his excuse was that the Colossal Dragon he had a contract with was too powerful, so the price of summoning was too high, making him reluctant to pay it. Such an excuse could only be used once or twice, and if he used it too many times, the Contractors with plenty of inside knowledge would start to suspect him.

“Relax, when I need to summon it, I will.” Kevin tried to act steady and confident, using this impression to stay the hands of those restless onlookers.

Ice Orchid seemed to have been become suspicious as well. She smiled and did not say anything else before she walked away.

“When the time comes, we can use your Contract Colossal Dragon as one of our trump cards at the very end. If you put in an application like that, Master Blue Void might even agree. Hahaha…” The voice of Gergenfor, a Contractor, came faintly from a tent nearby.

Out of all the observers, this guy was the one who put the least effort into hiding his intentions. He was practically drooling for Maria, and had wanted her to become his Subordinate Wizard many times, offering generous pay and conditions.

But Maria had rejected him each time.

On the surface, Kevin’s expression did not change at all, as though he never heard this voice.

“Father…” Maria walked up to him.

“Don’t worry, it’s fine.” Kevin gripped his daughter’s hand tightly. He wanted desperately to give her a sense of security, but clearly, he seemed even more helpless right now than he ever had.

Seeing Maria’s expression of worry, Kevin was even more determined to protect her. He must never summon that thing casually, or else if they saw through him… Maria would be in danger!

It was not fun, being targeted by these Contractors. These Contractors were all either extremely powerful and confident in themselves, or else they were extremely reckless and had thrown all caution to the winds. There were more of the latter than the former. Most of these people could no longer continue levelling up, that was why they decided to make one last insane gamble. Such people were greedy and selfish, and at crucial moments, legal restrictions meant nothing to them. There was only power; power was the only weapon that could protect them.

“Father, please tell me, your Contract Dragon…” Maria transmitted her voice to him using a spell.

“It’s fine, it’s fine…” Maria was too innocent, so Kevin did not dare to tell her the truth. It would truly be troublesome if she accidentally let it slip to someone.

“Who knows? Maybe it’ll be over before we even have to summon it.” Kevin comforted his daughter with words that even he did not believe.

The night grew darker.

Kevin was one of the very few Contract Wizards who had never summoned his Contract Dragon, so he was also one of the main targets for all the rumors and slander.

The team continued forward and spent several more days before they finally arrived at what seemed to be the very center of the entire Underground City — a huge plaza of darkness.

There was a tall and large black statue in the plaza, depicting a plus-sized butcher armed with a giant worn cleaver. He wore clothes that were barely better than rags, and there was a brutal, cruel smile on his face as he stood motionlessly in the plaza. It seemed as though he had been there for a very, very long time.

Blue Void ordered the team to stop.

“I sense the aura of death…”

“You are right, Master Blue Void, there is indeed a very powerful whirlpool of negative energy here. It is highly likely that there are many Undead Creatures here,” added the old Wizard who was his vice captain.

“Let’s make camp here first. We need to set up our defense system if we want to deal with a hoard of the Undead.”

Blue Void nodded.

A large pitch-black Demon Core appeared in his hands. It was a Level Six Demon Core, and its function was to summon his Contract Demon, a Dual-Headed Hell Black Dragon.